<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>booxi &#187; business management</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.booxi.com/blog/tag/management/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.booxi.com/blog</link>
	<description>booxi</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2017 18:59:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
		<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
		<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>http://wordpress.org/?v=3.9.1</generator>
	<item>
		<title>booxi was at the ESI in Montreal !</title>
		<link>https://www.booxi.com/blog/booxi-was-at-the-esi-in-montreal/</link>
		<comments>https://www.booxi.com/blog/booxi-was-at-the-esi-in-montreal/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2016 22:22:59 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Astrid Bertout]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[business management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[trade show]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.booxi.com/blog/?p=706</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[On October 16th and 17th, booxi was at the ESI in Montreal and our CEO M. Daniel Laplante was on of the speakers. Overview of this presentation full of business tips. ]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2 style="text-align: center"><img class="float_top aligncenter wp-image-609 size-full" src="https://booxi-live-wp-storage.storage.googleapis.com/SpaShow2016_post.jpg" alt="appointment sms reminder" width="1200" height="600" />October 16th and 17th, booxi was at the Esthetique Spa International and Daniel Laplante, our CEO, was one of the speakers.</h2>
<p><div class="creativ-shortcode creativ-shortcode-cols  creativ-shortcode-cols-half-half "></div><div class="creativ-shortcode creativ-shortcode-col creativ-shortcode-col-a"><div class="creativ-shortcode-col-inner"><p>The conference “How to Get More Revenues With Less Efforts : using simple and affordable online tools” was a success with a room that was full. M. Laplante was talking about the market statistics, trends, tools, and simple methods to get more results with less efforts. A set of tips easy to apply and providing amazing results.</p>
<p><img class="aligncenter wp-image-621" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/08YVo-RREDMKr0eNTjFyZwmOp1W6j-O8i_QDWRIw-S3nEStawaJffMWBlt28vY-Q_-hRp5Oe2s-vsNWb4RSs6A=s0" alt="daniel laplante" width="300" height="275" /></p>
</div></div><div class="creativ-shortcode creativ-shortcode-col creativ-shortcode-col-b"><div class="creativ-shortcode-col-inner"></div></div><br />
Your customers are online, you have to be there too. Which is why the conference was talking about tools adapted, affordable and easy to use.</p>
<hr class="dash" />
<p>We were there at our booth to answer questions about our smart appointment booking solution. It was also a privilege to receive some of our users, who wanted to share their experience with us, and to learn that they cannot imagine a life without booxi anymore.</p>
<table style="height: auto;margin-bottom: 0px">
<tbody>
<tr>
<td style="width: 50px !important"><img class="img_zoom size-full wp-image-726 alignleft" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/zjbgVl3skHLg0VgGdwrswiswhfO3NqyPVqnOMIg-xIuJ0HO3F3njrh458bHJg9HhBH220UGgnwY-NEwQeQJn=s0" alt="affiliate_b" width="40" height="40" /></td>
<td><strong>A Revenue Increase of Over $6000</strong></td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>
<p>For example, one of our customers saw her revenues increase by over $6000 in the last year, by avoiding no-shows (which she estimated to be 3 per week). 3 appointments * $40 = $120 *50 weeks = $6000. With a cost of $400, her return on investment for using booxi has been largely proven.</p>
<table style="height: auto;margin-bottom: 0px">
<tbody>
<tr>
<td style="width: 50px !important"><img class="img_zoom aligncenter size-full wp-image-728" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/B4aqCMrjcuzc2pSGKKEGQxEDR9CWqFt0ElOiLPjUrrKqoSEUGKw2L87rcqrvWuJafLej7WuIrWQ0xn6Z45c5n68=s0" alt="website_done_b" /></td>
<td><strong>A Competitive Advantage, That Also Saves a Lot of Time</strong></td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>
<p>Another customer explained to us that since she started offering online appointment booking, many customers from her competition became her customers because they like online appointment booking and SMS reminders. A crucial competitive advantage, that in addition of saving you time, will also attract new customers.</p>
<p style="text-align: center"><strong>Don’t waste time anymore, enjoy the benefits provided by booxi and easily increase your revenues</strong></p>
<p style="text-align: center"><a href="https://www.booxi.com/business/signup" class="creativ-shortcode creativ-shortcode-button creativ-shortcode-button-colour-allgreen creativ-shortcode-button-size-medium creativ-shortcode-button-edge-straight" target="_blank">Try it</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.booxi.com/blog/booxi-was-at-the-esi-in-montreal/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Manage the availability of resources such as rooms and equipments for your appointments</title>
		<link>https://www.booxi.com/blog/manage-the-availability-of-resources-such-as-rooms-and-equipments-for-your-appointments/</link>
		<comments>https://www.booxi.com/blog/manage-the-availability-of-resources-such-as-rooms-and-equipments-for-your-appointments/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2016 19:13:03 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Astrid Bertout]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Product Features]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[business management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[online booking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[resources]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.booxi.com/blog-dev/?p=29</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[No more headhaches, no more wasting time to manage your rooms and equipment and your appointment with booxi. ]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><div class="creativ-shortcode creativ-shortcode-cols  creativ-shortcode-cols-half-half "><div class="creativ-shortcode creativ-shortcode-col creativ-shortcode-col-a"><div class="creativ-shortcode-col-inner"><p>With booxi, you now have the ability to manage the availability of resources like rooms and equipments. You view the calendar of availability of each resource and reserve a resource for an appointment.</p>
</div></div><br />
<div class="creativ-shortcode creativ-shortcode-col creativ-shortcode-col-b"><div class="creativ-shortcode-col-inner"></div></div></p>
<ul>
<li>Resource Management</li>
<li>Resource Calendar</li>
<li>Reserve a Resource</div></li>
</ul>
<hr />
<h3>Resource Management</h3>
<p>You have access to the list of your resources from the main menu, and can add new resources by clicking on the <img style="font-weight: normal;color: #000000" src="https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/d-d1owrG3OfqLu5jzx27UDRZ-kiIUbKyMCziFZNpJbVKGy8tfDg5oG2vyNffT0WvQS9dUNwQy6XagqR7wj7VRrVxlp_GEFh6SchX9ig9tYgSmy3q7_2CeWVsdIh7Rxk9LW-Cb6pC" alt="" /> button. To modify, simply select the resource from the list.</p>
<p><img class="shadow_medium aligncenter" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/LNLVIhH5fOx8WiBbmPQO5qVg9AVEL_Nmvw2B1ftVTNpirvxFdzS8XIZ5ASL8MVXV7fizmeZrRg0l8l-IvWqZdUVWJhCtrL59ZQlSo1Lmc7odrUNQD73j9pIaGsrg_1XFH6A7tqGs" alt="section resources in booxi" width="560" height="563" /></p>
<p>Each resource has a name and a capacity, a list of services requiring this type of resource, a weekly availability schedule, and appointment rules.</p>
<p><img class="shadow_medium aligncenter" style="font-weight: normal;color: #000000" src="https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/cToLWbR35Kitf0Q9V0kTEwBgHFOF_IeuW39mZe79A_NcKMqJ5bpxnrCNcJBYvnwn7A1OZIFNqjyuufZC541xTO9st1lBPpdCaAtfODC4bbeZQNMR9BAwgHNqqsyhPTdI6RpXv3zM" alt="resource creation" width="624" height="468" /></p>
<p>The appointment rules allow you to share the resource’s calendar with the personnel, and adjust the appointment interval.</p>
<h3>Resource Calendar</h3>
<p>You can access the calendar of each resource by clicking on the calendar selection, the same way you access each personnel’s calendar. From the choice of personnel’s calendar, click on the resource tab to access the choice of resource, and select a resource. You can also add a mix of resource and personnel calendars in your week view.</p>
<p><img class="shadow_medium aligncenter" style="font-weight: normal;color: #000000" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/q3xxd_HCHa7F6zxQXWGdAldDyKHXdvJQQGUyJ4qNR82ykVZJ-IRP5bdWZoGyUcQF4Dm5mKDTx7oPSsQUOVO8wX-sILlB5-SwvYZA85zfb04ubKripxGsQveQhtb9xWdz-lg53nH9" alt="resource calendar" width="317" height="259" /></p>
<h3>Reserve a resource</h3>
<p>When you add an appointment to your calendar, you can now select and reserve a resource for this appointment, the same way you do for the personnel. Simply click on the list of resources and select one. The list will also show you the availability of the resource according to the time of the requested appointment.</p>
<p><img class="shadow_medium aligncenter" style="font-weight: normal;color: #000000" src="https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-Z2KU7kqWSLqJB-uWNaZzVVV5_D95mOmpqOk-Gt09O0FH1qvOFpIKa8x1Zhp5pEXunpme5r1c0i2K_jOZBnfuz5pSeheL_kZ5npLCeE1yFS3x4XfiILTlzoNR4wy0Swck8FUTzRY" alt="link an appointment with a resource" width="468" height="771" /></p>
<p>Once the resource is selected and the appointment is added, booxi will add the reservation to the selected resource’s calendar. If the reservation cannot be completed, booxi will advise you of the problem.</p>
<p><strong>That’s it, as simple as that</strong>! You can now relieve yourself of the headache of manage resource availability.</p>
<hr />
<p>Want to try it ? Create your booxi account and enjoy 30 day free.<br />
<span style="line-height: 21.6px">Try it now &#8211; No credit card required.</span></p>
<p style="text-align: center"><span style="line-height: 21.6px"><br />
<a href="https://www.booxi.com/business/signup" class="creativ-shortcode creativ-shortcode-button creativ-shortcode-button-colour-allgreen creativ-shortcode-button-size-medium creativ-shortcode-button-edge-straight" target="_blank">Try it for free </a></span></p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.booxi.com/blog/manage-the-availability-of-resources-such-as-rooms-and-equipments-for-your-appointments/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Save a lot of time by managing all your appointments with booxi.</title>
		<link>https://www.booxi.com/blog/managing-all-your-appointments-using-booxi/</link>
		<comments>https://www.booxi.com/blog/managing-all-your-appointments-using-booxi/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2016 19:07:30 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Astrid Bertout]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Business Tips]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[business management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[online booking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[time saving]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.booxi.com/blog-dev/?p=24</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[This article shows you how and why booxi will help you to optimize your time and your appointments management.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img class="img_zoom aligncenter wp-image-810 size-full" src="https://booxi-live-wp-storage.storage.googleapis.com/AdobeStock_949061862.png" alt="online appointment management solution" width="1200" height="800" /><div class="creativ-shortcode creativ-shortcode-cols  creativ-shortcode-cols-half-half "><div class="creativ-shortcode creativ-shortcode-col creativ-shortcode-col-a"><div class="creativ-shortcode-col-inner"><p>This article is about the benefits of using booxi to manage all your appointments.</p>
</div></div><div class="creativ-shortcode creativ-shortcode-col creativ-shortcode-col-b"><div class="creativ-shortcode-col-inner"></div></div></p>
<ul>
<li>Using both a paper agenda and booxi</li>
<li>The benefits of using booxi to manage all your appointments</li>
<li>Build a clientele</li>
<li>You set the rules, booxi does the job</li>
<li>Managing your work schedule</li>
<li>Managing your availability</li>
<li>You keep the control</div></li>
</ul>
<hr />
<p>Change is good, change is opportunity, however change requires will and time to adapt. The good news is that booxi requires very little change in the way you do things; while it brings so much in return.  Going from a paper agenda to a software one can be seen as a big step for some of us, but the benefits are too important to spend one more day without it.</p>
<h3>Using both a paper agenda and booxi</h3>
<p>booxi gives you the flexibility to manage your appointments your way, which means that you always stay in full control. However you can choose to do it in the most efficient way and save lots of time or progressively and start with continuing to use both your paper agenda and booxi at the same time.</p>
<p>Some professionals choose to use booxi just to get appointment requests. They get online without displaying their availability, they receive appointment requests from clients, confirm them in booxi or with the client on the phone, and they write down the appointments in a paper agenda.</p>
<p>With this method:</p>
<ul>
<li>Clients can&#8217;t choose the exact time of their appointment as booxi does not show your availability.</li>
<li>Only the clients booked in booxi can benefit from email/SMS confirmation and reminders.</li>
<li>It is also impossible to share schedule information with your team.</li>
<li>You won&#8217;t get a full client list in booxi and incomplete appointment history.</li>
<li>On the other hand, you keep using your paper agenda.</li>
</ul>
<h3>The benefits of using booxi to manage all your appointments</h3>
<p>The most efficient way to manage your appointments is to use booxi for all of them. Both you and your clients will greatly benefit from that.</p>
<p>How do your clients benefit from booxi when they book with it?</p>
<ul>
<li>They can see what is your availability, and pick the time slot that best suits them.</li>
<li>They can book at anytime, even when you are closed, without going through the unpleasant voice mail exchange game.</li>
<li>They receive a confirmation and a reminder message via email or SMS.</li>
</ul>
<p><img class="aligncenter wp-image-122 size-full" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/uDOSpJ6TfXTbR65n0NePoTDHEiFmg3H0wKWgcs_I7F5U5XOMZrnIakwwA3YdhyEZ5jPJUhjXK5Anx2-VcdjrIQ=s0" alt="offer online appointment booking to your customers" width="938" height="547" /></p>
<p>How do you benefit from booxi when you use it for ALL your appointments?</p>
<ul>
<li>You automatically build a clientele as booxi makes sure to create a client record for all your clients.</li>
<li>You can track appointments history for each client &#8211; which means better service, metrics and marketing.</li>
<li>You can save even more time, by telling booxi to automatically confirm appointments &#8211; in respect with your appointment rules.</li>
<li>Your team has access to their updated schedule at all time &#8211; you save time, and prevent schedule conflicts, and double booking.</li>
<li>All your clients get confirmations and reminders &#8211; which greatly contribute to reduce no shows and calls to inquire about the address.</li>
</ul>
<p><img class="img_zoom aligncenter wp-image-124 size-large" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/0UO00oNxj7q_lM0gw6OxvyKsdMQPWoqlljZBMm7pmu69WfgIKFVrPvKXEc9utRWApsTUJltH1T7M07Ue4FwX=s1024" alt="calendar" width="1024" height="1024" /></p>
<h3>Build a clientele</h3>
<p>Whenever you add an appointment for a new client, booxi automatically creates a client record and start keeping track of his appointments. This way, you know when was his last visit, what service was given and who took care of him. Knowing your client helps improving the service quality and build better relationships. You can leverage your client list (CRM) by analyse it (booxi will do it for you) and target specific clients to send them messages and promotions by email. Use for retention, fidelity or to get back old clients.</p>
<h2><img class="aligncenter wp-image-126 size-large" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/XIZqr--RZPu3qwaND5I_n_yeCQAxHj77AIgEwv87EXQvP63N1xbtse3QexbQZ8HJFWbGcNbaqf1L3EYwc1tkl6k=s1024" alt="Track appointment history" width="1024" height="1024" /></h2>
<h3>You set the rules, booxi does the job<img class="alignright wp-image-127" src="https://booxi-live-wp-storage.storage.googleapis.com/rules.png" alt="appointment rules" width="400" height="461" /></h3>
<p>booxi manages your availability and can automatically confirm appointments according to your rules. You can define those rules for your business in general, a specific service or a specific member of your personnel.</p>
<p>Here are a few examples of these rules:</p>
<p>You can display your availability online or ask the clients to provide some when they book online. Displaying your availability saves you lots of time; while asking the client&#8217;s availability gives you more control.</p>
<ul>
<li><span style="line-height: 21.6px">Disable the personnel selection for a specific service, so you can dispatch appointments yourself and better balance the workload.</span></li>
<li><span style="line-height: 21.6px">Prevent last minute bookings or bookings too much time in advance by setting limits.</span></li>
<li><span style="line-height: 21.6px">Confirm appointments automatically, manually or after a delay.</span></li>
</ul>
<p>You basically keep control over your availability, appointments and personnel according to your rules.</p>
<h3>Managing your work schedule</h3>
<p>You can define your work schedule by using the open business hours, define a weekly schedule per personnel or by simply adding available time slots to your calendar on a weekly/biweekly basis. For example, if one week you decide to open on a Sunday because a special event is coming, you can add an available time slot of 8 hours for that specific date.</p>
<h3>Managing your availability</h3>
<p>booxi identifies your availability by first looking at your work schedule, adding any available time slot you may have added to your calendar, and finally, removing all occupied time slots whether they are busy slots or appointments. When booking an appointment, your clients will not be able to see nor book occupied time slots. Using only booxi for all your appointments keeps your schedule accurate at all time. If you still use a paper agenda, you may have to keep your booxi calendar updated manually.</p>
<table>
<tbody>
<tr>
<td valign="top">
<h3 style="font-weight: 600">Enter your work schedule</h3>
<h3><img class="img_zoom size-full wp-image-137" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/tQ22WtBlWglNdLLLY-GravkUEx467k5mo_BrgI8seXTpHxMg1Dki-QTur6v65UnnUKTdT8zjGuk80Zk1P0pq=s0" alt="work schedule" /></h3>
</td>
<td style="padding-left: 2em" valign="top">
<h3 style="font-weight: 600">Add any extra availability</h3>
<h3><img class="img_zoom size-full wp-image-131" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/Pzq16S1W7oCq5Sctx7V3Wo4ITz1GcLQJOmT5f7N8AT0t5LIr6d1Un3hz8I50bB-LFSlfIzb2l-btw29lamApb28=s0" alt="available slot" /></h3>
<h3 style="font-weight: 600">Add any busy time</h3>
<h3><img class="img_zoom size-full wp-image-132" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/LIibwCBpb06Fy41Lqd-bD4JLKmHl1zKCS8r4PSetkhAkHSK-VnBfalXoAoBUJBdi-OORVfyRmL4kuEJeVA4q2CY=s0" alt="busy time" /></h3>
<h3 style="font-weight: 600">Calculate booked appointments</h3>
<h3><img class="img_zoom size-full wp-image-133" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/t_MnSWbExR2gPK5EFzWypyPlz-nWMTqEgLV3YjlC3KWkPi1l_MhhcScz2fPmKgCDdfChOO2QwA2GZ_84T-ijIpk=s0" alt="rendezvous" /></h3>
<h3 style="font-weight: 600">Equals : Availability</h3>
<h3 class="fnt_col999 fx_fnt_14">booxi will evaluate your schedule, existing appointments and time blocks to calculate your actual available.</h3>
</td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>
<h3>You keep the control</h3>
<p>No matter what the appointment rules and availability schedules are, you can always decide to bypass them, double book, book outside your work hours or book whenever you want, as you are always in full control. However your clients will not have this luxury.</p>
<h3>Things to remember</h3>
<ul>
<li>For each appointment, booxi provides email confirmation and SMS reminder</li>
<li><span style="line-height: 21.6px">booxi automatically creates new client records</span></li>
<li><span style="line-height: 21.6px">booxi keeps track of all your clients appointments &#8211; history</span></li>
<li><span style="line-height: 21.6px">Your clients can select a specific available time slot when they book online</span></li>
<li><span style="line-height: 21.6px">You always stay in control</span></li>
<li><span style="line-height: 21.6px">The more you use booxi, the more time and money you save, therefore the more efficient you become.</span></li>
</ul>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.booxi.com/blog/managing-all-your-appointments-using-booxi/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to update your staff?</title>
		<link>https://www.booxi.com/blog/tutorial-update-your-staff/</link>
		<comments>https://www.booxi.com/blog/tutorial-update-your-staff/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2016 18:58:55 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Astrid Bertout]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Tutorials]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[business management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[staff]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[team]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.booxi.com/blog-dev/?p=18</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[In this tutorial, we will show you how to well set up all the information about your staff in your booxi account.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="creativ-shortcode creativ-shortcode-cols  creativ-shortcode-cols-half-half "><div class="creativ-shortcode creativ-shortcode-col creativ-shortcode-col-a"><div class="creativ-shortcode-col-inner"><p>In this step by step tutorial, we will demonstrate you how to update your personnel and display your team on your booxi website.</p>
</div></div><div class="creativ-shortcode creativ-shortcode-col creativ-shortcode-col-b"><div class="creativ-shortcode-col-inner"></p>
<ul>
<li>Add and modify a staff.</li>
<li>Associate a picture to a staff.</li>
<li>Modify the work hours schedule of a staff.</li>
<li>Assign services to a staff.</li>
<li>Review the appointment rules of a staff.</li>
</ul>
<p>
</div></div></div>
<hr />
<p>You must first be signed in your booxi account to complete the following steps.</p>
<h3>Step 1 &#8211; Access your list of staff</h3>
<p>By default, a new booxi account only has one personnel, yourself. You may add members of your personnel for every person who takes appointments with clients, or any booxi users. From the main menu located on the left side of the page, click on Personnel to access the list of your personnel. <img class="aligncenter" style="font-weight: normal;color: #000000" src="https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/GFXpyQtKfST8RoV6IkvSobHdBBPXI0Lm1YCEGkmjbRLuUlsImq4O3UosRBDakaG6HXY_1UQBfseYYLJPCFV4cDNslAOyYIPIl-syp1YnWAXt_NXGvSrdfTwq4ArrTSurj887v7U" alt="section personnel on booxi" width="640" height="461" /></p>
<h3>Step 2 &#8211; Add a new staff</h3>
<p>You can add personnel to manage appointments for them, or to simply to show your entire team on your website. You can disable online booking for a specific personnel, but we strongly encourage you to enable booking for all of your personnel. For a receptionist, you can add a personnel without setting the profile status to online; this way the person will have access to booxi, and will not be displayed in your website.</p>
<ol>
<li>Click on the <img style="font-weight: normal;color: #000000" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/9IKUy-79mz5gMwNymJl4qWmgOmS_sB_Bh2uJGLEJu3haj-i38VvnMv-PiN_tOxof3MRacZF895FCsgUU5PDHR2P7PaQpHTNF8tA8vd9X3oqaEOMZjPHSX34HQDU9tk854OAlDKQ" alt="" />icon at the top of the list of personnel to add a new personnel.</li>
<li>Provide a First and Last name that will be displayed online.</li>
<li>Provide an Email Address that will be used by booxi to communicate with this person, but will not be displayed online.</li>
<li>Check the option Invite to join booxi, if you wish to invite this person to use booxi. You can also do this later.</li>
<li>Click on Create and your new personnel is created.<img class="aligncenter" style="color: #000000" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/Ayb9WAfMFttS_uRY3tQraIHQY_bB2PWO0feb15l4NWWYnqMvMAxI5iMGnT_YG8qjFBRaQx8UxWHNQ9Qzdr-rHtjMoZTnLRU9C-KfCMFG9CiYSnF4O1kKHwLOWrmkhzrhxKWEwTE" alt="invite a personnel to use booxi" width="414" height="346" /></li>
<li>See the next step Modify a personnel for the full list of features.</li>
</ol>
<h3>Step 3 &#8211; Modify a personnel</h3>
<p>The profile of each personnel gives you access to its details, assigned services, work hours schedule, appointment rules and associated picture.</p>
<ol>
<li>Select a member of your personnel from the list.</li>
<li>Click on Personnel Details. <img class="aligncenter" style="font-weight: normal;color: #000000" src="https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/ccdaWd1adjkxISmJDw6aeazFoQNDmDyLGG0KDoYWbEHc40ZMrmfxuONvbhrsATpBvOnDyyl0En7kJvKLY8xUEriZw0IWH60AcznHYd6AMd5x3SW5WOyxB8Rgoly4BDx0W0UpyFE" alt="Add personnel Details" width="640" height="447" /></li>
<li>You can modify the First and Last name which will be displayed online.</li>
<li>Change the Position to reflect what is the profession of this person.</li>
<li>Provide a Mobile and Work phone number which will not be displayed online, but used to communicate with the person.</li>
<li>Provide an Email address, not displayed online and also used to communicate with the person.</li>
<li>Finally provide a Bio that promotes and sell the person.</li>
<li>Once completed, click on Save at the top of the form to save your changes, or Undo to cancel your changes.<img class="aligncenter" style="color: #000000" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/8y5qRYYZmX_BfS-V_kX4R60uYc8UReGfz7mRGkKR8rBYyDTp1B1rlX3AMItjZ3Ypq9FJvNkDFtEbqbsdQ6aJxwiRml8FYM7SmeLjsRwEXy6GI8lVe5FHzI3uWdsa8bBlu2XdNAw" alt="save / undo" width="259" height="52" /></li>
</ol>
<h3>Step 4 &#8211; Associate a picture to a personnel</h3>
<p>You can apply a picture to each personnel or leave it blank. Providing a picture for your personnel will make your booxi website look more attractive to customers and ease their trust. <img class="aligncenter" style="font-weight: normal;color: #000000" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/x2HtxCPgez1DGnjOSyPSqfFKIf7HyA27_3-uHfB5U79kuGuthq61IZTq80hnIdEVIAuYBP7aKY8K14SWb4LrvdLaz6wFGqV9JwIZO9SZFRtgrWPXTfX_iOvJ1R_zpxGvnPSWBYE" alt="add a profile picture" width="261" height="263" /></p>
<ol>
<li>You can set or change the personnel profile picture by clicking on the <img style="color: #000000" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/wwh4j145ZELGoQQW_R2Bt6fB_Jze-EwTdKNmf-sMhprlO0DvYB23sDKM_krYukD2YUZCbzkk4X4Ig7V5ok-COHBQtwUOKmCHIfjrrkXo0Tr8ObwNgQ9_LotZRTOv-cP9PqWE6_k" alt="" /> icon at the bottom of the current profile picture. You may also use our mobile app to take a picture with your smartphone and apply it to this member of your personnel.
<ul>
<li>Click on the Upload a photo button to upload a picture from your computer or tablet.</li>
<li>Click on the Reset to default button to remove the picture so this personnel does not have any picture.</li>
<li>Use the 4 blue dots to crop or select the visible portion of the picture.</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Click on Save the photo button to save your changes, or click on the X at the top to cancel your changes.</li>
</ol>
<h3><img class="aligncenter" style="color: #000000" src="https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/ArxT8-LLsMJbhOg2gHRu8ZTTqI9yTzDHs-oQFtpIMvBc4hmNmTwhn3gY1rn-U45YiAXlhe0qvwQqA--DG-xlbLdRN9zcnybsZ1MlYRjthwjNyEBgKUwis54RlmEp1gLJQv5-9yY" alt="how to crop the image" width="640" height="406" /> Step 5 &#8211; Assign Services</h3>
<p>You can select which services this personnel offers, so that clients can only request an appointment for the right service with this personnel.</p>
<ol>
<li>Click on Assigned Services.</li>
<li>Click to apply a check mark on each service the personnel offers.<img class="aligncenter" style="color: #000000" src="https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/2fpcnOtPkH_nyTCx2MyZdW9M08W_Mfi39C9F7FrDzt-Lkxwtbk_WkaRAo9Z0iO_HKwU8lrFfG7kNbDfLfIYoT-zbY1AwRIlgXlOX86TPBp3O96NXiZ6DdhARV0k1uz0qaGuaFeI" alt="assigned services per personnel" width="640" height="427" /></li>
<li>Once done, click on Save at the top of the form to save your changes, or Undo to cancel your changes.<img class="aligncenter" style="color: #000000" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/8y5qRYYZmX_BfS-V_kX4R60uYc8UReGfz7mRGkKR8rBYyDTp1B1rlX3AMItjZ3Ypq9FJvNkDFtEbqbsdQ6aJxwiRml8FYM7SmeLjsRwEXy6GI8lVe5FHzI3uWdsa8bBlu2XdNAw" alt="" /></li>
</ol>
<h3>Step 6 &#8211; Review the Work Schedule</h3>
<p>If this personnel always works during open hours, you can simply set his work schedule at Open Business Hours; if he has different weekly schedule, choose Work Schedule and provide the schedule following the steps below; but if his schedule is decided on a daily, weekly or biweekly basis, you should choose Free Calendar and add available time slots directly in his calendar. To build a weekly schedule, specify time slots for each day of the week. You may provide multiple time slots per day, if for example the personnel has a lunch break (9:00-12:00 and another one for 13:00-18:00). You may also leave a day without time slots if he does not work on that day.</p>
<ol>
<li>Click on Work Schedule to review the schedule.
<ul>
<li>Provide a start and end time for each time slot.</li>
<li>Click on X to remove a time slot.</li>
<li>Click on + to add another time slot.<img class="aligncenter" style="color: #000000" src="https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/jFauvBHWWz_LGjC4LQUe8FUGuictnAMwjLSh_fImKboOAaUOxJvZwU1EweK2TG3lEHkUUQBHIqBG_UF8t5MP8ZErxetU8cLYf5AC6XBzkE2h4NLINdKViG2t_y7QVVXOPXzvZbM" alt="work schedule per personnel" width="559" height="374" /></li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Once you have completed your changes, click on Save to save them or Undo to cancel.<img class="aligncenter" style="color: #000000" src="https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/ZHCC8Nb1gvttolXAjfo1uinBgcmkl5IUSLFU6OUwFIvtZC0sfm-Y3U-EqpEP0GmzRWa7AH6sBw6laNq5-wKGIS9xJYdOc_RbQXSXwNZjqfdXpyzmW3A1KE8oKtBtez7PtoIeKPg" alt="save / undo" width="259" height="52" /></li>
</ol>
<h3>Step 7 &#8211; Review Appointment Rules</h3>
<p>The appointment rules allows you to tell booxi how to manage appointments and availability for this personnel.</p>
<ol>
<ol>
<li>Click on Appointment Rules to access and modify the rules.</li>
</ol>
</ol>
<p><strong>Enable Online Booking</strong> This rule allows you by disabling it to prevent consumers to book appointments online with this personnel. If for some reasons you want to display this personnel online, but prevent clients from booking online; you can uncheck the option to disable it. <strong>Show Availability Online</strong> This rule will display and offer to consumers the time slots that are still available, so they can book a specific time. It is always better to show your availability, because consumers love it and you save time; however, if you which to keep more control over your schedule and decide whether you will be available or not depending on how busy your week gets, you may disable this options. You can also use this option to receive appointment request and adjust the duration of the appointment after talking to the client. When this rule is disabled (no checkmark), the client is asked to provide up to 5 available time slots from his schedule, which means you receive a request with time options like for example : Monday, April 6th from 9:00 to 12:00; Wednesday April 7th from 12:00 to 17:00; and Friday from 17:00 to 21:00. You can than find a matching availability in your schedule and confirm a time to your client. <strong>Appointment Interval</strong> This rule allows you to fix the interval of available time slots that will be presented to a client when booking online. It is suggested to set this interval to the duration of the shortest service you offer. For example, if you only offer 1 hour appointments, set it to 60 min to prevent clients from booking at 8h15, 8h30 or 8h45, leaving empty time slots of less than 1 hour. With an interval of 60 min, clients will only be able to request appointments at 8h00, 9h00, 10h00 and so on. We will look at the other rules in another tutorial. <img class="aligncenter" style="color: #000000" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/KNmTo2OfUOvaDeBd1xKSL4zoY4MlgCwC6FMWZB-x8ZI9B3EMbgmiTx4j6A6KyuzDvSQoBBneU0pZpsfzdfypG3ZkrpnicUQa4uka2wCq35KaBK1yHGyb-eWoy4_w0swW_ysZLDU" alt="appointment rules per personnel" width="462" height="515" /></p>
<ol>
<li>If you made any changes, click on Save at the top of the form to save your changes, or Undo to cancel your changes.<img class="aligncenter" style="color: #000000" src="https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/nhkZ4SK1gnRtkUQf99Hhpsiu5IsIkCPjCHIZo48oSSqhCDny4dri4s4bMmeOHv6zUfq2Aby3HhXWYcrzERVAT-oINBW8iiunCYRWKEDX1eUr9NqyU5iTcHut0Mit005ykczEbkk" alt="save / undo" width="259" height="52" /></li>
</ol>
<h3>Step 8 &#8211; Put this personnel online</h3>
<p>Now that the personnel profile has been completed, you can put it online, so it becomes visible and clients can book appointment with it. The personnel will only be visible if your business is available online.</p>
<ol>
<li>Click on Offline and select Available online.</li>
<li>The status should turn green.<img class="aligncenter" style="color: #000000" src="https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/O13TuR-A28sDa5pl4n6T_HQyrG6If2yLbk8e5PqNOyNsV-Bo9E4DoqByjmgFK6zYnczCcTR4tgPTFh6TUvkJKxRqx5jEnDK1e7RMSqDXq0izKS0-8FkBq73p4-7u4wRiOPkZFA8" alt="personnel statut" width="260" height="347" /></li>
</ol>
<p>You can also Block this personnel and prevent him from using booxi. A personnel blocked will no more be visible online. You are done and can now move on to the Management of your appointments.</p>
<h3>Things to remember</h3>
<ul>
<li>Add personnel to allow clients to book with them &#8211; Each personnel status must be Available online for them to be displayed on your booxi website.</li>
<li>Associate services with each member of your personnel for them to be available to offer those services.</li>
<li>Review the work schedule of each personnel, so booxi knows when they are available.</li>
<li>You can let the clients choose a specific time slot, or ask their availability.</li>
<li>Adding photos and a bios that sell the expertise of your personnel, will bring trust from your clients.</li>
</ul>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.booxi.com/blog/tutorial-update-your-staff/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Update your service offer</title>
		<link>https://www.booxi.com/blog/update-your-service-offer/</link>
		<comments>https://www.booxi.com/blog/update-your-service-offer/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2016 18:55:44 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Astrid Bertout]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Tutorials]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[business management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[online booking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[services]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.booxi.com/blog-dev/?p=16</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[This tutorial shows you how to set up your service offer in your booxi account. ]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><div class="creativ-shortcode creativ-shortcode-cols  creativ-shortcode-cols-half-half "><div class="creativ-shortcode creativ-shortcode-col creativ-shortcode-col-a"><div class="creativ-shortcode-col-inner"><p>In this step by step tutorial, we will demonstrate you how to update your service offer. </p>
</div></div><div class="creativ-shortcode creativ-shortcode-col creativ-shortcode-col-b"><div class="creativ-shortcode-col-inner"></div></div></p>
<ul>
<li>Add and modify services</li>
<li>Add categories to group and classify your services</li>
<li>Associate a picture to a service</li>
<li>Assign personnel to a service</li>
<li>Review the appointment rules of a service.</div></li>
</ul>
<hr />
<p>You must first be signed in your booxi account to complete the tutorial.</p>
<h3>Step 1 &#8211; Access your services list</h3>
<p>From the main menu located on the left side of the page, click on Services to access the list of your services. By default, a new booxi account has only one service Request an appointment, you can modify it or simply disable it and add new services. <img class="shadow_medium aligncenter wp-image-69 size-full" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/T0eOZ_nXhdYGy6Ale9S9N2-DC5EwKCWk8XUIx2KmXSdnb_CgEIGreu6ScjOm4UeVn12I_9CyC6DqnxlJeXeEqQ=s0" alt="services section" width="720" height="518" /></p>
<h3>Step 2 &#8211; Add a new service</h3>
<p>A newly added service is not automatically published online, which gives you plenty of time to review its details before you set it to Available online (visible to clients). You can also group services in categories so it is easier for a client to find the service he is looking for.</p>
<ol>
<li>Click on the <img style="font-weight: normal;color: #000000" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/S1zykcWaU1DkJdJxBHPWznTj46I3xR9oWzeh2W6ZvV-NlVHig9OiDvE7OWhU-PhtasOUUCdUUM6Fx5HUbCpWFp99xvfMG4t4cXUhzWqqLgqzhpK8Ea4vipCTsCWmtkZ0dn9XgOw" alt="" />icon at the top of the service list to add a new service.</li>
<li>Provide a service name that will be displayed online.</li>
<li>Select a category or leave it to the Main Category.</li>
<li>Click on Create and your new service is created.<img class="shadow_medium aligncenter" src="https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/SDgWD9bdUHXog9tw0wiF8vxA67KBcwQdpPh27k4E2BZ6kYTLYNwJOUb1AytKjX-TIe_tx4XGL8uTp1KH6-O6gCIjbUpV1aq71KnOOIaUQ0kgejF_58MIka2eFyg_BzbjlfQEf0g" alt="add a new service" width="414" height="268" /></li>
</ol>
<p>You can display a service online without booking enabled, but we strongly encourage you to enable booking for all of them. See the next step Modify a service for the full list of features.</p>
<h3>Step 3 &#8211; Add a new category</h3>
<p>You can create new categories and associate services to them, so it is easier for a client to find the service he is looking for.</p>
<ol>
<li>Click on the <img style="color: #000000" src="https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/tDCZ5NC56rc2_WaDMjBxl9DOzDJutIng2l-wQ73CqvkpTdykAjzRyVNUr2winswg3O27kKDwzN3WwD7ON8pSx78261dai6RbuY6Q5JNmPtlNjyEvH8ab0lOuidu00WxDrUPwP8s" alt="" />icon at the top of the service list to add a new category.</li>
<li>Provide a category name that will be displayed online</li>
<li>Click on Create and your new category is created.</li>
</ol>
<h3><img class="shadow_medium aligncenter" src="https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/okXcKYDMo_GPDJnD7o-fwkcWS3-JawUtwo4l3tWhjBaaKO6GIJPhsijdBu-63O6iDAeaTRfbfkEkTqVNHAUjWcbP8hSibrAOTyPhL_ZbAkgGwTL3DX-mA8JrxsmiV1gn16DlHDI" alt="add a new category" width="414" height="221" /><br />
Step 4 &#8211; Modify a service</h3>
<p>The profile of each service gives you access to its details, assigned personnel (the ones who offer the service), appointment rules and associated picture.</p>
<ol>
<li>Select a service in the list</li>
<li>Click on Service Details <img class="shadow_medium aligncenter wp-image-70 size-full" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/NMf70tcqbX7920RXvovpKvbuI91fhV71illqgjjelorV486URlFd_fMQnr_dgVO8UkXw6yxS1FIMTaMJhl2k=s0" alt="set up service details" width="720" height="523" /></li>
<li>You can modify the Name which will be displayed online</li>
<li>Change the Category or leave it to General Services (meaning no category)</li>
<li>Set the Location to At My Business if the service will be given at your business address, or At Home if the service will be given at the client’s home or any address provided by the client.</li>
<li>Set a Duration for the service</li>
<li>Set a Price or leave it empty ($0) if you do not wish to display the price online &#8211; we strongly recommend to display the price as clients may only request an appointment if they can see the price.</li>
<li>Finally provide a Description that promotes and sell the service.</li>
<li>Once completed, click on Save at the top of the form to save your changes, or Undo to cancel your changes.<img class="shadow_medium aligncenter wp-image-71 size-full" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/YWE16iC0zsqWrrkn4KulFOHAGqBHLdi8vYfmeBw3VYHQ1ePCD4HDHznc4hVofw6HUF8nFXhTjnoInoHDHFvN8g=s0" alt="save/undo" width="259" height="52" /></li>
</ol>
<h3>Step 5 &#8211; Associate a picture to a service</h3>
<p>You can add a picture to each service or leave it blank. Providing pictures for your services will make your booxi website looks more attractive to clients.<a style="font-weight: bold" href="https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/73HWfduT2_6WoeiTXLmwbcj8Opw-BfjVd_SLL1Zy-4ZTDymRQgmCTwBpMmPYZHQiXrhWu59c59OIzBJ1DuwntwDrIIXhevZde3sAkqbHFIGFzNuvGCJu4dfRKDrWtRdZncIfNw4"><img class="shadow_medium alignright" src="https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/73HWfduT2_6WoeiTXLmwbcj8Opw-BfjVd_SLL1Zy-4ZTDymRQgmCTwBpMmPYZHQiXrhWu59c59OIzBJ1DuwntwDrIIXhevZde3sAkqbHFIGFzNuvGCJu4dfRKDrWtRdZncIfNw4" alt="" width="200" height="199" border="0" /></a> You can set or change the service profile picture by clicking on the small camera icon at the bottom of the current profile picture. You may also use our mobile application to take picture with your smartphone and apply them to your services.</p>
<ol>
<li>Click on the Upload a photo button to upload a picture from your computer or tablet
<ul>
<li>Click on the Reset to default button to remove the picture so this service does not have any picture.</li>
<li>Use the 4 blue dots to crop or select the visible portion of the picture.</li>
<li>Click the Save the photo button to save your changes</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Click on the X at the top to cancel your changes</li>
</ol>
<h3>Step 6 &#8211; Assign Personnel</h3>
<p>You can select which personnel will offer the service, so that clients can only request an appointment with the right personnel.</p>
<ol>
<ol>
<li>Click on Assigned Personnel</li>
<li><span style="line-height: 21.6px">Click to apply a check mark on each member of the personnel that offers the service.</span></li>
</ol>
</ol>
<p><img class="shadow_medium aligncenter wp-image-72 size-full" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/4mcGS2P5M4vV_kmL30_plBnSIU3zzLnJuheGt-Ia_4oIavzFmlwpxJgfSiltjSaplkVOYq8cFsM-Id7h6D6qWXM=s0" alt="assigned personnel to a service" width="672" height="520" /></p>
<ol>
<li>Once done, click on Save at the top of the form to save your changes, or Undo to cancel your changes.<img class="shadow_medium aligncenter wp-image-73 size-full" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/FxEomCS33zjRMDLQO5sgWEGsik4lujXXWNjzPWr_URht17QMl-dz_3WmLDRyvXuJ5tz8BWTkQhFSoKGmlB7l0w=s0" alt="saveundo" width="259" height="52" /></li>
</ol>
<h3>Step 7 &#8211; Review Appointment Rules</h3>
<p>The appointment rules allows you to tell booxi how to manage appointments and availability for this service.</p>
<ol>
<ol>
<li>Click on Appointment Rules to access and modify the rules.</li>
</ol>
</ol>
<p><strong> Enable Online Booking<br />
</strong>This rule allows you to disable online booking and to prevent clients to book this service online. You do so if you want to include this service in your offer but, for some reason, you feel it should not be booked online. For example; if you need to talk to the client to evaluate time and price; you can uncheck the option and disable it.</p>
<p><strong>Show Availability Online</strong><br />
When this rule is activated, clients can select and book a specific available time slots. We recommend that you show your availability because clients prefer that, and because it makes you save time. However, if you wish to keep full control over your schedule and decide whether you will be available or not depending on how your week gets busy, you may disable this option. When disabled (no checkmark), the client is asked to provide up to 5 available time slots from his schedule. This means you receive a request with time options like for example : Monday, April 6th from 9:00 to 12:00; Wednesday April 8th from 12:00 to 17:00; and Friday from 17:00 to 21:00. You can then find a matching availability in your schedule and confirm a time to your client.</p>
<p><strong>Disable Personnel Selection<br />
</strong> This rules allows you to disable the selection of a personnel. If you have multiple personnel taking appointments, your client is usually presented with a choice of personnel, unless you apply this rule. When disabling the personnel selection for a service, clients neither have the option to select a personnel, nor a specific time slot; instead, they have to provide their own availability and you receive an appointment request that must be dispatch to a specific personnel. This is useful when you need to control the workload of your staff and dispatch appointments yourself. We will look at the other rules in another tutorial.</p>
<p><img class="shadow_medium aligncenter" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/1ZpjmZUx2YzvkmrAmwk8-_C40d_ziLxb1PVtXWtekRgTZ_hrxKb8791PImBcOQWAVFaILc16v0b1nacTmmA3VI6UnzPr1i1Cdg9tPluY-WhRO-CGqIDn5oCN9iY1pS3k-i1dvAk" alt="appointment rules" width="452" height="490" /></p>
<ol>
<li>If you made any changes, click on Save at the top of the form to save your changes, or Undo to cancel your changes.<img class="shadow_medium aligncenter wp-image-73 size-full" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/FxEomCS33zjRMDLQO5sgWEGsik4lujXXWNjzPWr_URht17QMl-dz_3WmLDRyvXuJ5tz8BWTkQhFSoKGmlB7l0w=s0" alt="saveundo" width="259" height="52" /></li>
</ol>
<h3>Step 8 &#8211; Put this service online</h3>
<p>Now that the service profile has been completed, you can put it online, so it becomes visible and clients can book appointment with it. The service will only be visible if your business is available online.</p>
<ol>
<li>Click on Offline and select Available online.</li>
<li><span style="line-height: 21.6px"><span style="line-height: 21.6px">The status should turn green.</span></span><img class="shadow_medium aligncenter" src="https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/dkpLY_s-6mm2-4OnMg1ZqEHf3GmUwtfUofovyXb83c6BKlqCZHO964_Et30StoY3cC-wdz0cIgpEE0Auve6l1Je4hXJcmqQ_shPT0vApoh54-jie6OnqWKgX8FEThUww0JwL8ZY" alt="status" width="264" height="246" /></li>
</ol>
<p>You are done and can now move on to the Update your personnel tutorial.</p>
<h3>Things to remember :</h3>
<ul>
<li>You must set the status of a service to online to publish onto your website</li>
<li><span style="line-height: 21.6px">Group services in categories when you offer more than 10 services</span></li>
<li><span style="line-height: 21.6px">You can let the client choose an available time slot in your schedule or ask the client his availability.</span></li>
<li><span style="line-height: 21.6px">You can let the client choose a personnel or not and dispatch the appointments yourself.</span></li>
</ul>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.booxi.com/blog/update-your-service-offer/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>booxi is here to help you</title>
		<link>https://www.booxi.com/blog/booxi-is-here-to-help-you/</link>
		<comments>https://www.booxi.com/blog/booxi-is-here-to-help-you/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2016 18:47:14 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Astrid Bertout]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Tutorials]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[business management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[online visibility]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[time saving]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.booxi.com/blog-dev/?p=12</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Find out why after experiencing booxi you won’t live without it. booxi is so easy to use that you will wonder why you have not started using it before today. ]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><div class="creativ-shortcode creativ-shortcode-cols  creativ-shortcode-cols-half-half "><div class="creativ-shortcode creativ-shortcode-col creativ-shortcode-col-a"><div class="creativ-shortcode-col-inner"><p>
<span class="bx_text24">In this article, we will show you why after experiencing booxi you won’t live without it.</span></p>
</div></div><div class="creativ-shortcode creativ-shortcode-col creativ-shortcode-col-b"><div class="creativ-shortcode-col-inner"></div></div></p>
<ul>
<li>Increase your Visibility</li>
<li>Save Time</li>
<li>Offer a Better Customer Experience</li>
<li>Track your Metrics</div></li>
</ul>
<hr />
<p>booxi is so easy to use that you will wonder why you have not started using it before today. Sign up only takes a minute and provides countless benefits to your business.</p>
<h3>Increase your Visibility</h3>
<p>Let’s start with online visibility for your business, by looking at the website booxi builds for you. The site not only looks good with its cover picture and top class design but it also provides valuable information to customers such as your service offer, your personnel, and your business hours, among various things. booxi optimizes your site for search engines like Google (SEO), so customers can easily find you. No need to pay from $1,000 to $5000 for a website, booxi provides it, included in your membership.<br />
Outdated information on your website is now a thing of the past. With booxi, customers will always find the most updated information as booxi always keeps it updated with you current service offer, prices, personnel, schedule, open hours and so on that are used by you to book appointments in booxi.</p>
<p><img class="shadow_medium aligncenter" src="https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-HeHqoqwpiz8qPuPvRo6IslUAjb6xYgonpVAgfCBFXyiewG3K1S3xdHQrvK-rZ9Py24xaeVcZbnRRQsNLTINi3RRye-PKpI_reHd71VHKYAZ5jVUV_nx2ttNNSAoi6o4YI2V9rw" alt="" width="1421" height="1284" /></p>
<p>You already have a website! That is great because the more online visibility you have, the more costumers and appointment requests it drives to you. You can easily integrate our ‘Book Now’ button in your site, and let costumers book from both places and receive all appointment requests at one central point, into your booxi account.</p>
<h3>Save Time</h3>
<p>Statistics show that professionals spend in average 30 hours a month over the phone to manage their appointments. It takes an average of 10 minutes per appointment to exchange schedule information and finally confirm a time with a client. That means 6 appointments cost you 1 hour of your time, imagine what you could do with those hours&#8230; You can save time and let booxi handle a some of your appointments by inviting your clients to book online.</p>
<p>Clients love online booking because they can book when they have time (even though your business is closed), and take all the time they want to review their schedule. They spare themselves the same trouble as you, by escaping from voicemail exchanges because they too are busy during the day. They also love email confirmation and SMS reminders.</p>
<p>I am sure you can’t imagine yourself manually sending emails for each appointment, then later SMS to remind each clients. However it is has been proven to be one of the most effective ways to reduce no shows and stop loosing the associated revenue. booxi will automatically send an email confirmation for each appointment confirmed, providing all information handy, as well as an SMS or email reminder to make sure no appointment is missed.</p>
<h3>Offer a Better Customer Experience</h3>
<p>booxi can improve the quality of your service with your customers. Allowing customers to book online and sending email confirmations and reminders is just a start. Knowing your customers is key to provide a personalized service that they&#8217;ll talk about to everyone. booxi gives you access to the appointment history and notes of each customer, so you can impress them by remembering when was their last visit and what service you offered.</p>
<p><img class="shadow_medium aligncenter" src="https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/E-Ixe3SS4RYpGwXWGiyFKAcdi2RpBBAGsq_Q7-Nzp7KzEHc_D0HnXTpGtN9am5SO4-wDJDZKLcD0RkWj07cGxLdsO9nw9Uhm2PZbazPbrM8KdXB1tACRf5ib5xt7M3DxLb6oTdQ" alt="" width="1426" height="286" /></p>
<p>You can then use your client list to send them promotion emails, or find out who is due for another appointment. The more you know about your clientele, the more revenue you can get from them.</p>
<h3>Track your Metrics</h3>
<p>If you want to grow your business, you have to know your numbers and track your metrics. If you’re not an accountant or if you don’t have a natural affinity for numbers, let booxi handle this for you.</p>
<p>booxi provides you simple but useful metrics on your business and clientele. This includes metrics on your online visibility, your appointments and your client growth, so you understand better your growth and your clientele&#8217;s demand.</p>
<p><img class="shadow_medium aligncenter wp-image-324 size-full" src="http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/kdCjczhPg15oTOGOcrthQOpjspbXL4MKI-et1yFAWvfDTSzCrAD6GeDCfgYrCuWp2JAV8voSmZ2v3ZB5jNxPCw=s0" alt="stats" width="543" height="562" /></p>
<h3><strong>Things to remember:</strong></h3>
<ul>
<li>booxi builds a website for you.</li>
<li>Online appointment booking will save you time.</li>
<li>Your clients love online booking and email confirmations.</li>
<li>Automatic reminders helps reducing no shows.</li>
<li>Know your numbers to grow your business.</li>
<li>booxi&#8217;s virtual assistant works for you.</li>
</ul>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.booxi.com/blog/booxi-is-here-to-help-you/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>