<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>booxi &#187; Business Tips</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.booxi.com/blog/category/business-tips/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.booxi.com/blog</link>
	<description>booxi</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2017 18:59:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
		<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
		<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>http://wordpress.org/?v=3.9.1</generator>
	<item>
		<title>4 marketing tips to promote your website</title>
		<link>https://www.booxi.com/blog/4-marketing-tips-to-promote-your-website/</link>
		<comments>https://www.booxi.com/blog/4-marketing-tips-to-promote-your-website/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2017 20:06:35 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Astrid Bertout]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Business Tips]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[website]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.booxi.com/blog/?p=1591</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[In a fast-changing digital world, you need to constantly keep up-to-date with new trends to properly promote your business. ]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img class="float_top aligncenter wp-image-1593 size-full" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/mI2GV7mp_t4SMTwvqeifVMod0PXyqvSqLcK8o3uHpUIHOeHQFrYA-BStPzCQcwbfF-q6FNY3pZ2HjUuNxNtLaA=s0" alt="website promotion" width="1200" height="600" /><br />
In a fast-changing digital world, you need to constantly keep up-to-date with new trends to ensure that our business evolves along with the technology. Luckily for you, there are tons of tools available to help you deepen your web knowledge.</p>
<p>Today, WebSelf, one of booxi’s partners gives you 4 marketing tips to promote your website.</p>
<p><b>First, get to know your customers</b></p>
<p>The first step is to determine your target market and get to know your clientele.</p>
<p>This is essential since you will have to take them into account in almost all of your marketing actions, to retain them or simply to win new customers.</p>
<p><i>Your offers, products and services, who are they for?</i></p>
<p>The answer to this question is very important because it will give you an idea of ​​what type of audience you will be dealing with.</p>
<p>When you’ve somewhat determined your target market, you need to learn as much about them as you can. Their buying habits, their gender, their age, etc. The more information you have, the easier it will be to personalize your marketing efforts in order to maximize them.</p>
<p><b>1. Spread the good news</b></p>
<p>Someone once said that a website is a direct reflection of a business. That’s why your online presence, whether it’s through a website, social networks, online directories, etc. must be impeccable. at all times.</p>
<p>When you’re proud of the final result, it’s time to spread the good news and share your website everywhere! Ask for your entourage’s opinion and share a link on your personal social media to get the word out. It will also increase your visibility online and will allow you to win a few customers!</p>
<p><b>2. Use social platforms</b></p>
<p>Do we really need to tell you about the importance of creating business accounts on social networks? Be sure to choose wisely which platform you wish to appear on, and then properly use them. Do not forget that many will use it as a support for their technical questions. Answer all questions and suggestions from your customers and communicate with original and interesting content.<br />
<img class="img_zoom aligncenter size-full wp-image-1594" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/OTIZOfG-rBOquVjwa8ikWXrOgBLr5M3aGOsCOsxpwBz25PY2E4ANFKdrgaX9SvFRw94CXn7LkZDSpHHckAmPcw=s0" alt="social" /></p>
<p><b>3. Increase customer loyalty with a newsletter</b></p>
<p>A great way to retain your current customer base is to send them a newsletter. This is advantageous especially when we know that it is 5x easier and less expensive to retain our current customer base than to find new customers.</p>
<p>Send a newsletter to inform your customers of new things coming up, share your blog articles or simply to remind them that you still exist! WebSelf offers an email collector tool, in the editor, where you can collect your visitors’ e-mail addresses use them to send out a newsletter, for example.</p>
<p><b>4. Set up a reward system</b></p>
<p>Your satisfied customers will be your best brand ambassadors, and you must reward loyalty! There are several kinds of reward systems, whether it&#8217;s sponsorship, ex, offer a discount whenever a client refers you to another, or you offer your customers discounts or gifts after X numbers of purchases. Be careful: Offer only gifts / discounts that are proportional to expenses. You want to retain your customers but you do not want to lose too much money in the process.</p>
<p><a href="http://en.webself.net/">Try creating your free website NOW</a></p>
<p><a href="http://en.webself.net/">Webself</a> is a free and easy tool to create website. Choose your design, add your texts and pictures and publish your website on the Internet. It has never been easier to create a website! No computer knowledge required, only your imagination ! Start building your own website today.</p>
<p><img class="aligncenter wp-image-1596 size-full" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/F6KJa79JK3XNjpj_Vf6w7IzCLewlOCummGNpZNHrx6JNEPg8C9yB4Xlw1K822r9Pk9tNAo0RlsYIMxh7MZzeBdA=s0" alt="webself website creator " width="1440" height="600" /></p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.booxi.com/blog/4-marketing-tips-to-promote-your-website/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>5 Easy Ways to Gain Customer Trust &#8211; Overcoming the Stigma of the Beauty Industry</title>
		<link>https://www.booxi.com/blog/gain-customer-trust/</link>
		<comments>https://www.booxi.com/blog/gain-customer-trust/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2017 19:18:15 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[booxi team​]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Business Tips]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[customer retention]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[user experience]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.booxi.com/blog/?p=1445</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[This article provides beauty salon owners with 5 easy (and actionable) ways on how to present their business as a modern and reliable establishment. ]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img class="float_top aligncenter wp-image-1481 size-full" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/MTwsWMqTEEss7OBeZeMMtLe3LCghFmQYBgw5uukFzqWQo2zvHDsOLJcJfoepnzIaH3wMn0yjNYxIAqzBJOD81fs=s0" alt="trusted beauty salon " width="1200" height="600" />Great customer service and professionalism should be the first things that pop into your head when reading the title.<br />
Beyond that, there are some aspects that aren’t so obvious to everyone. When it comes to their personal appearance, customers want the best they can get and many are reluctant to venture toward new beauty salons in fear of having a disappointing, or worse, an unprofessional experience.</p>
<p>This article provides beauty salon owners with 5 easy (and actionable) ways on how to present their business as a modern and reliable establishment. From working with an efficiency-boosting <a href="https://www.lightspeedhq.com/">POS</a> system and <a href="https://www.booxi.com/en">automated appointment management system</a> to paying close attention to the details of their salon’s physical and online aesthetic, beauty shop owners will access insightful suggestions to improve (or maintain) their image and gain new loyal customers.</p>
<p><strong>1. Offer personal suggestions</strong></p>
<p>Although customers expect your professional advice, they appreciate hearing about your personal experience with the products or services you’re selling. After all, everyone is different and sometimes practical feedback (as opposed to theoretical or technical) can be a little more relevant and relatable. Taking an interest in your client and connecting with them on a personal level shows them you care and you’re gathering the information you need to give them the best advice possible.</p>
<p>On the other hand, this also means you can’t shy away from giving your customer bad news; it’s ok if you’re unable to provide them with every solution in the book. There may come a time where you’ll need to point out that your product or company may not be the right fit for their needs. They’ll appreciate the honesty and you’ll be remembered as the one who gives real advice.</p>
<p>According to <a href="https://www.lightspeedhq.com/blog/2017/09/4-ecommerce-takeaways-lightspeed-speaker-series/">Simon Tooley</a>, Founder &amp; CEO at Maison Etiket, “if someone has that memorable experience, it&#8217;s not about the product they bought, it&#8217;s actually about [the] people they interacted with.” We couldn’t agree more.</p>
<p><strong>2. Listen<br />
</strong></p>
<p>Ever walked into a retail store with sales clerks selling on commission and get pestered about all kinds of products you’re just not interested in? Of course you have &#8211; and chances are you didn’t buy any of those items.</p>
<p>Learn from their mistakes; stick to what your customer is telling you and don’t push unrelated products on them. You won’t sell more and, in fact, you risk losing the entire sale over it. Your expert advice may have convinced a customer to purchase an item or service, but if you sound too eager to increase their basket size, your credibility is undermined and the first thing you sold them on may now be in jeopardy. Are you actually giving good advice or are you simply trying to make a quick sale and saying whatever it is you think they want to hear?</p>
<p>By keeping an open mind, customers will sense that you&#8217;ve got their best interests at heart and be much more receptive and trusting of your professional advice.</p>
<p><img class="aligncenter wp-image-1480 size-large" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/88Z8fCTVjTUCvgHAYvJedsBkGUCPPzdNOpwQKjdvygkSWSa7o8JJodXkwa_nX8nZJlTNMGaCzdsORSmEcP_I=s1024" alt="listen your customers" width="1024" height="1024" /></p>
<p><strong>3. Unleash your psychic skills</strong></p>
<p>This one applies to businesses who’ve cultivated their relationships with customers (which should be all of them!), who are knowledgeable of their offering and have their answers ready.</p>
<p>Chances are, most of your customers ask similar questions and those conversations often lead to the same solutions. Pay attention to what they’re saying, detect patterns in their purchasing behavior and needs, ask the right questions and predict what their next concern might be, addressing it with an easy solution before they even bring it up. Often, they won’t even know about this solution, which makes it your job to find it for them, “Ask them the questions to get to why they truly come.</p>
<p>Sometimes you have to dig a little”, explains Simon Tooley. They’ll appreciate the thorough service and feel like they’re in good hands. For example, a client inquires about one of your services they’d like to try for the first time but they seem unconvinced of its value.</p>
<p>Instead of just providing them with the straight-forward answer, read between the lines, tell them about an upcoming discount on the service they should wait for and take advantage of.</p>
<p><strong>4. Display positive reviews from other clients</strong></p>
<p>Your customers are walking, talking, “free” adverts for your business &#8211; keep this in mind at all times and only make promises you can keep. A good way to ensure that is to enforce a “under promise, over deliver” rule.</p>
<p>As you may already know, freebies and surprises tend to make customers really happy and getting them to recommend you is one of the best things you can do for your business. Naturally, people are much more inclined to try and trust a business who already has the seal of approval from someone they know and trust. To make referrals happen, <a href="https://www.lightspeedhq.com/blog/2016/06/10-ways-get-feedback-online-customers/">put systems and incentives in place</a>. This can be something as simple as offering a small discount for every new client they bring in. Not only can this boost business, it’s also a great way to see how customers view your business and where to make adjustments.</p>
<p><strong>5. Respond to crisis quickly</strong></p>
<p>In the event of a crisis &#8211; an unhappy customer claiming he or she was misinformed, for example &#8211; don’t sit on your hands and hope the problem goes away (it never does).</p>
<p><a href="https://www.lightspeedhq.com/blog/2016/12/how-to-respond-to-negative-reviews/">Be decisive and respond quickly</a> to show your customers you can be trusted. Remain objective and professional because a lot can be told about a business in the way they handle and remedy a tough situation. A customer’s journey has 3 parts: before, during and after, and it’s important not to neglect the last one as it holds all the power to make or break that customer’s overall experience and lasting perception.</p>
<p>Your product or service must be desirable with clear added value; however, without the customer&#8217;s trust, they&#8217;ll probably buy from someone else. Somebody they trust.</p>
<div class="creativ-shortcode creativ-shortcode-alertbox creativ-shortcode-alertbox-colour-border"><p class="creativ-shortcode creativ-shortcode-alertbox-content"><br />
Athena Kyriacou a.k.a. Tina, is a Content Specialist at Lightspeed POS, based in Montreal, Qc. She describes creating content as “being in her happy place”. After work hours you can find her spending time with her dog, editing videos for her youtube channel, advocating gender equality and then with her dog some more.</p></div>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.booxi.com/blog/gain-customer-trust/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Create an effective satisfaction survey in 7 simple steps</title>
		<link>https://www.booxi.com/blog/create-an-effective-satisfaction-survey-in-7-simple-steps/</link>
		<comments>https://www.booxi.com/blog/create-an-effective-satisfaction-survey-in-7-simple-steps/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2017 16:02:02 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Astrid Bertout]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Business Tips]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Customer Acquisition]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[customer retention]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.booxi.com/blog/?p=1299</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Keeping customers happy is crucial to ensuring customer retention. It also helps greatly with new customer acquisition. Find out our best practice guide to create a relevant satisfaction survey and get a very accurate feedback. ]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img class="float_top aligncenter wp-image-1357 size-full" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/aCpigFxVn3sqZEIeHsUWzWrd-U-qYaikKK5ZLwtM5o-w85KBznS6MQtPf9kLuTDEp2Yc0OX7eLDangMr3CTS=s0" alt="create your own survey" width="1200" height="600" />Did you know that <a href="http://www.trackur.com/96-of-unhappy-customers-wont-complain-to-you-but-will-tell-15-friends-infographic" target="_blank">96% of unhappy customers</a> won’t complain and 91% of them will simply never return?</p>
<p>Given this, it’s easy to understand that you need to:</p>
<p>1- Ensure that your customers are happy with the services you offer as well as the overall customer experience you provide.</p>
<p>2- Send a survey on a regular basis to measure their satisfaction and see if there’s anything you need to improve upon.</p>
<p>Customer satisfaction is the key to your success: not only does it ensure customer loyalty, but it also helps attract new customers thanks to positive word-of-mouth.</p>
<p>Getting customer feedback regarding all the steps of your customer journey is therefore essential.</p>
<p style="text-align: center">In this guide, you’ll learn how to create a satisfaction survey with ease.</p>
<p><img class="img_zoom aligncenter wp-image-1300 size-full" src="https://booxi-live-wp-storage.storage.googleapis.com/form-animation.gif" alt="create your form" width="360" height="363" />Source : <a href="https://gsuite.google.com/learning-center/products/forms/get-started/" target="_blank">Google Inc</a></p>
<p>1. Determine all the steps throughout your customer journey, from initial contact to rebooking.<br />
Here’s an example of a customer journey:</p>
<p><strong>→ Before the appointment</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Find all the necessary information about the business quickly and easily</li>
<li>Contact the business quickly and easily.</li>
<li>Book an appointment quickly and easily.</li>
<li>Receive an appointment reminder.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>→ During the appointment</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Receive a warm welcome.</li>
<li>Receive excellent service.</li>
<li>Be listened to and receive assistance</li>
<li>Have a positive experience during payment.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong> → After the appointment</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Be able to book the next appointment quickly and easily.</li>
<li>Have incentive to return. For example, through a loyalty program.</li>
<li>Enjoy a personalized customer experience.</li>
</ul>
<p>2. For each of the steps you identify, make sure to ask your customers relevant questions.</p>
<p>Here’s an example for the first step in the “Before the appointment” section:</p>
<p><em>- How did you hear about our business?</em><br />
<em> Through Facebook</em><br />
<em> Through a friend</em><br />
<em> Through Instagram</em><br />
<em> By doing online research</em><br />
<em> While passing by</em></p>
<p><strong>Tip: </strong>After the questions,make sure to leave some space so customers can give their opinions, feedback and recommendations. They might bring up a point you didn’t think about.</p>
<p>3. Creating the survey</p>
<p>Once you’ve determined all your questions, you can start to build the survey. There are</p>
<p>many platforms that’ll help you do it for free. For example, you can use Google Forms.</p>
<p>*Here’s <a href="https://gsuite.google.com/learning-center/products/forms/get-started/" target="_blank">all the information you’ll need</a> to create your Google Forms account. From there, you’ll quickly learn how to create your first survey.<br />
<br />
<strong>Tip #1</strong> &#8211; At the end of the survey, make sure to add a section to thank your customers for taking the time to answer your questions.<br />
<br />
<strong>Tip #2</strong> &#8211; Estimate the time needed to complete the form and make sure to mark it clearly. This way, your clients will see their progress as they answer the questions. In general, try to be as concise as possible, and avoid creating a form that takes more than 5 minutes to complete.</p>
<p>You can even add a progress bar to encourage them.</p>
<p><a href="https://gsuite.google.com/learning-center/products/forms/get-started/"><img class="shadow_medium aligncenter wp-image-1301 size-full" src="https://booxi-live-wp-storage.storage.googleapis.com/progress-bar.jpg" alt="progress bar" width="324" height="73" /></a></p>
<p>4. Send out your survey</p>
<p>Once your survey is ready, send it out to get as many answers as possible, in order to get as much useful information as possible.</p>
<p>Send it out on all your communication channels:</p>
<ul>
<li>Create a post on your Facebook page, and on every other social network that you use for business. Don’t forget to mention how long it’ll take to complete the survey.</li>
<li>If you have a client list, send the survey by email. They’ll be able to fill it out when they have some time.
<p><strong>Tip #1</strong> – Personalize the email subject header in order to increase the chances that your customers willopen it and complete the survey. It’s an effective strategy to increase your open rate.<em>Here’s an example:<br />
</em><em>[Fname], your opinion matters to me!</em></p>
<p><strong>Tip #2 </strong>– Don’t forget to explain why they’re receiving the email.For example, it can be: “Thanks for visiting us. In order to offer you the best experience possible, we would like to ask you some questions.”</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li>You can even send them the link by text message at the end of their appointment. Between 92 and 98% of all texts are read, making it the media with the highest open rate. In comparison, emails are only read 22% of the time.</li>
</ul>
<p>5. Analyze the answers</p>
<p>Once you start to receive answers, take time to analyze them. Determine your strengths as well as the steps during the customer journey that need to be improved.</p>
<p>Don’t forget to take into account all the additional suggestions and comments made by your customers.</p>
<p>It’s also important to identify how many times the same point is brought up by different customers. This will let you know what to focus on first.</p>
<p>6. Build for the future:</p>
<p>Based on the answers you receive and your analysis of them, prioritize future actions in order to improve your customer experience.</p>
<p><em>For example:</em></p>
<p>If the main issue raised by your customers is that it’s hard to find your business online, focus your efforts on promoting your business and building an online visibility strategy.</p>
<p>If their main frustration is that it takes a lot of time to book an appointment, why not offer online appointment booking to your customers?</p>
<p>And so on.</p>
<p>Then, for all the changes you need to make in order to improve customer satisfaction, establish deadlines and respect them.</p>
<p>7. Finally, send out your satisfaction survey regularly.</p>
<ul>
<li>This will help you monitor your improvements and see if they’ve had a positive impact on customer satisfaction.</li>
<li>Because customers’ expectations can quickly change, you need to make sure you meet them all the time.</li>
</ul>
<p>You now have all the information you need to create an effective satisfaction survey, and to implement changes that will help you offer a standout customer experience.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.booxi.com/blog/create-an-effective-satisfaction-survey-in-7-simple-steps/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Small Businesses &#8211; Use the Web at Your Advantage</title>
		<link>https://www.booxi.com/blog/small-businesses-use-the-web-at-your-advantage/</link>
		<comments>https://www.booxi.com/blog/small-businesses-use-the-web-at-your-advantage/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2017 17:00:17 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Astrid Bertout]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Business Tips]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Owners]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[online visibility]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[website]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.booxi.com/blog/?p=1275</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[With hundreds of new businesses created every day, it is important to stand out. You can't simply offer a quality product or service, you also need to make yourself visible on the web! Here are 3 ways to have a web presence. ]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img class="float_top aligncenter wp-image-1294 size-full" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/thwtcJeYvy4UY2z2SFC6rOTr6PxuKL63TDut3BewTUPhKXBLCQfT-6-ix8SbOrH8uRcMq-ArA8DmuMBaGWnHz3o=s0" alt="webself" width="1171" height="527" />With hundreds of new businesses created every day, it is important to stand out.</p>
<p>You can’t simply offer a quality product or service, you also need to make yourself visible on the web! It is very rare that a company, no matter the sector of activity, isn’t on the web somehow.</p>
<p>According to <a href="http://www.chainstoreage.com/article/study-81-research-online-making-big-purchases" target="_blank">Chainstorage.com</a>, it is said that 80% of consumers search online before shopping; it is therefore important that your customers find you!</p>
<p>Luckily for you, there are several ways to have a web presence; through a website, social networks, newsletters, mobile application, etc.  Today, we talk about three ways you can use the web to your advantage!</p>
<h2>1. Get to know your target market</h2>
<p>One of the first steps in getting a business up and running is to determine who will be your target market, who will benefit from your products or services. If you determine your target audience from the beginning, it will be easier to adapt your content, your visuals, to build your website as well as all of your communications (newsletter, text messaging, social networks).</p>
<p>Why is it important to adapt to your target audience?  Because not only do you want to build a good relationship with your customers by offering them a quality experience, but you also want to increase loyalty. By creating a web community with your potential and current customers you increase the chances of recurrence, good reviews, references, etc.</p>
<p>Competitive intelligence is also important before getting starting your own business. Look at similar businesses, those that offer the same services or are located near you. It will give you a good idea for your pricing, services offered and well as the target market. Keep in mind though, this isn’t to copy, but rather to use the information as a guide or for inspiration.</p>
<p>Try to be as creative as possible on the web. Live videos, Facebook contests, daily Instagram posts, ‘Client of the Month’ articles, all of those are great ideas to create an active web community!</p>
<p>Another advantage of the web? Personalized communication!</p>
<p>The personalization of your posts is very interesting and you should definitely explore all of its advantages! For example, on Facebook, you can sponsor posts that will only reach your target market. You can also collect the names of your customers and use it when sending a monthly newsletter. Customizing will make your customers feel that they are important to you; This is a great way to focus on customer loyalty.</p>
<p><img class="shadow_medium  aligncenter wp-image-1280 size-full" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/7blA2CEd0IT6Rn2ZPlQNGY-1KmvvJ8-I41kk0qDRs_MVjlrhajtiqQI02zLpezamj4vosAxqwLpu3Koimpebpg=s0" alt="feedback" width="901" height="480" /></p>
<h2>2. Listen</h2>
<p>Listening to your customers on the web? It is possible and you should definitely do it! In fact, you can gather valuable information that will help you adjust when it’s time to make some changes or modifications in your business.</p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Observe purchasing behaviors:</strong>
<p>Your customers use your services only once and never come back? Do you have a high recurrence rate? Keep records of your customers to evaluate their purchase behaviors, it will be easy to determine if you need to make changes, for example,  there might be something wrong  if the recurrence rate is very low.</li>
<p></p>
<li><strong>Collect comments:<br />
</strong></p>
<p>If you have the time, try to offer a personalized after-sales service.  Send a thank you email asking the customer for their comments on the product, service, or ask them to submit a review about their experience. Facebook offers a &#8216;review&#8217; section to allow customers to give their opinion based on stars (1 to 5)  as well as leave relevant comments. Do not forget to reply to these comments, whether they are positive or negative!</li>
<li><strong>Participate in forums:</strong>
<p>There are several forums or groups on Facebook where you can gather information. For example, about ten thousand professionals joined a Facebook group called &#8216;Dans la tête des entrepreneurs’. It is not unusual to see people ask for design advice about their website or get more information about marketing tactics. it is very interesting because the answers come from professionals who are there to help you! It’s also a great way to make contacts.</li>
<p></p>
<li><strong>Surveys:</strong>
<p>Surveys are also interesting because they allow you to collect answers of questions you may have. You can add a survey section in your newsletter and ask your customers some monthly questions. Want to offer a new service? Create a survey to see if it could possibly interest your customers. There are several tools to help you, for example, <a href="https://fr.surveymonkey.com/" target="_blank">SurveyMonkey</a>.</li>
<p>
</ul>
<h2>3. Adjust</h2>
<p>By collecting information about your customers and their buying habits, you will be able to adjust when the time comes to make changes. Chances are that you have to be flexible when you&#8217;re in business, and that&#8217;s a good thing, because adjusting to please your target market is a good way to retain your customer base and demonstrate how much you care about them.</p>
<p style="text-align: center"><span class="bx_text24">There’s nothing wrong with modifications!</span></p>
<p>Just be sure to notify your customers. Web platforms are a great way to keep your customers informed on news features or updates. Use them to your advantage by encouraging people to react to your publications, leave comments, share or ask questions. Do not forget that adjustments are not a sign of weakness, on the opposite, it shows your customers your flexibility!</p>
<p>You can also use the newsletters, to talk about upcoming news or changes! Newsletters are an excellent way to build loyalty. Have you ever thought about text message marketing? If it works with your target market, why not try it? It is said that 93% of people have a smartphone and 98% of all text messages are open!</p>
<p>You have every advantage to use the web if you are in business! Not only is it an inexpensive (or even free) solution, but the web could propel your business to another level! Customer loyalty, newsletter, animated social platforms; explore the different ways and see what works with your customers, while having fun!</p>
<p style="text-align: center"><span class="bx_text24">Your idea deserves a great site!<br />
Go to <a href="http://www.webself.net" target="_blank">WebSelf.net</a> to create your own free website today!</span></p>
<p>Webself is a free and easy tool to create website. Choose your design, add your texts and pictures and publish your website on the Internet. It has never been easier to create a website! No computer knowledge required, only your imagination ! Start building your own website today.</p>
<p><a href="http://www.webself.net"><img class="shadow_medium aligncenter wp-image-1295 size-full" src="https://booxi-live-wp-storage.storage.googleapis.com/webself-banner.jpg" alt="create your website " width="1440" height="600" /></a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.booxi.com/blog/small-businesses-use-the-web-at-your-advantage/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>12 creative ways to benefit from Instagram</title>
		<link>https://www.booxi.com/blog/12-creative-ways-to-benefit-from-instagram/</link>
		<comments>https://www.booxi.com/blog/12-creative-ways-to-benefit-from-instagram/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2017 15:51:50 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Astrid Bertout]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Business Tips]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Customer Acquisition]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[online visibility]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social network]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.booxi.com/blog/?p=1229</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Help your beauty salon get noticed with 12 great Instagram post ideas. ]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img class="float_top aligncenter wp-image-1230 size-full" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/8JmwZulno89yNK_B_Q5OdUh1moD4l4t79TyLBT0PV_ifXV0rwIqBne0DfYG-CT8NTXFnbIL_74qoPsQdbY7UMA=s0" alt="benefit from instagram" width="1200" height="600" /></p>
<p>According to <a href="https://business.instagram.com/blog/500000-advertisers/">Instagram Advertiser Statistics</a>, 50% of Instagrammers follow a business account. Even more interesting for you, 60% of Instagrammers say they’ve found information about a product or service through the application.<br />
And most importantly, 75% of Instagrammers either visit a website, do research, buy a product/use a service, or talk to a friend after being inspired by a post.</p>
<p>This is a great opportunity to enhance your online visibility, acquire new customers and increase your sales &#8211; especially if you work in an industry where visual presentation is important. Like beauty and wellness, for example.</p>
<p>To begin, don’t use your personal account. Make sure to<a href="https://www.booxi.com/blog/how-to-create-your-business-instagram-account-a-step-by-step-guide/" target="_blank"> create a separate business account </a>instead. This way, you’ll benefit from professional features that will help convert your online visitors into customers. Then, once they become customers,there are other features that will analyze their behaviour.</p>
<ul>
<li>As you know, Instagram is an image-sharing platform, so make sure you only post high-quality photos and videos. This may seem like obvious advice, but you’d be surprised how often sub-standard images are used. Remember, everything you share will affect your business image and reputation, so make sure you choose wisely.</li>
<li>Make sure to add all the relevant information to your profile. This way, your followers will be able to interact easily with your business, or contact you directly if they need to.<img class="shadow_small aligncenter wp-image-1233" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/VEMfBBU6WRe6BeMN-bAaWYKoP8qtQQeqH14OitlX4diQvx_lcEX3AFhpmd3xFGk81mOlBywRAVRqAdCrhtkZbQ=s0" alt="etiket instagram account" width="484" height="861" /><br />
As an example, Etiket’s bio includes a business description, a mention of the industry they work in, a link to their website and three separate calls to action: Call, Email, and Directions. (Just in case you’re not aware, a call to action is a button designed to provoke an immediate response. Ex: Call Now)</li>
<li>Use popular and relevant hashtags that are related to your industry. Why?</li>
</ul>
<p>Because hashtags extend your reach and make it easier for Instagrammers to find your content. In addition, posts with at least one <a href="http://get.simplymeasured.com/rs/simplymeasured2/images/InstagramStudy2014Q3.pdf?mkt_tok=3RkMMJWWfF9wsRolua%252FAZKXonjHpfsX57%252BwtX6a2lMI%252F0ER3fOvrPUfGjI4CTsViI%252BSLDwEYGJlv6SgFQrDEMal41bgNWRM%253D">hashtag generate 12.6% more engagement</a> on average.</p>
<p>How can you think of great hashtags for your posts?</p>
<p>To get inspired, do a hashtag search and see what the most popular hashtags on Instagram are.</p>
<p><img class="shadow_small aligncenter wp-image-1231" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/N4xtaQxQ0sB5SYoPNpTo5CwFUASM9-3F9_ZMszzWs7D2_UenH_5VHOimpwgsV2LtDR8EAPxzKvHMxRIHJPg3epw=s0" alt="hashtag research" width="439" height="781" /></p>
<p>You can also follow other businesses in your industry and see what kind of hashtags they’ve added to their posts. Obviously don’t copy them, but definitely draw inspiration from them.</p>
<p>Finally, you can also use a tool to find the most relevant hashtags for your pictures. Like<a href="https://focalmark.com/">Focalmark</a>, for example. In just a few clicks, you’ll be able to find the most relevant hashtags for the images you’re sharing. And the tool’s algorithm will provide the most popular hashtags for a specific audience.</p>
<p>How many hashtags should you use?</p>
<p>It’s important to add hashtags, but make sure not to go overboard with them.<br />
A study by <a href="https://trackmaven.com/blog/everything-marketers-need-know-instagram-sponsored-content/">TrackMaven</a> shows that posts with 4-5 hashtags generate the most interactions.</p>
<p><img class="shadow_small aligncenter wp-image-1234 size-full" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/prQ55hLSwRBR_LIF3HsS-MMBVL0X42nhkpoM_vkoBOoY9VtMglwvbua-0y347nHTtDc0DIJhk_5MKlg8bpP1=s0" alt="interactions by hashtags" width="805" height="448" /></p>
<p>You can also create a hashtag that uses your business name. So when your followers share pictures about you, they can add a specific hashtag and mention your business name (@businessexample) at the same time.Not only is it a good way to start creating an online community around your business, butit will also make it very easy to know when someone mentions your business on Instagram.</p>
<ul>
<li>Like any other social network, you have to interact with other Instagram users in order to create a community. So make sure to comment on their posts and like their accounts. But that doesn’t mean you should like every account you come across. Instead, find the ones that reflect the values and image you want your business to have and like those.Similarly, you can follow people who’ve subscribed to your account. And if someone mentions your business on their account, take the time to reply. It will show your audience that you’re interested in them and that you’d like to interact with them.</li>
<li>Use Instagram stories to give your followers a peek at your day-to-day business.</li>
</ul>
<p>*What’s a story?<br />
A story is a live video shared on Instagram. It’s temporary, disappearing after 24 hours.</p>
<p>Stories are a good way to create relationships based on direct interaction. A study conducted by Social Bakers shows that <a href="https://www.socialbakers.com/blog/2621-instagram-stories-five-things-marketers-need-to-know">stories have a positive impact on your overall Instagram performance</a>. After watching a story, a follower is more likely to visit your account and interact with it (by liking or commenting on your photos, for example).</p>
<ul>
<li>Use your Instagram account to share useful content with your followers.</li>
</ul>
<p>Are you a hair salon owner? Make a short video tutorial that features an easy do-it-yourself hairstyle.</p>
<p>Are you a beauty salon owner? Post a short video tutorial about makeup that your followers can easily reproduce on their own.</p>
<p>Are you a wellness center owner? Give advice about nutrition, health and well-being, and provide tips your followers can use in their daily lives.</p>
<ul>
<li>Share quotes that inspire and motivate. Learn how to <a href="https://www.booxi.com/blog/how-to-create-shareable-images-that-drive-traffic/">create shareable images that drive traffic </a>by following this guide.  (what guide are you referring to exactly?)<br />
You can also share inspirational lifestyle photos.</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li>You can also post photos that are related to calendar events.For example, during winter,<a href="https://www.instagram.com/sephora/?hl=en">Sephora</a> shared a picture of two products that were placed in snow.<br />
Similarly, <a href="https://www.instagram.com/marcellecosmetics/?hl=en">Marcellecosmetics</a>posted a photo featuring lipsticks and hearts during Valentine’s day.<img class="shadow_small aligncenter wp-image-1235" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-XKS6XONFLlwm5HAYU_4K-SqLDY1QytfJv4rG3haUzUUHF7fffTanlSGmvsiI3EZ43w3fXC4KEU_uaTl9AyQ=s0" alt="promotion ideas based on calendar" width="745" height="683" /></li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li>Post photos of all the members of your team. On Instagram, pictures with people get <a href="http://expandedramblings.com/index.php/important-instagram-stats/13/">38% more likes</a> than those without, and get 32% more comments. It’s a great way to humanize your business.</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li>Also share customer-generated content about your business and products,  and make sure to tag them. Why? Because the content has already been created, and so it’s saved you time. More importantly,<a href="https://zuberance.com/zuberrants/category/top-10-stats-about-online-reviews">88% of people trust online reviews from strangers</a> as much as personal recommendations. Plus, it’s a good way to show your followers that you’re interested in them, which in turn helps you build a closer relationship.</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li>Share some pictures of your products and make them stand out by displaying them in a creative way.<img class="shadow_small aligncenter wp-image-1236" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/Xh2Ki_2W5jv36ZohjR7KRoBc9bFViBR1UXn8RQwIZ-tCzapqobKM-3gsNul6QpzGa_gG7TejyE4Bs2GKaNgkDog=s0" alt="display your products" width="440" height="783" />On the other hand, don’t only post product shots on your account. That’ll bore your followers in a hurry.</li>
<li>Finally, share some stunning Before &amp; After photos. It’s a great way to get people interested in your services.<img class="shadow_small aligncenter wp-image-1237" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/TnCxbc7em6XEPuAZtzbMw4FlzX3x1QCSz7IRibqHv8lfSCemgvOQWgPB0XuAy8S9uDcKWO4rJetOLW0v5mlGJg=s0" alt="before/after picture" width="670" height="430" /></li>
</ul>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.booxi.com/blog/12-creative-ways-to-benefit-from-instagram/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Get more customers by adding online appointment booking to Google My Business</title>
		<link>https://www.booxi.com/blog/get-more-customers-by-adding-booxi-on-google-my-business/</link>
		<comments>https://www.booxi.com/blog/get-more-customers-by-adding-booxi-on-google-my-business/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2017 21:10:44 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Astrid Bertout]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Business Tips]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[customer]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[online visibility]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.booxi.com/blog/?p=1226</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[You can now easily convert online visitors into customers by adding booxi directly to your Google My Business account.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img class="float_top aligncenter wp-image-1217 size-full" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/QSkaIa1KvQ4501-WCLZCBddUzVAomUnvHqhPSI3AZtSkbleD_hy1t72d_dK9W_dxemyghzQ2rufKk0dPh4yD10k=s0" alt="thumbnail" width="1200" height="600" /></p>
<p>Did you know that today 35% of customers would like to schedule appointments during non-business hours and that 25% of millennials (people under 35) will only book appointment online?</p>
<p>Then it&#8217;s obvious that online appointment booking is a competitive advantage and adding it on Internet is a strategic way to attract new customers.</p>
<p>The good news? You can now add online appointment booking directly on your Google My Business profile: a powerful tool to convert online visitors into customers.</p>
<p><strong>How to do it?</strong><br />
The first step is to create your account on Google My Business.<br />
If it’s not already done, here is a <a href="https://www.booxi.com/blog/get-more-visibility-by-registering-with-google-my-business-2/" target="_blank">step by step tutorial</a> to show you how to do it.</p>
<p>It’s easy to do it and free!</p>
<p>Then,</p>
<p><img class="img_zoom size-full wp-image-1219 alignleft" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/VqGEY7CvfXAI3GMrO-Uj4eNE5jJCsZvOrCUoG3y0no5Hgk7tubtd3Ofy2kDI_x-cLfiYTVoNz-RVOda69A7zu1o=s0" alt="unnamed (2)" /><br />
Go to the <a href="https://www.google.com/appserve/mkt/p/aZ4_3ZYNqumnqKN7XzF7PNPc3HF9qzgu-qXrbSYeMzcaGvDeyzN942-z2VHp_51GKjC-S-q93R9pzUON5oqxZ8b64nRcargMbUjtbuk93y9txqtfPkVZuQbS-phwnkEjqaYvDUiE6aARbTeasqwuxwRO48muh8lkSW9s_wbPPhFGIlml7a2G4ROr0ufKSNev63Nfjmvn8Nb_v_Cyxr9uUKIjcnKYdx_IsvJ2t2XtH_uMBJei8Htsr_E=" target="_blank">&#8220;Posts&#8221; tab<br />
</a><a href="https://www.google.com/appserve/mkt/p/aZ4_3ZYNqumnqKN7XzF7PNPc3HF9qzgu-qXrbSYeMzcaGvDeyzN942-z2VHp_51GKjC-S-q93R9pzUON5oqxZ8b64nRcargMbUjtbuk93y9txqtfPkVZuQbS-phwnkEjqaYvDUiE6aARbTeasqwuxwRO48muh8lkSW9s_wbPPhFGIlml7a2G4ROr0ufKSNev63Nfjmvn8Nb_v_Cyxr9uUKIjcnKYdx_IsvJ2t2XtH_uMBJei8Htsr_E=" target="_blank"> <img class="shadow_small aligncenter wp-image-1224 size-full" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/CC59Fn-9uID2cic99kg8LPA-nwEwcATABfQ1aHAPQB8-MogofHpN4cppoF3arvW_I8DLLoNCMlTfH3NB_YzV9Q=s0" alt="posts tab google my business" width="387" height="252" /></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><img class="img_zoom size-full wp-image-1221 alignleft" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/Q8d32nMfhAOc5XJSp6MNvHOz8oB0Ws5E0DDVZldPel9mcnrGIo9mE_jpwX8WjxyO4sGo0C1PP3qWcuN2rTpxDgg=s0" alt="unnamed (3)" /><br />
And click on the section “Write your post”.<br />
Create your message by adding a picture, a short text and the “Reserve” button. On the line <span style="color: #3366ff">example.com</span> add your booxi website link.</p>
<p>To find this link, sign in your booxi account and click on My Business tab, then on Business Details. Copy the link under the section “booxi site”.</p>
<p><img class="shadow_small aligncenter wp-image-1225 size-full" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/3xTJHL2gg-2Gcx-3yQmfy4wHI3hnTg-AE_sbI3yiJSz10CddxrUNsYSzg9upd1UORfOWqfIOt_mcSaowwK6t=s0" alt="book-now-button" width="453" height="930" /></p>
<p><img class="img_zoom size-full wp-image-1223 alignleft" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/xjGS0NwcMTD4Ig7pKGva4FufvodP0E1Ie8K0bYgXRfDlAlUQcmHgZ8qK9b5nA04yhh9Up2TofD75AAfK-39h=s0" alt="unnamed (4)" /><br />
Once it’s done click on Preview and then on Publish. And it’s live on Google, so it’s easy to convert your online visitors into customers!</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p style="text-align: center">You want to add online appointment booking directly on your Google My Business account but you don&#8217;t use booxi yet?<br />
Create your free trial right now!<br />
<a href="https://www.booxi.com/business/signup" class="creativ-shortcode creativ-shortcode-button creativ-shortcode-button-colour-allgreen creativ-shortcode-button-size-medium creativ-shortcode-button-edge-rounded" target="_blank">Get Started</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.booxi.com/blog/get-more-customers-by-adding-booxi-on-google-my-business/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to turn new customers into repeat customers?</title>
		<link>https://www.booxi.com/blog/turn-new-customers-into-repeat-customers/</link>
		<comments>https://www.booxi.com/blog/turn-new-customers-into-repeat-customers/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2017 19:24:48 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Astrid Bertout]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Business Tips]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[customer retention]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[loyalty program]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.booxi.com/blog/?p=1126</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Making sure that new customers become regular customers is an effective strategy that will have a positive impact on your bottom line. Here are 4 strategies to convert your visitors into loyal customers.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/larrymyler/2016/06/08/acquiring-new-customers-is-important-but-retaining-them-accelerates-profitable-growth/#1df6387a6671%20" target="_blank"><img class="float_top aligncenter wp-image-1131 size-full" src="https://booxi-live-wp-storage.storage.googleapis.com/product-recommendation.png" alt="customer experience" width="1200" height="600" /><br />
60-80% of customers</a> who describe themselves as satisfied do not go back to do more business with the company that initially satisfied them1.</p>
<p>Why does this happen? Simple. Too often, no solid relationship is established between the business and the customer. And with all the options available on the market, if no real connection is made, customers will try other businesses.</p>
<p>However, here are four strategies you can quickly implement to establish a lasting relationship with your customers, thus ensuring that they become regulars &#8211; which in turn will have a positive impact on your bottom line.</p>
<ul>
<li>
<h3>Provide a great experience and make sure your customers are satisfied</h3>
</li>
</ul>
<p>This may seem obvious, but it’s the first step to converting a new customer into a regular customer.</p>
<p>If customers are disappointed with their first visit, they’ll never come back to see you. So make sure to pamper them from the get-go. Spend a few minutes at the beginning of the appointment to ask them some questions and understand exactly what their needs are.</p>
<p><span style="text-decoration: underline">Work with the right tools</span></p>
<p>During their first visit, a client will appreciate it if you ask them a few questions. It shows that you’re interested in them and that you’re taking the time to get to know them. And from a business standpoint, it’s important to know what their expectations are, which of your services they may be interested in, and how they heard about your business in the first place.</p>
<p>All of these questions are important to ask during the first appointment as they help establish initial contact and form the basis of a relationship.</p>
<p>But if you ask the same questions during their second visit, you’ll risk frustrating them. Everything will have a familiar ring to it, and they’ll interpret your questions as a way of making conversation as opposed to genuine interest on your part.</p>
<p>If you don’t want to take any risks, use CRM (a tool that helps you manage customer relationships) and make sure to jot down the information you received.</p>
<p>During their next visit, a quick glance at your notes will help you remember your previous conversation with them &#8211; even the smallest details.</p>
<p>The customer will be flattered and impressed by the great customer experience you offer. By making them feel that they’re not just a number, you’ll establish a trusting relationship.</p>
<ul>
<li>
<h3>Add online appointment booking</h3>
</li>
</ul>
<p>Did you know that 35% of clients try to book their appointments outside of opening hours and that 25% of people under the age of 35 only book appointments online?</p>
<p><a href="https://www.booxi.com/blog/testimonial-esthetique-isa-belle/" target="_blank">People are trying to simplify their lives</a>. If you help them save time, they’ll appreciate it and come back to see you.</p>
<p>By adding a “Book Now” button directly <a href="https://www.booxi.com/blog/add-online-booking-to-facebook/" target="_blank">on your Facebook page</a> or your website, you’ll make it easier for visitors and give them a good reason to keep doing business with you.</p>
<p>So make sure you offer online appointment booking. Not only will it keep you competitive, but it&#8217;s also a very effective way to start collecting customer email addresses.</p>
<p><img class="img_zoom aligncenter size-full wp-image-779" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/oNOI6q05eem6KgtCexIW-j9pOA5a35DbYRegSeVo0aoZvlz1GB0462BPKHlIzWdxuqLTUA9FZaPKt-221BrLLA=s0" alt="get customers to book online" /></p>
<ul>
<li>
<h3>Build a list of clients and communicate with them regularly</h3>
</li>
</ul>
<p>Be sure to build a client database that includes their email addresses. Then make sure to send them promotions or information about your business on a regular basis. If you stay top of mind with your customers, they’re more likely to book their next appointment with you rather than with the competition.</p>
<p>Here are a few kinds of messages you can send to customers to start building a lasting relationship with them:</p>
<p>After their visit, send them a message to thank them for booking an appointment with you. You can also take the opportunity to ask them how their experience went.</p>
<p>One month later you can send them a message to remind them to book an appointment. This message will have even more impact if you tell them about a promotion at the same time.</p>
<p>In addition, thanks to your customer database you’ll be able to <a href="https://www.facebook.com/business/help/170456843145568" target="_blank">target them directly with Facebook ads</a>. For example one month or two later, use Local Awareness Ads from Facebook to target them with promotion : they should book an appointment shortly.</p>
<ul>
<li>
<h3>Set up a loyalty program and give people incentive to become regular customers</h3>
</li>
</ul>
<p><a href="http://info.bondbrandloyalty.com/2016-loyalty-report" target="_blank">81% of consumers</a> are more likely to continue doing business with brands that offer loyalty programs.</p>
<p>There are many options available to you. One of the most effective methods is to set up a point accumulation system that allows customers to receive special promotions or obtain rewards.</p>
<p>For example:<br />
Every dollar spent is worth one point.<br />
Every new appointment you book directly at the end of the current appointment is worth 150 points.<br />
When a customer refers a friend, they’ll get 2000 points.</p>
<p>Once a customer reaches 5000 points, offer them a discount on a product or service.</p>
<p>You can also offer a free service after the 10th appointment.</p>
<p><span style="text-decoration: underline">Here’s a helpful hint:</span><br />
Make sure you only reward your regular customers by adding a few conditions.<br />
For example, you can decide that after one year of inactivity, any points that have been accumulated will be lost.</p>
<p>To make sure that as many customers as possible want to be a part of your program, offer them even greater benefits.</p>
<p>This could include birthday discounts, invitations to private sales, or invitations to events that feature an expert in your field or an influential blogger.</p>
<p>If you want to make sure that you’re offering benefits that your customers actually want, ask them what their expectations are, and what it is that brings them back to your business on a regular basis.</p>
<p><img class="img_zoom aligncenter size-full wp-image-1127" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/yoCIdjstmxCOb_BvQwsN34dzScP3BQ88RcYUVMQv6hiVuOAFzRleppXV9aZ36tHThDAQi0ba7qrgxQpT0NW_iw0=s0" alt="loyalty program" /></p>
<p>To conclude, if you want to turn new customers into regulars, you need to make them feel important, and you need to a build a trusting relationship with them over the long term.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.booxi.com/blog/turn-new-customers-into-repeat-customers/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to get new customers with Local Awareness Ads: A guide for Small Businesses</title>
		<link>https://www.booxi.com/blog/get-new-customers-with-local-awareness-ads/</link>
		<comments>https://www.booxi.com/blog/get-new-customers-with-local-awareness-ads/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2017 18:12:30 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Astrid Bertout]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Business Tips]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Customer Acquisition]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Facebook ads]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Local Business]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.booxi.com/blog/?p=1080</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Learn how to use Facebook Ads to promote your business locally and attract new customers. ]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img class="float_top aligncenter wp-image-1079 size-full" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/wsptTct0Hi9pf30znqaA3t8e3o_5P5U6T3wv40G0yOoGbCMmDq-YRXndBBIhFh2cOV5OP3Mcj3lUVasUxRGF=s0" alt="local awareness ads" width="1200" height="600" />A study performed by Google showed that 4 out of 5 consumers want <a href="https://think.storage.googleapis.com/docs/how-advertisers-can-extend-their-relevance-with-search_research-studies.pdf%20">personalized ads</a> based on their city, postal code or immediate environment. This represents a great business opportunity for small business owners.</p>
<p>You can take advantage of these findings by using local awareness ads from Facebook to target potential customers that live close to your business. Facebook ads are simple to use and allow you to manage your budget with ease (for example, you can set a limit of $5/day). In order to increase the chances of driving targeted people to your salon, give them a good reason to click on your ads and interact with your business. One thing you can do is offer them a promotion on one of your services or products.</p>
<p>Let&#8217;s show you how to create and set up your first local awareness ads.<br />
Before you create a promotion to attract new customers, you need to make sure you exclude your current customers from the targeted audience.</p>
<p>This video explains how to <a href="https://www.facebook.com/business/help/170456843145568?__mref=message_bubble">create a customized audience</a>. We’ll then show how you to make sure your current customers don’t receive your Facebook ads.</p>
<p>Once it’s finished, let’s start creating your ad:</p>
<ol>
<li>Access the <a href="https://www.facebook.com/login.php?next=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.facebook.com%2Fads%2Fmanage%2Fpowereditor%2F%3Furl%3Dhttps%253A%252F%252Fwww.facebook.com%252Fads%252Fmanage%252Fpowereditor%252F%26campaign_id%3D163681540489385%26placement%3D%252Fbusiness%252Fhelp%252F162528860609436%26creative%3Dcta_button" target="_blank">Power Editor</a>.</li>
<li>Next, choose your marketing objective by selecting the “Reach” option. Then give your campaign a name.
<p><img class="shadow_small aligncenter wp-image-1096 size-full" src="https://booxi-live-wp-storage.storage.googleapis.com/marketing-goal.png" alt="marketing-goal" width="932" height="935" /><br />
If it’s not already done, set up your account and click “Continue”.</p>
<p><img class="shadow_small aligncenter wp-image-1097 size-full" src="https://booxi-live-wp-storage.storage.googleapis.com/account-settings1.jpg" alt="account settings" width="958" height="559" /></li>
<li>In this section, you’ll be able to exclude your current customers from targeting.<br />
Just click on the “Exclude” link and select the audience you decided on at the beginning of this guide.</p>
<p><img class="shadow_small aligncenter wp-image-1098 size-full" src="https://booxi-live-wp-storage.storage.googleapis.com/exclude-current-client-listr.png" alt="exclude-current-client-list" width="944" height="710" /><br />
Then, to promote your business at the local level, check the box that says &#8220;Use the location of your Facebook page to reach people near your business&#8221;.<br />
You can also determine your advertising radius, and even include or exclude specific neighborhoods.</p>
<p><img class="shadow_small aligncenter wp-image-1099 size-full" src="https://booxi-live-wp-storage.storage.googleapis.com/geographic-radius.png" alt="local awareness " width="937" height="624" /><br />
At this stage you can also determine if you want to target the people who live in the area, the people who were recently in the area, the people traveling through the area or everyone in this area.</p>
<p><img class="shadow_small aligncenter wp-image-1100 size-full" src="https://booxi-live-wp-storage.storage.googleapis.com/targeted-people.png" alt="targeted-people" width="737" height="628" /><br />
You can then refine the audience you want to reach by adding specific criteria. For example, you can target by:<br />
- Age<br />
- Gender<br />
- Language<br />
- You can even target people based on interests, behaviours or the type of connection with your business (for example you can decide to include or exclude your fans).You can save the target audience you just created for future use.</p>
<p><img class="shadow_small aligncenter wp-image-1101 size-full" src="https://booxi-live-wp-storage.storage.googleapis.com/more-detailled-target.png" alt="more-detailled-target" width="656" height="434" /></li>
<li>You can request automatic placements by Facebook or make your own settings. All you need to do is determine where you want to show your ads.<br />
<img class="shadow_small aligncenter wp-image-1102 size-full" src="https://booxi-live-wp-storage.storage.googleapis.com/placement.png" alt="placement" width="661" height="652" /></li>
<li>Finally, determine the budget for your ad and when it’ll run.
<p><img class="shadow_small aligncenter wp-image-1103 size-full" src="https://booxi-live-wp-storage.storage.googleapis.com/budget-and-schedules.png" alt="budget-and-schedules" width="942" height="782" /><br />
Once you’ve set all the criteria, click “Continue”.</li>
<li>You can now create the visual for your ad.Be sure to make your offer precise. It must be easy to understand and easy to apply.<br />
For example, you could offer a 25% discount on a service or advertise a giveaway.</p>
<p>Once you’ve determined your offer, create an image for your ad.</p>
<p>It could be really simple. An image that illustrates your service(s) is often enough.</p>
<p><img class="shadow_small aligncenter wp-image-1104 size-full" src="https://booxi-live-wp-storage.storage.googleapis.com/image-format.png" alt="image-format" width="939" height="796" /><br />
Depending on your ad, choose the appropriate format (carousel, single image, single video or slideshow).<br />
Here’s an example:</p>
<p><img class="img_zoom aligncenter size-full wp-image-1105" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/yNVMPa--9bw3DDHFG6JjgJjjwvGjYnvgAw0puOYsLQiNy-NxN1hH64-Yfji8DPOwTEtAFXFuajCoThMlsJEjjA=s0" alt="ads example" />It’s really important that you add a call to action, which is simply a button that encourages people to interact with your ad.<br />
For example, if you offer online appointment booking, make sure to direct the targeted audience to the link that lets them book online.<br />
In addition, by using an appointment tool you’ll be able to review appointment history &#8211; and then you’ll be able to verify if a person is actually a new customer.</p>
<p><strong>To go even further:</strong></p>
<p>Some appointment tools let you ask your customers how they heard about your business while they’re booking online.<br />
It’s a good way to track how many new customers you’ve attracted thanks to your ad. In turn, you’ll be able to measure your return on investment.</p>
<p><img class="shadow_small aligncenter wp-image-1106 size-full" src="https://booxi-live-wp-storage.storage.googleapis.com/call-to-action.png" alt="call-to-action" width="400" height="529" /></li>
<li>Once everything’s done, click on the &#8220;Place Order&#8221; button.
<p><img class="shadow_small aligncenter wp-image-1107 size-full" src="https://booxi-live-wp-storage.storage.googleapis.com/place-order.png" alt="place-order" width="246" height="39" /></li>
<li>Then add your credit card information:
<p><img class="shadow_small aligncenter wp-image-1108 size-full" src="https://booxi-live-wp-storage.storage.googleapis.com/credit-card-ingo.png" alt="credit-card-info" width="439" height="526" /></li>
<li>Click on “Continue” and you’re done.</li>
</ol>
<p>There &#8211; you’ve just created your first local awareness ad to attract new clients.</p>
<p>You can let it run for a week for two (or however long your test period is) and then analyze your return on investment at the end of it. Depending on how many new customers you attracted, you can adjust your Facebook ad as needed and keep testing.</p>
<p><img class="shadow_small aligncenter wp-image-1109 size-full" src="https://booxi-live-wp-storage.storage.googleapis.com/complete-ads-example.jpg" alt="complete ads example" width="521" height="529" /></p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.booxi.com/blog/get-new-customers-with-local-awareness-ads/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Create Shareable Images That Drive Traffic?</title>
		<link>https://www.booxi.com/blog/how-to-create-shareable-images-that-drive-traffic/</link>
		<comments>https://www.booxi.com/blog/how-to-create-shareable-images-that-drive-traffic/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2017 14:57:27 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Astrid Bertout]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Business Tips]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[online visibility]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social network]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.booxi.com/blog/?p=1049</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Posts that contain photos are 2.3x more engaging than those without photos. In addition inspirational quotes can lead to post interaction, especially shares. Here are a few quick tips to help you create shareable visuals by combining photos and quotes. ]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p style="text-align: left"><a href="http://buzzsumo.com/blog/how-to-massively-boost-your-blog-traffic-with-these-5-awesome-image-stats/"><img class="float_top aligncenter wp-image-1073 size-full" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/lOoGupjaXYu4-yaklSfR1MNdB0zNlmwcdE7Mx7uZSv6Tx6bTmaVDhOffGpYBWrSTOki8Km0SzbVvzc4YVQIDjg=s0" alt="create your own pictures" width="1200" height="600" />Mike Gingerich</a>, writer at Social Media Examiner, says that “people love inspirational quotes that motivate them or elicit a particular emotion, which in turn can lead to post interaction, especially shares”.</p>
<p>This seems to be a winning strategy since it can make more people aware of your business and potentially lead to new customers.</p>
<p>In addition, Facebook posts that contain photos are 2.3x more engaging than those without photos.</p>
<p><img class="wp-image-1050 size-full aligncenter" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/dITfPx5UnGwgv_KA6rECtYN311_Yw_XCtIxEpV_hndjopK1xkqMTQ8EDz5uh-BcqmHKu8dXy4FAndXDZgZ4A=s0" alt="impact of images" width="800" height="556" /></p>
<p>Clearly, then, it’s essential that you add visuals to your posts in order to increase audience interaction as well as your online visibility.</p>
<p>Here are a few quick tips to help you create shareable visuals by combining photos and quotes.</p>
<h3>1. A Picture is Worth a Thousand Words</h3>
<p>The first step is finding photos that fit your business.</p>
<p>You can either use <a href="https://burst.shopify.com/">royalty-free photos from Shopify</a> or choose <a href="https://www.booxi.com/blog/6-outils-pour-avoir-des-photos-splendides-pour-votre-site-web/">one of the following solutions</a>.</p>
<p>Here’s an example that clearly illustrates the creative process.</p>
<p>Imagine that I’m the owner of a hair salon and I want to put a quote on my Facebook page.</p>
<p>The first thing I should do is write a list of keywords that relate to the services I offer.</p>
<p>For example:</p>
<ul>
<li>Hair</li>
<li>Hairdresser</li>
<li>Haircut</li>
</ul>
<p>Then I’ll do a photo search using those words.<br />
Once I find the picture I want, I’ll download it.</p>
<p>Here’s the one I decided to use:</p>
<p><span class="bx_text16"><img class="img_zoom aligncenter size-full wp-image-1051" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/51krfd-CQKddvJqRhBlb5gXp2s_EjtkE36VdXk8-teWg6rxh12iOn7TnXApwesURdh-0zBHKfbfWN-U702Hw6g=s0" alt="image for social network " /></span></p>
<p><span class="bx_text16">*Of course, if you have the time and resources to do it yourself (maybe you own a high quality camera, for example), by all means create your own visuals.</span></p>
<h3>2. Select the Quote</h3>
<p>Next thing you need to do is customize the picture in order to make it shareable. Like we talked about with keywords, you should select a quote that relates to what you do. The good news? It’s usually very easy to find an inspirational quote that’s connected to your field of work.</p>
<p><strong>Here’s a trick:</strong> Use the list of keywords you set up in step # 1 and do a Google search. For example, your search could be &#8220;Quotes + Hair&#8221;. You’ll quickly find a whole bunch of quotes. Now all you have to do is choose the one that suits your needs best.</p>
<p>Going back to my hair salon example, I’ll chose the following quote: &#8220;A woman who cut her hair is about to change her life&#8221; &#8211; Coco Chanel</p>
<h3>3. Customize the Image</h3>
<p>Now that you’ve found the picture and quote you need, all you have to do is to combine them.</p>
<p>To do so, just:</p>
<ul>
<li><a href="https://www.booxi.com/blog/create-your-canva-account-to-produce-your-own-visuals/">Create your Canva account</a>,</li>
<li>Select the type of visual you want to produce.<br />
In my case, I want a picture for my Facebook page, which is why I selected the “Facebook Post” option.<img class="img_zoom aligncenter size-full wp-image-1052" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/CRbKErVXRigar6K5gJH2QYC_IaVAbF4d78TmTo2S92tdVl9ECKAZ4WJa31qi3V48GGh9tn-iD7kVw4NMrIYB=s0" alt="social media type " /></li>
<li>Canva offers a variety of ready-to-use templates. Select the one you prefer.<img class="aligncenter" style="padding-top: 15px:" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/KrLkwIesQUG8rsby-UZWZfkXkOiUacC2Rczr8nxkJEPuR28jV2fjqdEVJC3ZFDQ2uDSji-yPwI1SXjZOfKn-=s0" alt="select-layout" width="508" height="592" /></li>
<li>Upload the picture you find online by clicking on the “Uploads” button, and then click on the “Upload your own images” button.<br />
<img class="img_zoom aligncenter size-full wp-image-1054" style="padding: 5px:" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/7OAVHrx6_FHoIR_17wsb3Qb5HYnOJYGDcavpe_vNqToQ16uNNs3bWFAM5rMBXSctfUbPRhishEOaaZZ2PJChZ40=s0" alt="upload-picture" /></li>
<li>Add the quote you selected earlier by clicking on the “Text” button. Then add the name of your business, but in a discrete fashion.</li>
<li>Save everything by clicking the “Download” button at the top right of the page.</li>
</ul>
<p>The following dropdown menu will appear:</p>
<p><img class="img_zoom aligncenter size-full wp-image-1056" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/DglwwJx2rXbBxd1iUcEV9tPpj4SilTbkmZbXfV-1vR6_ez7whPlIDAS8W20EhkdzwMCRTt8-VPqrbjh7bkyTfQ=s0" alt="format to download " /></p>
<p>Select the format you want when downloading. The .png and .jpeg formats are recommended.</p>
<p>Here’s the result:</p>
<p><img class="img_zoom aligncenter size-full wp-image-1057" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/iOnvhrNLFbMV3-nTNwrTB18EMnf5KjPLBmpaluTusJN_2bLfGZLq-83hIXRlP6ZBFi_SPc5mSWtytnWwJJYF3-w=s0" alt="visual creation" /></p>
<p>You can now post this picture on all your social networks. Analyze the results and repeat these steps any time you want.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.booxi.com/blog/how-to-create-shareable-images-that-drive-traffic/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>5 Reasons Why Your Business Should Offer Online Appointment Scheduling</title>
		<link>https://www.booxi.com/blog/why-your-business-should-offer-online-appointment-scheduling/</link>
		<comments>https://www.booxi.com/blog/why-your-business-should-offer-online-appointment-scheduling/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2017 16:34:57 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Astrid Bertout]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Business Tips]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[online booking]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.booxi.com/blog/?p=950</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[A major, but tedious part of running a service-oriented business is scheduling; however, the technology available today gives business owners an opportunity to simplify and automate it. Here are the 5 top reasons why you should be using online scheduling tool.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img class="float_top aligncenter wp-image-963 size-full" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/WeXicrU_7BsfWi5etyzY0cPzm6V4o3foZMvNlids0HHpjCa2VrUKj2vDJ3Y66hRKSWLyU-1cBdLXUwbK5HMhRIw=s0" alt="online appointment booking system" width="1200" height="600" />A major, but tedious, part of running a service-oriented business is scheduling. Manual systems typically mean going through a lot of back and forth with customers that usually leads to errors. These mistakes can negatively impact your relationship with clients and your business reputation.</p>
<p>Technology available today however, gives business owners an opportunity to automate scheduling. Online scheduling tools offer a more professional way to handle bookings and appointments, they also provides efficient, systematic, and ultimately, practical solutions that allow you to manage clients communications.</p>
<p>To give you a better understanding of what it can really do for your business, we’ve hashed out the top 5 reasons why you should be using online scheduling tool —</p>
<h2>1. You want to make the most of your time</h2>
<p>Online scheduling tools are designed to reduce, if not completely eliminate, the back and forth between you and your client. Trying to determine available dates for a meeting, making sure that it doesn’t conflict with any of your busy schedules, ensuring that there are no overlaps—this whole process can be very frustrating. There are more productive ways that you can spend your time on than trying to pin down a date and time that works for you and a client.</p>
<h2>2. Customers demand efficiency and innovation</h2>
<p>As a business, you recognize that your time is important; on the flipside, customers and clients want to know that companies they deal with aren’t wasting their time either. In the same way that you don’t want to go back and forth setting, cancelling and rescheduling appointments, it’s just as much of a hassle for customers. That said, customers demand efficiency and convenience from businesses they patronize—and online booking tools are one way to provide them with it.</p>
<h2>3. Minimizes no shows</h2>
<p>For any service business, no shows are a big concern. Unused appointments are essentially costing your business time and money, especially if it is dependent on limited slots that could have been used by other, interested customers. Whether you’re running a clinic, a fitness studio, or a salon, implementing a scheduling tool means you’re not only automating the booking process, but you’re also putting in place efficient tools that minimizes no-shows. These tools come with automated email and text reminders that, at the very least, can give customers enough time to inform you of a cancellation.</p>
<h2>4. Provides mobility</h2>
<p>One of the most convenient elements of automated online scheduling is that it’s easily accessible whether you’re on your phone, or your tablet, or computer. Knowing you can access important elements of your business anytime, anywhere means everything is run with a sense of transparency and efficiency that gives business-owners full control of their schedules. This also means that customers have access to the scheduling platform and can book appointments on the go, ensuring that the entire process is equally convenient for them</p>
<h2>5. Captures important customer data</h2>
<p>You can use online scheduling tools to serve as a database and archive of your customer information. You can use this information to continuously evolve your business to better serve their needs; and because it records and tracks data efficiently, it means you have a reliable archive of references you can use to build relationships with your customers.</p>
<p>Our online appointment booking software could prove to be one of the most important things you can do for your business.</p>
<hr class="dash" />
<p style="font-size: 30px;font-weight: 200;color: #888;text-align: center">Try it for free</p>
<p style="font-size: 16px;text-align: center;color: #555">14 days &#8211; No credit card required</p>
<p style="text-align: center"><a href="https://www.booxi.com/business/signup" class="creativ-shortcode creativ-shortcode-button creativ-shortcode-button-colour-allgreen creativ-shortcode-button-size-medium creativ-shortcode-button-edge-straight" target="_blank">Get Started</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.booxi.com/blog/why-your-business-should-offer-online-appointment-scheduling/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>