<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>booxi &#187; appointment</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.booxi.com/blog/tag/appointment/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.booxi.com/blog</link>
	<description>booxi</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2017 18:59:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
		<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
		<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>http://wordpress.org/?v=3.9.1</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Generate Appointment Reports to Monitor Your business</title>
		<link>https://www.booxi.com/blog/generate-appointment-reports/</link>
		<comments>https://www.booxi.com/blog/generate-appointment-reports/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2017 20:30:20 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Astrid Bertout]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Product Features]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[appointment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Owners]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.booxi.com/blog/?p=1456</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[With booxi, it’s now easy to generate reports from your appointments data. A relevant information to analyze your business and help you to bring it to the next level. ]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img class="float_top aligncenter wp-image-1501 size-full" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/vlag5YfyW7i7IcrFCWGZMejfiMo6l6WW_EM2eJ_rb2NxbWqP45YUGDFCwmNmwKEjQgXf4oWZe1W0XXFltjnNvQ=s0" alt="appointment report" width="1200" height="600" />Reports are powerful tools to analyze your business, to take the right decisions, to know where you should focus your efforts and where there is room for improvement.</p>
<p>With booxi, you can now easily export reports from your appointments data, adjust your criteria and analyze them.</p>
<p>Here are key information your can extract from these reports:</p>
<ul>
<li>Know which service is most appreciated by your customers.</li>
<li>Know the busiest periods (whether in terms of days of the week or schedules)</li>
<li>Visualize your employees’ performance</li>
<li>Determine who are your most regular customers</li>
<li>Make comparisons for all of these aspects, over different periods of time.</li>
</ul>
<p>To do it, you have to realize the export. It’s very easy to do it:</p>
<ol>
<li>Sign in your booxi account and go on the Calendar Tab.</li>
<li>Then click on the “More options” icon, and select the “Appointment Report” option.<img class="img_zoom aligncenter size-full wp-image-1502" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/I1KAR7kEOiXj2rDOCTd5WAsWzB90ZF9h2hbf05jepl5LK9njEu1hVlMvu2ur_FLeBVCKwXb8PlmfrJ9NRpjqHA=s0" alt="appointment export report" /></li>
<li>Select the criteria and click on Export.<i>Tips: To analyze only completed appointments, make sure to exclude all cancelled appointments and no-show appointments.</i><img class="img_zoom aligncenter size-full wp-image-1503" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/AUrx0-CvrdLpYKwZWRGF0gp8VsKSoucayCGFuMe2AkYCHOngl_2W4FvSvp2yWdteP5p1OBNkXdlvhVZOrbRt8A=s0" alt="export de rapport de rendez-vous" /></li>
<li>Then click on the link “Click here to download the report”.<img class="img_zoom aligncenter size-full wp-image-1460" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/DhT_hJGqRyEUx8dwdrH-Nx-g3IHpYjFJdEy-7s-gSimSK-3A-wrexHKaew-edljuFdlOmfdSjZ_wGuwyNbMyjg=s0" alt="download report" /></li>
<li>You can now open your file (you can find it at the bottom left of the window). Use Excel or Google Spreadsheet to open it and start to analyze the data that interest you.</li>
</ol>
<p>Analysis of reports is crucial for your business management. This is an effective way to determine if your business is growing, stagnant or if you need to make some changes.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.booxi.com/blog/generate-appointment-reports/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Automatically Dispatch Appointments to Your Personnel and Spend Less Time Managing Schedules</title>
		<link>https://www.booxi.com/blog/automatically-dispatch-appointments/</link>
		<comments>https://www.booxi.com/blog/automatically-dispatch-appointments/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2017 17:03:59 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Astrid Bertout]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Product Features]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[appointment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[online booking]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.booxi.com/blog/?p=1493</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[It is now possible to automatically dispatch appointments booked online to the available personnel instead of asking your client to choose a personnel, or do the dispatch manually yourself. ]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img class="float_top aligncenter wp-image-1487 size-full" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/jGIIyUywkNnHRAH79me-Fa-ksrFffuWo5z3uwyYLe5HoM-cei9k1N-7QZf4GtaITOduYufJT4mzHzB2BkK0XhZo=s0" alt="automatic dispatch " width="1492" height="713" />It is now possible to automatically dispatch appointments booked online to the available personnel instead of asking your client to choose a personnel, or do the dispatch manually yourself. This way appointments get evenly distributed to your personnel, and you spend no time managing schedules.</p>
<p>Whether you have 10 or 100 employees, book spaces like conference rooms, gun ranges, pet wash cabins, or stuff like bikes, kayaks, booxi can dispatch appointments for you, and save you precious time.</p>
<ul>
<li>How Appointments Are Automatically Dispatched</li>
<li>Setup a Service for Automatic Dispatch</li>
<li>Online Booking Experience</li>
</ul>
<p><b>How Appointments Are Automatically Dispatched</b></p>
<p>When using appointment automatic dispatch, booxi computes the availability of each personnel and presents a choice of dates and time slots that have at least one personnel available each. When the client selects a time slot, booxi automatically dispatches the appointment to the personnel available that has the least appointments for the selected date. This way all personnel will have on average the same number of appointments.</p>
<p>Depending on the Approval Mode you set, you will receive appointment requests (manual mode) or approved appointments (automated mode) in your booxi calendar. All automated, saving you lots of schedule management efforts and time.</p>
<p><b>Setup a Service for Automatic Dispatch</b></p>
<p>You can enable automatic dispatch per service, simply by changing two simple appointment rules for that service. Automatically dispatching appointments will not require the client to select a personnel, so you must first <b>Disable personal selection</b>, and then set the <b>Time Slot Selection</b> to <b>Display time slot with automatic dispatch</b>. You can then offer some services with automatic dispatch, and other with a personnel selected by the client.</p>
<ol>
<li>Go to the profile of the service you would like to dispatch appointment automatically.</li>
<li>Click on <b>Appointment Rules</b> for that service</li>
<li>Turn <b>Disable Personnel Selection</b> On</li>
<li>Set the <b>Time Slot Selection</b> option to <b>Display time slot with automatic dispatch</b></li>
<li>Click <b>Save </b>at the top of the Appointment Rules form, and you’re done.<br />
<a href="https://booxi-live-wp-storage.storage.googleapis.com/AutomaticDispatch_2_En-1.png"><br />
<img class="img_zoom aligncenter size-full wp-image-1496" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/cmW7LEtpE_NZn4KuLIBeg8-vOov6nZdNMoYjhZSfnM5VapNIpk-6BoXngxUZTodCHafxrkMGjlr5j6oczotzug=s0" alt="automatic dispatch setting" /> </a></li>
</ol>
<p><b>Online Booking Experience</b></p>
<p>When a client selects a service that is set to automatically dispatch appointments, he is presented with a choice of dates and time slots, without prior personnel selection. These time slots are the available times that have at least one personnel available. If more than one personnel is available for the selected time, booxi will dispatch the appointment to the personnel with the least appointments for that day.</p>
<p><img class="img_zoom aligncenter size-full wp-image-1488" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/Ww8UXP3eZWEA79O-MLJEuFE8_oXLQOvJZaSVGlSB6g0FiSONXXsyTf9Of8ro7awtvI9v8ZCPOk7Nh6-pSg6sdbk=s0" alt="AutomaticDispatch_2_En (1)" /></p>
<p>Your client will receive a confirmation and reminder without mention of who is the selected personnel, leaving you the possibility to make some changes afterwards.</p>
<p style="text-align: center">You spend to much time managing your employees&#8217; schedules? Try booxi for free during 14 days!</p>
<p style="text-align: center"><a href="https://www.booxi.com/business/signup" class="creativ-shortcode creativ-shortcode-button creativ-shortcode-button-colour-allgreen creativ-shortcode-button-size-medium creativ-shortcode-button-edge-rounded" target="_blank">Get Started</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.booxi.com/blog/automatically-dispatch-appointments/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Are you Ready for the Rush of Holidays?</title>
		<link>https://www.booxi.com/blog/are-you-ready-for-the-rush-of-holidays/</link>
		<comments>https://www.booxi.com/blog/are-you-ready-for-the-rush-of-holidays/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2016 16:54:41 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Astrid Bertout]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Business Tips]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[appointment]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.booxi.com/blog/?p=831</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Holidays are a very busy time. Here is our checklist to make sure you get the most of this period without stress.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img class="float_top aligncenter wp-image-832 size-full" src="https://booxi-live-wp-storage.storage.googleapis.com/merry-christmas.png" alt="marketing ideas to get the most out of the Holidays" width="1200" height="600" />Holidays are a very busy time. That’s why we made a checklist for you to be sure you don’t miss anything, and that you get the most of this period.</p>
<ul>
<li>Send a message to wish happy holidays to your customers and to thanks them? Don’t know how to do it? Here is an article that would interest you!<br />
|link to article: Connect with your customers for Christmas and Get more Revenues|</li>
<li>Take also the time to post a publication on your social networks to thanks them.</li>
<li>Make sure to block your day off on your calendar for your own holidays so no one can book an appointment?</li>
<li>According to last year do you need to increase your time slot availabilities in order to answer the demand? Make sure to be able to benefit the most from this busy period and to have sufficient resources.</li>
<li>Publish posts on your social networks to let your customers know about your schedules?</li>
<li>Call your most regular customers if they didn’t book their appointment yet to be sure that they will have their appointment.</li>
<li>Order January retail stock (if your suppliers are closed)?</li>
<li>Want to do more? Why won’t you search which hairstyles are the most shared and liked through Pinterest and Instagram? Moreover it can be a great source of relevant content for your social networks.</li>
</ul>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.booxi.com/blog/are-you-ready-for-the-rush-of-holidays/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>How do successful small businesses retain their clients?</title>
		<link>https://www.booxi.com/blog/customer-retention/</link>
		<comments>https://www.booxi.com/blog/customer-retention/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 Aug 2016 18:53:14 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Astrid Bertout]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Business Tips]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[appointment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[customer retention]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[user experience]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.booxi.com/blog-dev/?p=155</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[48% of small-business owners worldwide said their customers drove their success however few businesses have real strategies to build strong relationship with their existing clients. Find out our best strategies to increase your customer satisfaction and build your customer loyalty. ]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img class="float_top shadow_large aligncenter wp-image-156" src="http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/JHPV6H7630XdPkT6aGGbYt4dbNOeCKLImj9rhG4hRqb7P49-i18E3Nvyp_2SQR6yXKK8HAX__SnumvA7zN1ltQ=s0" alt="loyal customer" width="750" height="490" /><br />
<a href="https://www.emarketer.com/Article/How-Small-Businesses-Get-Keep-Clients/1012460" target="_blank">48% of small-business owners worldwide said their customers drove their success,</a> however few businesses have real strategies to build strong relationship with their existing clients. Here are the best tips to increase customer satisfaction and build your customer loyalty.</p>
<h3>1 &#8211; Ask for Feedback</h3>
<p>Regularly ask your customers to provide feedback. They love that you care about what they think, and a customer that feel listened will communicate a positive message about your business to his surrounding.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>This feedback can also help you save an unsatisfied customer, who would probably not have expressed himself directly to you, and would have never come back. In fact from 1000 unsatisfied customers, only 40 will tell you, while 600 will go somewhere else next time*.</p>
<p>If a complaint is immediately and effectively managed, and a solution is provided; chances are that this unsatisfied customer will become a regular customer, and sometimes even an ambassador for your business.</p>
<p><img class="aligncenter wp-image-849 size-full" src="https://booxi-live-wp-storage.storage.googleapis.com/online-reviews.jpg" alt="online reviews" width="750" height="500" /></p>
<p><span class="bx_text14" style="color: #ffffff;background-color: #44ce5e;padding: 2px 8px"><strong>TIPS</strong></span></p>
<ul>
<li>Send an automated thank you message, with a link to leave a comment.</li>
<li>When a comment is posted online, make sure to answer quickly, to present your apologies, and ask to be called to manage this situation. Do not try to solve the problem publicly.</li>
</ul>
<h3>2 &#8211; Help Your Customers Remember Their Appointments</h3>
<p><img class="aligncenter wp-image-845 size-full" src="https://booxi-live-wp-storage.storage.googleapis.com/send-sms-reminder.jpg" alt="send-sms-reminder" width="1000" height="667" /></p>
<p>Just like you, customers don’t like having to call to ask for the address or the time of their appointment, because they forgot. And if they have taken their appointment long in advance, it is likely that they forget about it, and miss their appointment.</p>
<p>To avoid any risks, send a confirmation email to your customer after he booked an appointment with you, so he has the address and the time of the appointment handy. Also make it easy for him to add this appointment to his personal calendar using an ICS (Internet Calendar Subscription) attachment to the confirmation email. In the same way, you can send him an SMS reminder a little before the appointment. It improves the customer experience since you reduce the probability that he has to call you because he forgot, or that he misses his appointment.</p>
<p><span class="bx_text14" style="color: #ffffff;background-color: #44ce5e;padding: 2px 8px"><strong>TIPS</strong></span></p>
<ul>
<li>Use an appointment management system to automate your confirmations and reminders and save lots of time.</li>
</ul>
<h3>3 &#8211; Make Sure Your Customers Think About You</h3>
<p>Customers are constantly solicited by other service providers, so the opportunity to forget about you or try a new provider are very present. It is important to remind them you exist, and invite them to book a new appointment with you.</p>
<p>Keep track of their last appointment and send them an email invitation to book their next appointment with you. This personalized message reinforces the relationship, because every customer feels unique.</p>
<p>Use a CRM (software to manage the customer relationship) to track appointments and send these emails with the right timing. This small attention will make a huge difference and will decrease the risks that your customers book with the competition.</p>
<p><span class="bx_text14" style="color: #ffffff;background-color: #44ce5e;padding: 2px 8px"><strong>TIPS</strong></span></p>
<ul>
<li>Use a CRM (Customer Relationship Management) software to simplify all these tasks and automate the appointment tracking for each customer and make sure to send emails with the right timing.</li>
</ul>
<h3>4 - Improve the Customer Experience</h3>
<p>If a customer is satisfied about your services, he is likely to come back. That seems pretty simple, but be careful, other factors can influence this relationship. For example, customers hate to leave voicemails, but love immediate access to information such as your availability. So if you are temporarily unreachable, you take the risk that your customer forget to call back, or worst, book an appointment with the competition.</p>
<p>The best way to avoid this situation, is to take appointment bookings 24/7, which means even outside your open hours. You can accomplish that using an <a href="https://www.booxi.com/features#online-appointment-booking">online appointment booking solution</a> that is affordable and easy to use. Customers love it, and you save lots of time off the phone; besides, it obviously much cheaper than a receptionist.</p>
<p><img class="aligncenter wp-image-851 size-full" src="https://booxi-live-wp-storage.storage.googleapis.com/online-appointment-booking1.png" alt="online-appointment-booking" width="1200" height="600" /></p>
<p><span class="bx_text14" style="color: #ffffff;background-color: #44ce5e;padding: 2px 8px"><strong>TIPS</strong></span></p>
<ul>
<li><a href="https://www.booxi.com/blog/add-online-booking-to-facebook/">Add online appointment booking directly to your Facebook page </a>and your website, as well as in all your online profiles and posts.</li>
</ul>
<h3>5 &#8211; Reward your Best Customers</h3>
<p>The more customers are loyal, the more they talk about you, and the more they bring new customers your way. Give them a special attention after their appointment, or periodically. For example: send them a thank you message after their appointment; give them exclusive and limited promotions such as a 10% discount for both, when they bring a friend; or give a gift card to your top 10 customers. They will be so proud that they’ll speak about it and make good publicity for your business.</p>
<p><span class="bx_text14" style="color: #ffffff;background-color: #44ce5e;padding: 2px 8px"><strong>TIPS</strong></span></p>
<ul>
<li>Use a CRM or an appointment management solution to <a href="https://www.booxi.com/features#client_profiles">build better relationships with your clients</a> by automatically sending thank you messages, running reports to identify your best customers, and preparing mail campaign to send exclusive promotions.</li>
</ul>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h3>Apply All These Tips in Simplicity</h3>
<p>It may look like a lot of effort, but it is not when you use the right tools.<br />
These tasks can be completely automated using a cloud appointment management solution like booxi. It is very easy to use, affordable, and it provides more results with less effort; thus representing a huge return on a little time and money investment.</p>
<hr />
<p style="text-align: left">Get a CRM and build a better relationship with your customers.<br />
Try it right now &#8211; no credit card required.</p>
<p style="text-align: center"><a href="https://www.booxi.com/features#client_profiles" class="creativ-shortcode creativ-shortcode-button creativ-shortcode-button-colour-allgreen creativ-shortcode-button-size-medium creativ-shortcode-button-edge-straight" target="_blank">Read More </a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.booxi.com/blog/customer-retention/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>booxi Got The Attention of The Toronto ESI 2016</title>
		<link>https://www.booxi.com/blog/booxi-got-the-attention-of-the-toronto-esi-2016/</link>
		<comments>https://www.booxi.com/blog/booxi-got-the-attention-of-the-toronto-esi-2016/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2016 16:55:27 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Astrid Bertout]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[affordable solution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[appointment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[time saving]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.booxi.com/blog-dev/?p=71</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[The benefits of booxi through the amazing feedback of EIS Toronto attendees.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h3 style="text-align: center"><strong><img class="float_top aligncenter" src="https://3.bp.blogspot.com/-HIdZMFguUdQ/VyJT8nKDYnI/AAAAAAAAANk/Xu2vjk3QheAOL20YPfTILs_SeAxrssEhwCLcB/s400/IMG_0602.JPG" alt="" width="400" height="266" /><br />
booxi at the 2016 Toronto ESI (Esthetic SPA International) Show attracted hundreds of business owners and professionals with its smart solution.</strong></h3>
<p>Business owners and self-employed professionals are more and more conscious that they need to manage their business more efficiently, and that includes visibility and accessibility to their services by consumers, as well as an access to information on their business and an optimisation of their time. Which is why they are shopping for tools to help them.</p>
<p>They have definitely realized by now that their old and expensive salon management software needs to be replaced, and that there are better and less expensive solutions available in the market. Even professionals working alone understand that they can also profit from smart solutions like booxi.</p>
<p>It is the beauty and simplicity of booxi that catch their attention at first, and then when they find out about all it can do for them, and how easy to use and affordable it is, we can feel their relief. They have finally found something that will really change their life. The return on their investment is so big, that the fear and burden of using software goes away.</p>
<p>It was great to see them bringing more people to our booth, as they wanted to share their discovery, booxi. We had a great time with our visitors, presenting booxi and answering questions. We will be happy to help hundreds of professionals and business owner using booxi, to get more results with less effort.</p>
<p>Lots of graduating students will now have a chance to start their own business without investing money on a website or software, booxi will provide them all they need at a uncomparable affordable price and simplicity.</p>
<p>Professionals and business owners will have the opportunity to start using a cloud solution that finally meets their needs and budget, to help them get where they always wanted to be in their business.</p>
<p><strong>Thank you all for visiting us at EIS, and we wish you lots of success with your business using booxi.</strong></p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.booxi.com/blog/booxi-got-the-attention-of-the-toronto-esi-2016/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>iPhone App &#8211; Improved Calendar</title>
		<link>https://www.booxi.com/blog/iphone-app-improved-calendar/</link>
		<comments>https://www.booxi.com/blog/iphone-app-improved-calendar/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2016 19:16:39 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Astrid Bertout]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Product Features]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[appointment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[iPhone / iOS]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[multiple services]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.booxi.com/blog-dev/?p=31</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[All your appointments on hand, with the new features on the iPhone app. ]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&nbsp;</p>
<div class="creativ-shortcode creativ-shortcode-cols  creativ-shortcode-cols-half-half "><div class="creativ-shortcode creativ-shortcode-col creativ-shortcode-col-a"><div class="creativ-shortcode-col-inner"><p>Thanks for your patience with our iPhone mobile app updates. This update will improve your agenda view and ensure that you always see the details of appointments when new types of appointment are added to booxi.</p>
</div></div><br />
<div class="creativ-shortcode creativ-shortcode-col creativ-shortcode-col-b"><div class="creativ-shortcode-col-inner"></div></div></p>
<ul>
<li>Improved Agenda View</li>
<li>New Types of Appointment</li>
</ul>
<p></div>
<hr />
<h3>Improved Agenda View</h3>
<h2><a style="font-weight: normal" href="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/wHwCsECbzd4_moN1_q9wK2gnuHbbDpD3mFr3kAUk_VKYwlx8Js6U0Q9LgendfGkUbUNrdzW91EZXjZ5uuFeKLjPFO0L-_q3NQnCCKGIqpQvVGbezWGG-LlBlCocH3twwAk4xbAjt"><img class="shadow_small alignright" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/wHwCsECbzd4_moN1_q9wK2gnuHbbDpD3mFr3kAUk_VKYwlx8Js6U0Q9LgendfGkUbUNrdzW91EZXjZ5uuFeKLjPFO0L-_q3NQnCCKGIqpQvVGbezWGG-LlBlCocH3twwAk4xbAjt" alt="" width="195" height="400" border="0" /></a></h2>
<p>Depending on how you manage your availability, our previous mobile app was not always efficient. We have improved it to better display your daily appointments.</p>
<ul>
<li>If you have appointments on top of available time slot, booxi will now split the time slots in parts, displaying what is still available and your appointments without overlaps; making it easier to track time.</li>
<li>New appointment types that are not yet supported by the mobile app will now be displayed as regular appointments instead of busy time slot; providing you more information.</li>
</ul>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h2><a href="https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/sPTayNswE0OsK5sp0WaWetV3KcIAuqXYiogAyFiDCTx58s6-3R1ZHjDqHFgxu6oqWZZ6EK9_5EQRJj1Tcyl-6GzEGXrcnYgRU0ythytZjbG9AyJXbKNewfKx_4R74o3LjA-_pXFZ"><img class="shadow_small alignleft" src="https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/sPTayNswE0OsK5sp0WaWetV3KcIAuqXYiogAyFiDCTx58s6-3R1ZHjDqHFgxu6oqWZZ6EK9_5EQRJj1Tcyl-6GzEGXrcnYgRU0ythytZjbG9AyJXbKNewfKx_4R74o3LjA-_pXFZ" alt="" width="196" height="400" border="0" /></a></h2>
<h3>New Types of Appointment</h3>
<p>We often add new features to booxi; which sometimes leaves the mobile app behind. The result is that new types of appointment like the multi-service appointment can’t be accessed using the mobile app. We fixed this for now and the future, by always providing you at least the details of the new appointment type, but limiting its editing to the appointment time only.</p>
<ul>
<li>Support for new and future appointment types</li>
<li>Display new appointment types in the agenda view</li>
</ul>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.booxi.com/blog/iphone-app-improved-calendar/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Time saving : Status, Colors, Copy Paste and more.</title>
		<link>https://www.booxi.com/blog/time-saving-status-colors-copy-paste-and-more/</link>
		<comments>https://www.booxi.com/blog/time-saving-status-colors-copy-paste-and-more/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2016 19:11:07 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Astrid Bertout]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Product Features]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[agenda]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[appointment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[multiple services]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.booxi.com/blog-dev/?p=27</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Gain efficiency thanks to the colors that allow you to know your schedules at a glance and learn some tips to save even more time.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img class="float_top  aligncenter" src="https://4.bp.blogspot.com/-ejU1y2kgWos/Vp8LN2XogpI/AAAAAAAAAik/WBUR6EXCOYs/s320/booxi_NewFeature_Calendar_Full.png" alt="" width="320" height="191" border="0" /></p>
<p><div class="creativ-shortcode creativ-shortcode-cols  creativ-shortcode-cols-half-half "><div class="creativ-shortcode creativ-shortcode-col creativ-shortcode-col-a"><div class="creativ-shortcode-col-inner"><p>Your feedback has greatly helped us to improve booxi in many ways this month. Among many improvements, here are the most important ones.</p>
</div></div><br />
<div class="creativ-shortcode creativ-shortcode-col creativ-shortcode-col-b"><div class="creativ-shortcode-col-inner"></div></div></p>
<ul>
<li>Calendar Look</li>
<li>New Appointment Status (Completed, No-Show, Client Arrived)</li>
<li>Disabling Automatic Messages</li>
<li>Appointment Preview with multiple services</li>
<li>Time Slot Copy / Paste</div></li>
</ul>
<hr />
<h3>Calendar Look</h3>
<p>The appointment&#8217;s look have been improved to make the colors more obvious and bring the most important information at the top. We are also introducing 2 new appointment status colors (for Completed and No-Show appointments).</p>
<p><img class="shadow_medium aligncenter" style="color: #000000" src="https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/0d-dlcNdPzDPAkmtzK_Xf2v1UcX5TwzwanQ443oMz2wbO1TRNdOhjZy4Nc8Ldpg_XYhH8v3MkXlH9ZvPCkzURzSlwHOg4Z0fIzyKXLnvUqimUq-CNLCbq3DGM1e1gzXLAExECNob" alt="" width="495" height="74" /></p>
<h3>New Appointment Status</h3>
<p>We have added a few new appointment status for you to better track your appointments. You can now set and appointment as Completed or No-Show, as well as signal that a client has arrived (when you have multiple staff managing the appointments). Simply right-click on any appointment and change its status. The option Client Arrived is obviously only available for appointments of the current day, while Completed and No-Show are available for appointments in the past.</p>
<p>Completed appointments are grey, No-Show purple, and Client Arrived is green with a little client icon <img style="color: #000000" src="https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/66kH1Iehghv5jowYvKYRnKT_6JdQCbHdIAK-RouoWlrW7D0GKKv3bpAud4GPaTJq2msknup4G7cTO68oZk_P37lHvb4tPZrcdQYSXN3HupcmUD9xiJXsX_kcJphDobAu1ps4q39D" alt="" /> located in the bottom right corner of the appointment.</p>
<p>The option Reopen allows you to cancel the Completed status, the option Cancel No-Show allows you to cancel the No-Show status; while the option Cancel Client Arrived allows you to remove the client arrived indicator.</p>
<h3>Disabling Automatic Messages</h3>
<p>When you modify or add a new appointment, you can now change the message option to prevent booxi from sending a message to the client. Simply change the option “Approve without client confirmation” to “Do not send a message to the client” and no message will be sent. If the appointment was just added and you decide to not send any messages, the appointment will be yellow like a new request. This will help you to remind that this appointment has not yet been approved as the client has not been informed.</p>
<p><img class="shadow_medium aligncenter" style="color: #000000" src="https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/Jf4zoVPND4ePzBQJNQq_WnKks3rgGLgFDTcUA1Lz_MzcZkpkfl2_U1bd4Eg8ctCRUG2nI_dvojAxLu6ch8lJrm8g855p0VXCVWFabBe2BlssK9--gRiq-FPiB2VwlwGHIiS_6BR-" alt="" width="471" height="119" /></p>
<p>We have also adjusted the rules that send emails and SMS, in order to make sure we only send messages to a client when the date or duration of the appointment has changed, and not for any changes.</p>
<h3>Appointment Preview</h3>
<p>When your mouse is over an appointment, we display a preview popup which now has the full list of services for multiple services appointment. Category names will also soon be added.</p>
<p><img class="shadow_medium aligncenter" style="color: #000000" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/VYhrJElNlEC9Wib2VHVrdNBDzi5bJaSC-S70VcjY-lbm_CsYA2-hToPSiAXRui46XrqkJllMM3qti6abF9KkrvmpewXnIXgZxlYng4092eIEiOlY9JirOSOra0hm0WaiDkXBerea" alt="" width="400" height="387" border="1" /></p>
<h3>Time Slot Copy / Paste</h3>
<p>Not only you can move an appointment or a time slot (drag and drop), but you can now Copy and Paste time slots repeatedly. Simply right-click on a time slot (busy or available) and select Copy, then right-click in the calendar and select Paste. Repeat the Paste action to copy the same time slot multiple times, and you can now build your schedule in less time.</p>
<p><img class="shadow_medium aligncenter" style="font-weight: normal;color: #000000" src="https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/KBed22B9FOgAQf8ouDUYulnaTWPgxtgCdfWku891Mobjje9cy4MsIhRVtoPf9q8NERB5c3AJ2dbu2sPuDR1M78dAWseguJ4ruFGzTzfJh5TuvREjXhS6NodOjRhCbQmcNyNmMxFy" alt="" width="299" height="62" /><br />
<img class="shadow_medium aligncenter" style="color: #000000" src="https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/4cBVtQCVapTgwFUfxFsUNOcgl1DLExqNEb-zz7_cXS2ZH55suSXTD37lsKnQ5thrOslzITt1JIiFEhm2-El4ymNWizDBvaoU9MX0mJVNm3DS2FTUROWD4G3RyeflHG-AL7jlbR9M" alt="" width="299" height="61" /></p>
<h3></h3>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.booxi.com/blog/time-saving-status-colors-copy-paste-and-more/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>You can now book multiple services in the same appointment!</title>
		<link>https://www.booxi.com/blog/you-can-now-book-multiple-services-in-the-same-appointment/</link>
		<comments>https://www.booxi.com/blog/you-can-now-book-multiple-services-in-the-same-appointment/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2016 19:09:52 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Astrid Bertout]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Product Features]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[appointment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[multiple services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[spacing]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.booxi.com/blog-dev/?p=26</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Learn how you can book multiple services in the same appointment from booxi to be even more efficient. ]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><div class="creativ-shortcode creativ-shortcode-cols  creativ-shortcode-cols-half-half "><div class="creativ-shortcode creativ-shortcode-col creativ-shortcode-col-a"><div class="creativ-shortcode-col-inner"><p>This is a short article to tell you about the multiple services appointment feature, and how to use it.</p>
</div></div><div class="creativ-shortcode creativ-shortcode-col creativ-shortcode-col-b"><div class="creativ-shortcode-col-inner"></div></div></p>
<ul>
<li>Add multiple services</li>
<li>Add spacing</li>
<li>Calendar view with multiple services appointments</li>
<li>Appointment confirmation email with multiple services</div></li>
</ul>
<hr />
<h3>Adding Multiple Services and Spacings</h3>
<p>You can now add multiple services in a single appointment, as long as all services are provided in sequence (one after the other). You may add spacing in between services, but you should expect the client to remain onsite for the duration of the appointment.</p>
<p>If you need to book an appointment with different personnel, then you need to create different appointments in each personnel&#8217;s calendar.</p>
<p>The appointment form remains very similar, but you now have the ability to add, edit and remove services and spacing as well as order them, as follow:</p>
<ul>
<li>Add a new service or spacing <img style="font-weight: normal;color: #000000" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/2EBKDhLiqiUVp1vc-vKSsYP0SWL2hLdh-G9hiPxm_Bgm9EEhCEFnce_P4j_8JZnrDB_O0Kky1tK8LOMZ11qmXPvTvtOrokHSk_Np7hijeW9ErAX89lQS7fbJwVysQMu7bcF2FSMJ" alt="" /></li>
<li>Remove the selected service or spacing <img style="font-weight: normal;color: #000000" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/E02ATfaqy7a_Y12WCYvyJHp33DpiqKcmuilFU6G4E-IgTi7QKUAxKx0rhB1ZYioB6J31UnRXBtkI5urZEYUpPLWukwqm2goXuhcfdV3blih6VoKQEko0ZU1zUpvJPKI3Pz8cBHSk" alt="" /></li>
<li>Change the order of the selected service or spacing <img style="font-weight: normal;color: #000000" src="https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/vYOT5JJfjtzqbq7fz-_gNqcWQGd8v1T732l1uZ4ggnq7d0_MHOfpLpJToKLzWmFR_f8EP-2gdQw7GLdOtDz5Ol3P7IjJhyryNyy6E-LNjwgYX96tZM64cFEKih7Qg41b7If-ZwB4" alt="" /><img style="font-weight: normal;color: #000000" src="https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/9Zt2IJqQqm76sxCUoD-00brdlQZA1RMgTOFaC1d8OP8-SH3_EzHCoJ8Fzw0K0cBU84DShmF-Dda71yyAx1SS_vc-syiEnQC3sErn3Byarpp390SSWnsxWozHC-exl91xprQ4FhqB" alt="" /></li>
<li>Select or edit a service or spacing <img style="font-weight: normal;color: #000000" src="https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/P8i2H5WIAQ1Ve7sZnf52Rkt5gmj20FvmAyp62yzv5rTGpYDA5VG1u8_0ft1R4LnxTPIxpq5jrv6N-Dov4N_fBFvNLtV3uYdLLna4fr2_C4Au5yOx-s8XmfI4vO3u_otTQ8nlnKNd" alt="" /></li>
</ul>
<p>To add a service, click on <img style="font-weight: normal;color: #000000" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/2EBKDhLiqiUVp1vc-vKSsYP0SWL2hLdh-G9hiPxm_Bgm9EEhCEFnce_P4j_8JZnrDB_O0Kky1tK8LOMZ11qmXPvTvtOrokHSk_Np7hijeW9ErAX89lQS7fbJwVysQMu7bcF2FSMJ" alt="" /> and select <img style="font-weight: normal;color: #000000" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/rDJp7HbImAc6R-O_JFskkH6k2yveb3R5BdtgOIHBIMWsr5gQ6PY0VZkyjk3_qYhL_-Ievgy6pcefQ6ouh6beC9kMf506GJr1Yt_kWc08y4ddZcMrILTTe7Fd7CRzn2g65BhP9am1" alt="" />Add Service, then complete the requested information. If the service already has a spacing by <img class="shadow_medium alignright" src="https://1.bp.blogspot.com/-JS2NBlMWHXo/VnJbjXdsZ6I/AAAAAAAAAgo/slD6X0HUu6E/s320/MultiService1eng.png" alt="Add multiple service and spacing to an appointment" width="290" height="320" border="0" />default, that spacing will be automatically added after the service. Add more or complete the appointment.<br />
To add a spacing, click on <img style="font-weight: normal;color: #000000" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/2EBKDhLiqiUVp1vc-vKSsYP0SWL2hLdh-G9hiPxm_Bgm9EEhCEFnce_P4j_8JZnrDB_O0Kky1tK8LOMZ11qmXPvTvtOrokHSk_Np7hijeW9ErAX89lQS7fbJwVysQMu7bcF2FSMJ" alt="" /> and select <img style="font-weight: normal;color: #000000" src="https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/DOYzrN8tvRXJPOEPgVaGRn6mL-ogKboZk6n8k3j7RTiVgg8F8AbU2SDBetvZlLnaZ4LnDguS8PNmCuG6sjNFNHIHw4pDcj6zQ-6MRK_YUmcOj7ZcoXiVbq8t9BYFxwKJOfoHw27M" alt="" />Add Spacing After, then complete the requested information. Add more services or complete the appointment.</p>
<p><a style="font-weight: normal" href="http://1.bp.blogspot.com/-YlnvYda80Iw/VnJb6GpGJQI/AAAAAAAAAg0/VaTqkxaUmFk/s1600/MultiService2eng.png"><img class="shadow_medium alignleft" src="https://1.bp.blogspot.com/-YlnvYda80Iw/VnJb6GpGJQI/AAAAAAAAAg0/VaTqkxaUmFk/s320/MultiService2eng.png" alt="Appointment with 2 services and 1 spacing" width="320" height="254" border="0" /></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Here is an example with a first service of 60 min followed by a 15 min spacing and a second service of 60 min for an appointment duration of total 135 min.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h3>Calendar View of Multiple Services Appointments</h3>
<p><a style="font-weight: normal" href="https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/Q6Pkr5RjIqF3aC0uFHVql8EgvRUcM0vj17VcYG4OWDeAu8j4UK2r_ZSyziOcGGHUyvQta1PGyGpC3_Y25GmuZzGyVf-RrKzvrvEUgb3_SEh-2HNy_OSaftil6grZxch2O8UtkRkM"><img class="shadow_medium alignright" src="https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/Q6Pkr5RjIqF3aC0uFHVql8EgvRUcM0vj17VcYG4OWDeAu8j4UK2r_ZSyziOcGGHUyvQta1PGyGpC3_Y25GmuZzGyVf-RrKzvrvEUgb3_SEh-2HNy_OSaftil6grZxch2O8UtkRkM" alt="Calendar event with appointment for multiple services" width="247" height="76" border="0" /></a></p>
<p style="text-align: left">An appointment with multiple services will show the first service name followed by (+) to identify that the appointment has more services. Also the total spacing is always displayed next to the duration as (+ 15 min). Click on the appointment, and you can see and modify the full list of services.</p>
<h3>Multiple Services Appointment Confirmation Email</h3>
<p>The confirmation and reminder messages sent for multiple services have slightly changed in order to provide more details to your clients. The appointment itself always has a total duration that excludes the last spacing, but we added the list of requested services with for each the individual time and duration.</p>
<p><img class="shadow_medium aligncenter wp-image-169 size-full" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/fDVw_mEOxIOOFjhQY89wb8SnkmEl7lOcjADk4sHiCymxQAwf1N68vyLeidwpHlq5mguCebRU-_6QCxCfmdHX=s0" alt="confirmation" width="372" height="434" /></p>
<p>In order to keep the SMS message short, it only contains the first service name with a (+) at the end.</p>
<hr />
<p style="text-align: center">Not a booxi user yet? Sign up Now!</p>
<a href="https://www.booxi.com/business/signup" class="creativ-shortcode creativ-shortcode-button creativ-shortcode-button-colour-allgreen creativ-shortcode-button-size-medium creativ-shortcode-button-edge-straight" target="_blank">Try it for free</a>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.booxi.com/blog/you-can-now-book-multiple-services-in-the-same-appointment/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Be successful by tracking your metrics with booxi.</title>
		<link>https://www.booxi.com/blog/statistic-and-advice-with-booxi/</link>
		<comments>https://www.booxi.com/blog/statistic-and-advice-with-booxi/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2016 19:04:59 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Astrid Bertout]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Tutorials]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[appointment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[customer]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[online visibility]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.booxi.com/blog-dev/?p=22</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[To be successful in business, you have to keep track of your goals and results closely. With booxi it's easy to do it. ]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img class="float_top shadow_large aligncenter wp-image-417 size-full" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/2d15Jav70lm5VBuX_vPURXlqooA6iwXXsL1xazlvXHiaCsxKOBngcNuuuMM2E2Ns_kEDl82e60IWOIgbFqcfzQ=s0" alt="Client-Acquisition_EN" width="1200" height="600" /><br />
<div class="creativ-shortcode creativ-shortcode-cols  creativ-shortcode-cols-half-half "><div class="creativ-shortcode creativ-shortcode-col creativ-shortcode-col-a"><div class="creativ-shortcode-col-inner"><p>Nowadays, to run a successful business, you need information. Information about your clients, your revenues and costs, your peak time and down time, etc, but that sounds complicated. To keep it simple we decided to start with 3 simple topics.</p>
</div></div></p>
<div class="creativ-shortcode creativ-shortcode-col creativ-shortcode-col-b"><div class="creativ-shortcode-col-inner"></div></div>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<ul>
<li>Statistics and metrics</li>
<li>Visibility</li>
<li>Appointments</li>
<li>Clients</div></li>
</ul>
<hr />
<h3>Statistics and metrics</h3>
<p>booxi can analyse and compute all that complicated data for you, and present you with simple colorful information that you understand without getting a headache. It has the capability to provide you with statistics and metrics on countless aspects of your business.</p>
<p>If you sign into your booxi account, go to My Business and select Activity, you get access to a series of 3 topics that provides you actual and average statistics with key metrics.</p>
<h3><img class="shadow_medium aligncenter wp-image-110 size-large" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/ikuGdGv2SGuxSbIsq7l7kY-UtOnGqy8Ii4yVgqT1ddSG_0SCTfxAFR2iik-zQ_ZAml-Krg9f2aoQACzQHcQ54w=s1024" alt="statistic" width="1024" height="1024" /><br />
Visibility</h3>
<p>The visibility topic provides you with information on the internet traffic you had on your booxi website, as well as how many times the book now button was used for an actual week or on average per day of week for a specific month. This information tells you if you are doing a good job in attracting customers to your booxi website, as well as how often they look at booking online with you.</p>
<ul>
<li>Use the left and right arrows to navigate from one week to another or through months</li>
<li>Use the down arrow to switch from actual week data to average per day of week for each month<img class="shadow_medium aligncenter" style="font-weight: normal;color: #000000" src="https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/V-i4WFucfjSJ3oILWzPRNBDUZyRPSBGtw5-uJ9CzFYoP92Akv1BsZ5Q3BtnIzCbaAY7yVpHxSdVEzPV0P-Q8IEFKLWXQnm7DENbbECZEO3J-eZcXJHEY2bzFOkL-fJeHed8wgBg" alt="" width="400" height="395" /></li>
</ul>
<h3>Appointments</h3>
<p>The appointments topic provides you with information on both the overall and the online appointments you have per actual week or in average per day of week for each month. This information tells you about your busy days, week and months, as well as how good your doing at promoting online appointments. The more online appointments you get, the more time you save.</p>
<p><img class="shadow_medium aligncenter" style="font-weight: normal;color: #000000" src="https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/OSjU4RuhO3UQ37IYPjJl84tKIcL6k3jgkGV6wDbDK2ozKTfoc8Oo4rzW6w-VcijS0Yx32hUZoF_2Q1VgWZyFlhqrJibeVp_AYnciWTAu7vAjJsdzvsrB0yuyi4END2M10iO-qKc" alt="Stats_Appt.JPG" width="388" height="400" /></p>
<p>To save even more time, read <a href="https://www.booxi.com/blog/getting-clients-to-book-online/">our tips</a> to get your customers to book online.</p>
<h3>Clients</h3>
<p>The clients topic provides you with a simple statistic on your growing clientele. It tells you on a 6 months basis how fast your clientele is growing, as well as how many of those clients booked their first appointment with you from your booxi website (or through online booking). This a great data when you are growing a clientele, and if you already have one, you can measure how fast your clientele gets added to booxi and how quick they adopt online booking.<br />
<img class="shadow_medium aligncenter" style="color: #000000" src="https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/Y-nAgPwGboyMY8SKJwi5OTI0GYaTIWsWSs0S0wZuXjm9IFymwDOfGxXrfMs4a1QwsisWci1gkb8RB3GVKBGI_3cDzuHBoEzW_2EByQ2DyioWHC14MJ7DykUdEl7tHOypgkhFbK8" alt="Stats_Client.JPG" width="388" height="400" /></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>See, I told you it was simple.</p>
<h3>Things to remember</h3>
<ul>
<li>You can access your statistics and metrics from My Business &#8211; Activity</li>
<li>You can view actual data or averages and review it through time</li>
</ul>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.booxi.com/blog/statistic-and-advice-with-booxi/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>