<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>booxi &#187; Business Facebook Page</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.booxi.com/blog/tag/business-facebook-page/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.booxi.com/blog</link>
	<description>booxi</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2017 18:59:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
		<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
		<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>http://wordpress.org/?v=3.9.1</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Facebook Advertising to Increase Your Visibility</title>
		<link>https://www.booxi.com/blog/facebook-advertising-increases-visibility/</link>
		<comments>https://www.booxi.com/blog/facebook-advertising-increases-visibility/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2016 17:18:53 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Astrid Bertout]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Business Tips]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Facebook Page]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[online visibility]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.booxi.com/blog/?p=552</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[You want to get more online visibility, to attract more customers and make your small business successful? Advertise online with Facebook Ads.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="color: #000000;font-family: sans-serif;font-size: medium"><img class="float_top aligncenter wp-image-577 size-full" src="https://booxi-live-wp-storage.storage.googleapis.com/facebook_ads_laptop.png" alt="advertising on facebook" width="1082" height="555" /></span></p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Do you have a Facebook page ?</strong><br />
If not, it is time to create one, so here is an article that explains how to do it : <a href="https://www.booxi.com/blog/get-more-visibility-by-creating-your-facebook-page-for-your-local-business/">https://www.booxi.com/blog/get-more-visibility-by-creating-your-facebook-page-for-your-local-business/</a></li>
<li><strong>Do you have a “Book Now” call-to-action?</strong><br />
If you don’t, here is a guide to help you : <a href="https://www.booxi.com/blog/add-online-booking-to-facebook/">https://www.booxi.com/blog/add-online-booking-to-facebook/</a></li>
<li><strong>Do you regularly publish relevant content to your fans ?</strong><br />
Here are some tips to regularly post on Facebook in only 15 minutes per week : link to the article “ Post regularly on Facebook in only 15 minutes per week”</li>
<li><strong>You are now ready to go further and gain more visibility online through Facebook ?</strong></li>
</ul>
<hr />
<div class="creativ-shortcode creativ-shortcode-pullleft creativ-shortcode-pullleft-colour-light-gray">”Facebook is the #1 influencer of purchases for 47% of Americans.“</div>
<p>This is a huge business opportunity for you. In addition, with Facebook ads you can target your audience with precision, while keeping control of your expenses.</p>
<p>You simply have to use the type of ads that matches your needs, and measure its performance using the metrics provided by Facebook.</p>
<p>Here are 3 types of ads that can help you to reach your goals with a small budget.</p>
<hr />
<h3 style="text-align: center">Boost your Posts</h3>
<hr class="dash" />
<p>When publishing a post on your page you can use Facebook ads to boost it, which means reaching a larger audience.</p>
<p>It’s a very interesting strategy to make your page known to new visitors or to stand out in your fan’s newsfeed. It allows you to sensitize them to your content, in particular if you make effort to regularly publish relevant content for your audience. Indeed the process of boosting your post drives new visitors to your page. If the information is pertinent for them, they should be interested in your page, and they will be more likely to come back and interact with it.</p>
<p>This type of ads is easy and quick to set up, because there are very few options to configure; however, this reduced number of options gives you less control and, unlike most of the Facebook ads, you can’t target your audience with as much precision. In addition your content has to be very relevant to your audience, otherwise it will be a waste of both your time and money.</p>
<p>Audience Targeted by :</p>
<ul>
<li>Fans (people who liked your page) and their friends, or</li>
<li>Demographic</li>
<li>Interests<img class="border_grey border_round aligncenter wp-image-557 size-full" src="https://booxi-live-wp-storage.storage.googleapis.com/boost-a-post.jpg" alt="facebook paid advertising" width="500" height="541" /></li>
</ul>
<hr />
<h3 style="text-align: center">Reach People Near your Business</h3>
<hr class="dash" />
<p>This type of ads is used to attract local customers who live or work near your business. You can promote a post (for example a promotion for one of your services) within a radius that you can customize. Don’t forget to target mobile devices as lots of people use their smartphone to access Facebook when they are not at home or at work. That will surely increase the visibility of your post.</p>
<p>Audience Targeted by :</p>
<ul>
<ul>
<li>Proximity (radius of 1 to 50 miles)</li>
<li>Demographic</li>
</ul>
</ul>
<p><img class="border_grey border_round aligncenter wp-image-555 size-full" src="https://booxi-live-wp-storage.storage.googleapis.com/reach-people-near-your-business.jpg" alt="advertising with facebook" width="927" height="619" /></p>
<p>With this type of ads, Facebook will allow you to add specific call to action:</p>
<ul>
<li>Like Page</li>
<li>Call Now</li>
<li>Get Directions</li>
<li>Learn More</li>
<li>Send Message</li>
</ul>
<p>The Facebook ads call-to-action is a button which invites users to interact with your business. Don’t miss the opportunity to easily convert your visitors into customers or to start a relationship with your audience by adding one of this button.<br />
Local promotion ads are an excellent way to attract more qualified customers who are near your business, in addition to increase your visibility.</p>
<div class="creativ-shortcode creativ-shortcode-pullright creativ-shortcode-pullright-colour-light-gray">“ Smartphone is used for 80% of shops or services researches”.</div>
<hr />
<h3 style="text-align: center">Get People to Claim Your Offer</h3>
<hr class="dash" />
<p>With this type of ads you can promote offers on your services (coupons, rebates, or any other special offer) that people will use in your business or your website. It’s an efficient way to attract new customers.</p>
<p>If the offer is solely available in your business, make sure to target local customers only. And use this type of ads if you want to increase your sales on a specific time, or if you want, for example, to encourage customers to come during less busy hours.</p>
<p>Audience Targeted by :</p>
<ul>
<li>Fans (people who liked your page) and their friends, or</li>
<li>Socio-demographic</li>
<li>Interests</li>
<li>And more</li>
</ul>
<p><img class="border_grey border_round aligncenter wp-image-556 size-full" src="https://booxi-live-wp-storage.storage.googleapis.com/claimyouroffer.jpg" alt="best facebook ads" width="941" height="600" /></p>
<p style="text-align: center">By starting with a small budget spent on a limited time you will be able to familiarize yourself with Facebook ads and identify which option works best for you, according to your goals.</p>
<p><span class="bx_text16 bx_text14">References:</span><br />
<span class="bx_text16 bx_text14"> 1) <a href="http://bettermousetrap.ca/entries/jason/top-12-internet-marketing-stats-for-2015">http://bettermousetrap.ca/entries/jason/top-12-internet-marketing-stats-for-2015</a></span><br />
<span class="bx_text16 bx_text14"> 2) <a href="http://blogues.radio-canada.ca/triplex/2014/05/08/recherches-telephone-achat/">http://blogues.radio-canada.ca/triplex/2014/05/08/recherches-telephone-achat/</a></span></p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.booxi.com/blog/facebook-advertising-increases-visibility/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Add Online Booking to Facebook</title>
		<link>https://www.booxi.com/blog/facebook-online-appointment-booking/</link>
		<comments>https://www.booxi.com/blog/facebook-online-appointment-booking/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2016 16:35:38 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Astrid Bertout]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Tutorials]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Facebook Page]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Call to Action]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[online booking]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.booxi.com/blog-dev/?p=66</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Social networks receive a lot of daily traffic, why not get the most out of your Facebook page and turn some of those visitors into customers. This article will introduce Facebook Business Pages as well as adding online booking to your facebook page.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="float_top creativ-shortcode creativ-shortcode-video-embed"><iframe class="post_vid_iframe" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/Z4h1FK88C_E" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div>
<p>As you know consumers increasingly spend time on social networks. Most of you, self-employed professionals and small business owners, probably already have a Facebook business page. The main reason for that, is to get additional visibility and new customers. Some of you may even receive appointment requests by Facebook messages which is time consuming as you and your customers may not always answer promptly.</p>
<p>Obviously, the main objective of this visibility is to get customers to book appointments.<br />
Let’s see how to get more appointments with less effort using your Facebook Business Page.</p>
<h3>How to Add Online Appointment Booking to Your Facebook Page?</h3>
<p>If you already use an online appointment booking solution, like booxi, you can easily add online appointment booking directly from your Facebook Business page. It allows your customers to instantly book an appointment with you, so they won&#8217;t forget or book with your competitors. Some of you may still be using a paper calendar, so I would strongly suggest to take a look at a simple solution like booxi to enable online appointment booking and save hours off the phone. 20% of your customers will start booking online as soon as you have online booking, that is a 6 to 8 hours of time savings per month.</p>
<p>Some online appointment booking solutions give you the opportunity to confirm and control every online booking, as well as automatically send confirmation by emails for all your booking. In addition it can send reminders by emails or text messages (SMS). All these features save you a tone of time, decrease your no-shows, and improve the quality of your service.</p>
<h3>Facebook</h3>
<p>Add online appointment booking directly from your Facebook page is a cinch.</p>
<p>Let’s start by copying your booxi URL</p>
<p>From your booxi account, complete the following steps:</p>
<ol>
<li>Click on My Business tab from the main menu.</li>
<li>Click on Business Details.</li>
<li>Scroll down to the section booxi site.<img class="shadow_medium aligncenter wp-image-184 size-large" src="http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/RuOxJ-u079o5r8lwPMRjiCa3ZwRr2drsYGo3jgbKa7QBpUBz2jTvuHuzaNpJpA5qfjUy5HL4s-eota6-lqcvyg=s1024" alt="booxi interface" width="1024" height="1024" /></li>
<li>Select the URL and copy it to paste it later on Facebook.</li>
</ol>
<p>Then let’s Add your Book Now button on Facebook</p>
<ul>
<li>Open your Business Facebook Page and</li>
<li>Below your cover picture, you should find the option “Add a button”. If you have already added a call-to-action button, you should have access to the option “Edit Button” to replace this button, because you are allowed to have only one call to action at the same time.</li>
<li>Click on Add a Button or Edit Button to configure it.<img class="shadow_medium aligncenter wp-image-181 size-full" src="https://booxi-live-wp-storage.storage.googleapis.com/add-a-button.jpg" alt="Facebook Online booking " width="909" height="829" /></li>
<li>The following pop-up will appear. Select Book Now among the button options.<img class="shadow_medium aligncenter wp-image-183 size-full" src="https://booxi-live-wp-storage.storage.googleapis.com/book-now2-e1472868573768.jpg" alt="Facebook Book Buton" width="752" height="430" /></li>
<li>Paste your booxi URL. At the end of it, you can add ?book=now so the online appointment booking automatically appears.</li>
<li>Click on Create, if it is your first call to action on Facebook or on Save Changes if you just modified it.</li>
</ul>
<h3>And You’re Done!</h3>
<p>Your customers can now book appointment online with you. From that point, you may post once a month an invitation to book appointments online, just to remind your customers that they can do it. This small addition will allow you to save a lot of time , and customers can even book outside your business hours, without leaving voicemail. How wonderful is that?</p>
<hr />
<p>Make it easy for your customers to book with you by addind online booking directly on your Facebook page.</p>
<p style="text-align: center"><a href="https://www.booxi.com/features#online-appointment-booking" class="creativ-shortcode creativ-shortcode-button creativ-shortcode-button-colour-allgreen creativ-shortcode-button-size-medium creativ-shortcode-button-edge-straight" target="_blank">Learn More</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.booxi.com/blog/facebook-online-appointment-booking/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Get More Visibility by Creating Your Business Facebook Page for Your Local Business</title>
		<link>https://www.booxi.com/blog/get-more-visibility-by-creating-your-facebook-page-for-your-local-business/</link>
		<comments>https://www.booxi.com/blog/get-more-visibility-by-creating-your-facebook-page-for-your-local-business/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2016 16:33:16 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Astrid Bertout]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Business Tips]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Facebook Page]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[online visibility]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.booxi.com/blog-dev/?p=64</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Create your Business Facebook Page and Get More Visibility. ]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img class="float_top aligncenter wp-image-596 size-full" src="https://booxi-live-wp-storage.storage.googleapis.com/Feature4_EN.png" alt="create a Facebook Page" width="640" height="520" /></p>
<p><div class="creativ-shortcode creativ-shortcode-cols  creativ-shortcode-cols-half-half "><div class="creativ-shortcode creativ-shortcode-col creativ-shortcode-col-a"><div class="creativ-shortcode-col-inner"><p>Do the following and get more visibility and more appointments via Facebook :</p>
</div></div></p>
<div class="creativ-shortcode creativ-shortcode-col creativ-shortcode-col-b"><div class="creativ-shortcode-col-inner"></div></div>
<ul>
<li>Create your Facebook page for local business</li>
<li>Invite your friends</li>
<li>Add online appointment booking</li>
<li>Get visibility on your page by publishing posts</div></li>
</ul>
<hr />
<p>Statistics show that 85% of Canadian Internet users have a Facebook account, which means your customers are there and you have to be there as well. Plus, the Facebook business page is free.</p>
<h3>Create Your Facebook Page</h3>
<ol>
<ol>
<li>To create a Facebook page for your local business, you must first have a personal Facebook account.
<ul>
<li>If you don’t, you can create one here : <a href="https://www.facebook.com/">https://www.facebook.com/</a><img class="shadow_medium aligncenter" src="https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/fwi3yPvAw660DuK7KkZbWegcYKXveDgH7tP0kONnaz4wzSpwzaIx2wzxiQpey0aMje6UEhz5NfhpP6P9oMqfQVPm6WFiMTmMGaL5cOyPzSPcYsME2iW9zxIz0cmVReycmTKPsHG_" alt="create a facebook account" width="1101" height="663" /></li>
<li>If you already have a Facebook account, simply log into your account with your email address and your password.<img class="shadow_medium aligncenter" src="https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/NnOKyV3ppUOuf0MGMiZC7odaG_uGbA7LYlP2RDGDC7-V-4hHtgMlp2Wk2gWbWPoF6L9LJyGXhdBKDdxPrzC8hP9TvVZwD-qlHxaOVEbJ4JNvawepjkedTQOqvyiSg3mo-1knQ1It" alt="log in your Facebook account" width="1039" height="71" /></li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Then click on Create Page from your account menu (small icon located on the top right of the page).<img class="shadow_medium aligncenter" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/vczrl7g5-Mx9wZvqt4gnRfyEebyVMpwyg5KuszHGHB97wgueYhimznsOqin7GY8uEiA5uVw0CSFejcXcsp6qCJPlkiFkrwa7Owc2ALsjpth8nsY2CfPzJy4uGSHeC8dx4iP8mlWw" alt="create a page" width="337" height="242" /></li>
<li>Choose the option Local Business or Place and follow the steps.<img class="shadow_medium aligncenter" src="https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/dBN4nIHg9lt0Rxb5R9WUOROWXqGley0hiilruYTOFxqU7DkNQR0E-Ixis4NQGf4AwGneaYzng_taScYVPJdBDDPEIAkpevsTgqywDNChOqqawzFwOiXJvgLl7gayGOTCg_7VNvk_" alt="local business or place" width="289" height="289" /></li>
<li>Identify your Business by choosing the sector or area of activity that best represents your business and by providing all the requested information. Then Click on the Get Started button.<img class="shadow_medium aligncenter" src="https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/qAqL5Fceoyy5AiJXc5nVThuTaYd4JFrF8Y9jX-E6_fT5W38aQul2ILkKu2rKMId9s0RJC2sgf57jSic8In0yW2AMP-dvt3Ih4RO3I0kk-T1RvVlbrldcH0eR90mSorIyqOoBAdpO" alt="set up your area of activities" width="291" height="291" /></li>
<li>Set up your business, starting with the About section.<br />
In this section, you can type category names matching your business activities (to optimize search results), add a description of your service offer, add a link to your website if you have one, and finally reserve your unique Facebook web address. Don’t forget to check Yes to the question that asks if your business is real, else you will not be publicly visible. Then click on the Save Info button.<img class="shadow_medium aligncenter" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/POqtSZWd0dWGkqPNt3zdv1QfMaWXpGxF-JfFXit7TtAkMy0rK6DAPiM9UaAbv2XEym2YeuSL-wlO7srP0mLS0GLoYj021auC72naMyJoyFVbq5HweGSx_KLE_f0gFD1QSQv487Xu" alt="set up your About Section" width="711" height="550" /></li>
<li>Add a profile picture (or logo) from a file saved on your computer or from a website. Once it is done, click on the Save Photo button.<img class="shadow_medium aligncenter" src="https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/lmQBUmdYbhc3AEppvr6AoTwkXics3Qy-VevI_fZkZGsPDtwYVC8zHJHfH2f8BDc-0v47HyWeKZbmeXiX1VNkCVUe-VWMbZmAJacidGHGGuI9CFn3fPZiAlcf5TlabDpZs_OGZ-9T" alt="set up your profile picture" width="630" height="378" /></li>
<li>Then add your page to your Favorites for easier access by clicking the green Add to Favorites button.<img class="shadow_medium aligncenter" style="color: #000000" src="https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/8RGiCDuG-yL1nPCjJrKWd-F0mrBgzz2oqHzbLhAAwWiqaH1p4SegoLwhs0NfhHR9_RbJrSAt0WBIU2TM7rZmusGQXPZ4hQbIgaqMo50bPQ_mURRN35OykeSftFauewEKoIPSNp7V" alt="add your page to favorites" width="624" height="356" /></li>
<li>Once it is done, you must claim your business by checking the Claim box, and by checking “I am authorized to represent these Pages”. Then click on the Claim Pages button.<img class="shadow_medium aligncenter" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/N1El-eAajRgHvmEl7Q0o_ffN3nabdgISNZtTtVnhGzUkhAVPZTMpJOfNA3swsvxtlmIPGs6uHm8G7eqZB-j6fRg03DWsYPrnKa3Y0k9OczE7413bDLOaewTAmlUYcJxKlaV68eLQ" alt="claim your business page" width="972" height="390" /></li>
<li>Finally, identify your Preferred Page Audience, by configuring which people you want to communicate with. Facebook will use this information to better target to whom it will display your publications. Select a choice for Locations, Age, Gender, Interests and Languages, and then click on the Save button.<img class="shadow_medium aligncenter" src="https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/Y8DtO9nO--vAqcwS0UugtQPdZjH5QIAbArJ80EbGi7UiMNqnZrxOw_QgHUB7CG3XAiXDMkbcRHjZAvikG4eR3eCmDVzE9BaiU5p0ih3FGP2NiIg44X8EeDDt3fbHlK8JVidZxnhY" alt="set up your preferred page audience" width="619" height="630" /></li>
<li>And that’s it ! Your page is created !</li>
</ol>
</ol>
<h3>Invite Your Friends</h3>
<p>Now you can invite your friends to like your page by clicking on <strong>Promote</strong> and then on <strong>Invite Your Friends</strong> from the dropdown menu.</p>
<p><img class="shadow_medium aligncenter wp-image-186 size-full" src="https://booxi-live-wp-storage.storage.googleapis.com/promote.jpg" alt="promote your facebook page" width="909" height="829" /><br />
<img class="shadow_medium aligncenter wp-image-189 size-full" src="https://booxi-live-wp-storage.storage.googleapis.com/invite-your-friends1.jpg" alt="invite friends to like your page" width="301" height="389" /></p>
<h3>Add Online Appointment Booking to Your Facebook Page</h3>
<p>Add online appointment booking directly on your Facebook page by<br />
Here is a short step by step <a href="https://www.booxi.com/blog/facebook-online-appointment-booking/" target="_blank">tutorial</a> to learn how to do it.</p>
<p><img class="shadow_medium aligncenter wp-image-187 size-full" src="https://booxi-live-wp-storage.storage.googleapis.com/book-now3.jpg" alt="add online appointment booking to your Facebook page" width="794" height="470" /></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h3>Get Visibility on Your Page by Publishing Posts</h3>
<p>Now we recommend you to regularly publish posts on your page, in order to keep it active. Don’t forget that you can edit your Page whenever you want. For example, you can regularly modify your profile and cover pictures.</p>
<p>Of course your business Facebook page is a showcase for your actual business, so we suggest you stay professional and pay special attention to spelling.</p>
<h3>Tips</h3>
<p>If you are self-employed and your business Facebook page contains your name, it is good practice to put your personal account in private, to avoid confusion for customers who will make a search using your name.</p>
<hr />
<p style="text-align: center">To find out more articles like this one, we invit you to join the booxi community on Facebook.</p>
<p style="text-align: center"><a href="https://www.facebook.com/booxicom/" class="creativ-shortcode creativ-shortcode-button creativ-shortcode-button-colour-allgreen creativ-shortcode-button-size-medium creativ-shortcode-button-edge-straight" target="_blank">See Facebook Page</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.booxi.com/blog/get-more-visibility-by-creating-your-facebook-page-for-your-local-business/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to get my clients to book online?</title>
		<link>https://www.booxi.com/blog/get-clients-to-book-online/</link>
		<comments>https://www.booxi.com/blog/get-clients-to-book-online/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2016 18:52:17 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Astrid Bertout]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Business Tips]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Facebook Page]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[online booking]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.booxi.com/blog-dev/?p=14</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Find out our tips to encourage your customers to book appointments online.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img class="float_top aligncenter wp-image-779 size-full" src="https://booxi-live-wp-storage.storage.googleapis.com/Untitled-18.png" alt="get customers to book online" width="1200" height="600" /><div class="creativ-shortcode creativ-shortcode-cols  creativ-shortcode-cols-half-half "><div class="creativ-shortcode creativ-shortcode-col creativ-shortcode-col-a"><div class="creativ-shortcode-col-inner"><p>This article provides you simple advice on how to get your clients to book online.</p>
</div></div><div class="creativ-shortcode creativ-shortcode-col creativ-shortcode-col-b"><div class="creativ-shortcode-col-inner"></div></div></p>
<ul>
<li>Online Communication</li>
<li>Word of mouth</li>
<li>On your Business Cards</li>
<li>On your Voicemail</div></li>
</ul>
<hr />
<p>Now that you have a booxi account with a complete profile and good looking website, it&#8217;s time to invite clients to use this awesome online booking feature! They&#8217;ll love you for it, as they&#8217;ll save time, just as you will.</p>
<ol>
<ol>
<li>
<h2>Online Communication</h2>
</li>
</ol>
</ol>
<p><img class="aligncenter wp-image-639 size-full" src="https://booxi-live-wp-storage.storage.googleapis.com/prise-de-rendez-vous-11.jpg" alt="online appointment booking system" width="873" height="593" /><br />
First thing you must do, is to make sure your business profile is available online. If you can find your booxi website on search engine, it means you are. To set your business profile online, you simply have to sign in on your booxi account, go to My Business and choose Available Online located right under your business logo or your profile picture.</p>
<p>Now inform your customers about this feature!</p>
<ol>
<ol>
<ul>
<li><strong>On social networks</strong></li>
</ul>
</ol>
</ol>
<p>Communicate everywhere, Facebook, Google plus, Twitter, Instagram, Pinterest, and other social medias are efficient tools to get your clients to book appointments online via booxi. Post an announcement about the fact that you now offer online booking for appointments, you can tell them about the advantages of booking online as well.</p>
<p><img class="aligncenter wp-image-857 size-full" src="https://booxi-live-wp-storage.storage.googleapis.com/get-my-clients-to-book-online.jpg" alt="facebook post to get clients to book online" width="514" height="362" /></p>
<p>Ask your clients and your friends to share your post or your booxi website. Clients are more receptive when it comes from another client than from a business.</p>
<p>Then you can publish this post again many times in the same month, to make sure that it has a great visibility.</p>
<ol>
<ol>
<ul>
<li><strong>On Facebook </strong></li>
</ul>
</ol>
</ol>
<p><span style="color: #000000;font-family: sans-serif;font-size: medium">As we just saw it, you can use social networks to inform your customers. To go even further, you can <a href="https://www.booxi.com/blog/add-online-booking-to-facebook/">add the book now button directly on your Facebook page</a></span></p>
<p><a href="https://www.booxi.com/blog/add-online-booking-to-facebook/"><img class="shadow_medium aligncenter wp-image-244 size-full" src="https://booxi-live-wp-storage.storage.googleapis.com/book-now5.jpg" alt="add book now on facebook" width="794" height="470" /></a></p>
<ol>
<ol>
<ul>
<li><strong>On your Website</strong></li>
</ul>
</ol>
</ol>
<p>You can also add online appointment booking directly from your website if you have one. Then your customers will stay on your website and you will avoid risks that they book with the competition.<br />
<img class="aligncenter wp-image-858 size-full" src="https://booxi-live-wp-storage.storage.googleapis.com/book-now7.jpg" alt="book now call to action" width="164" height="43" /></p>
<ol>
<ol>
<ul>
<li><strong>In your Newsletter<br />
</strong></li>
</ul>
</ol>
</ol>
<p>If you regularly communicate with your customers through newsletter, use them to explain, step by step, how to book online. And for the following newsletters make sure to add a &#8220;Book Now&#8221; call-to-action at the end of it. Moreover, you should make sure that all emails you send to your clients includes your booxi URL and invites them to book their next appointment online. Remember, the more clients book online, the more time you save off the phone.</p>
<ol>
<ol>
<ul>
<li><strong>Ask booxi to announce it for you </strong></li>
</ul>
</ol>
</ol>
<p>As soon as you are ready and your account is well set up, contact booxi : the team will send a message to all your customers to inform them that you now offer online appointment booking.</p>
<ol>
<ol>
<ul>
<li><strong style="color: #555555;font-family: 'Titillium Web', sans-serif;font-size: 18px">Classified ads and online directories</strong></li>
</ul>
</ol>
</ol>
<p>When you publish a profile on industry specific directories or classified ads websites such as kijiji for example, add your booxi website link (URL) so clients can easily book with you. Do the same wherever you post in forums or blogs, always add your booxi URL.</p>
<ol>
<li>
<h2>Word of mouth</h2>
<p>Talk about it! During the appointment, while completing a sale at the counter, or even while booking over the phone. Explain to them the benefits of online booking, how much it is a time saver, and that they can use it 24/7. Moreover tell them they will receive a confirmation email and an SMS or email reminder just before their appointment, so they never miss.</li>
<li>
<h2>On your Business Cards</h2>
<p>Next time you will print new business cards, make sure to add the link to book online with you.</li>
<li>
<h2>On your Voicemail</h2>
<p>Make sure to change your message on your voicemail.<br />
For example you could say &#8220;Hello, you are at Infinity Salon. If you are calling for your next appointment, you can know book online at www.booxi.com/booxi&#8221;.<br />
Thus, even when your customers call outside your open hours, they can book.</li>
</ol>
<p>Appointments book by themselves, you become more efficient and you finally find time for you.</p>
<hr class="dash" />
<p style="font-size: 30px;font-weight: 200;color: #888;text-align: center">Try it for free</p>
<p style="font-size: 16px;text-align: center;color: #555">14 days &#8211; No credit card required</p>
<p style="text-align: center"><a href="https://www.booxi.com/business/signup" class="creativ-shortcode creativ-shortcode-button creativ-shortcode-button-colour-allgreen creativ-shortcode-button-size-medium creativ-shortcode-button-edge-straight" target="_blank">Get Started</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.booxi.com/blog/get-clients-to-book-online/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>