<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>booxi &#187; benefits</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.booxi.com/blog/tag/benefits/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.booxi.com/blog</link>
	<description>booxi</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2017 18:59:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
		<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
		<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>http://wordpress.org/?v=3.9.1</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Why you should use a cloud based solution to manage your appointments</title>
		<link>https://www.booxi.com/blog/why-you-should-use-a-cloud-based-solution-to-manage-your-appointments-rather-than-a-computer-based-one/</link>
		<comments>https://www.booxi.com/blog/why-you-should-use-a-cloud-based-solution-to-manage-your-appointments-rather-than-a-computer-based-one/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 Aug 2016 20:07:37 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Astrid Bertout]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Business Tips]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[benefits]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cloud]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.booxi.com/blog-dev/?p=172</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[In one hand, most of appointment management softwares based on computer are outdated and no longer meet the customers’ needs,  which have evolved.
On the other hand they are very expensive, they do not allow collaborative work nor data access at anytime. So it is time to change for a cloud-based solution! ]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img class="float_top shadow_large aligncenter wp-image-241 size-full" src="https://booxi-live-wp-storage.storage.googleapis.com/cloud1.jpg" alt="use a cloud based solution to manage your appointments" width="1200" height="600" /><br />
<div class="creativ-shortcode creativ-shortcode-cols  creativ-shortcode-cols-half-half "><div class="creativ-shortcode creativ-shortcode-col creativ-shortcode-col-a"><div class="creativ-shortcode-col-inner"><p><span class="bx_text28">We explain you why you should now use a cloud based-solution.</span></p>
</div></div></p>
<div class="creativ-shortcode creativ-shortcode-col creativ-shortcode-col-b"><div class="creativ-shortcode-col-inner"></div></div>
<ol>
<li>Accessible from any device</li>
<li>Accessible from anywhere</li>
<li>It&#8217;s less expensive</li>
<li>Increases security for your peace of mind</li>
<li>Answers the market demand</li>
</ol>
<p></div></p>
<hr />
<p><span style="line-height: 21.6px">In one hand, most of appointment management softwares based on computer are outdated and no longer meet the customers’ needs, which have evolved.<br />
</span><span style="line-height: 21.6px">On the other hand they are very expensive, they do not allow collaborative work nor data access at anytime.</span></p>
<p>It is therefore time to adapt your business to provide your customers what they are looking for. This change is cloud based management software!</p>
<h3>1 &#8211; Accessible from any device</h3>
<p>Cloud solutions are often accessible from different devices such as computer, tablet and smartphone.</p>
<p>Imagine the following scenario: You have just arrived in your business, you have appointments scheduled all day long and not a minute to lose. And here comes the drama : Your computer doesn’t boot. And there might be numerous reasons (power cut, virus on your computer, update necessary that will put 3 hours&#8230;).</p>
<p>With a cloud-based solution, you can immediately access to your customer records and appointments from your tablet or smartphone since all the data are stored in the cloud.</p>
<h3>2 &#8211; Accessible from anywhere</h3>
<p>Some expensive solutions allow you to access your business computer remotely, but it has to be in use, while a cloud solution gives you access to your data at any time, wherever you are and with a complete safety.</p>
<p>You can even give a limited access to employees. They will be able to access their calendar directly from their smartphone. Then they will stop to call you to ask about their schedules and their appointments. It is the same for you : enjoy more freedom with your handy calendar, wherever you are.</p>
<h3>3 &#8211; It’s less expensive</h3>
<p>While you will have to spend a start-up cost to install software and then pay a monthly fee, cloud solutions usually don’t require start-up fees nor installation. Just pay your monthly or yearly fee to enjoy this tool. Most of the solutions offer very advantageous prices, according to your needs and your budget.</p>
<p><img class="aligncenter wp-image-132 size-medium" src="http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/8ja28rQEhtLBrhdVqQyeoCQSEr8YQS_ohSscqXr72D6h-4sOQutN_C85_5cAClYPfKPbLeQK2uIL46ebtbHg=s300" alt="manage appointments from home on your tablet" width="300" height="300" /></p>
<h3>4 &#8211; Increased security for your peace of mind</h3>
<p>If unfortunately you have been robbed, a fire breaks out or simply the hard drive of your computer breaks, you could lose all your data. Are your backup copies always tested and updated &#8230;?</p>
<p>Cloud-based solutions usually have automatic and instant backups. It is therefore impossible to lose your data. Also, if your computer is robbed, or if you lose your smartphone, no data are stored on any device, they remain in the cloud.</p>
<p>Here are several examples of cloud solution:</p>
<ul>
<li>Online Appointment Booking — booxi</li>
<li>POS — Lightspeed</li>
<li>Accounting Software — Quickbooks</li>
<li>Email Access — GMail</li>
</ul>
<h3>5 - Answers the market demand</h3>
<p>Cloud-based solution generally provides features more adapted to the client today, which are at the same time features that greatly benefit to you. For example with booxi enjoy :</p>
<ul>
<li>Online booking appointment — Customers love that and you save a lot of time off the phone.</li>
<li><span style="line-height: 21.6px">Confirmations by email — Customers have all the information they need.</span></li>
<li><span style="line-height: 21.6px">Reminders by email and SMS  — Less no-shows, and more happy clients.</span></li>
</ul>
<hr />
<blockquote><p> To conclude, cloud-based solution allows you to save time and money while your customers enjoy it and all your data are secured.</p></blockquote>
<hr />
<p style="text-align: center"><span class="bx_text24">Secure your data on the cloud and<br />
bring your business to the next level.</span></p>
<p style="text-align: center"><a href="https://www.booxi.com/business/signup" class="creativ-shortcode creativ-shortcode-button creativ-shortcode-button-colour-allgreen creativ-shortcode-button-size-medium creativ-shortcode-button-edge-straight" target="_blank">Try it for free</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.booxi.com/blog/why-you-should-use-a-cloud-based-solution-to-manage-your-appointments-rather-than-a-computer-based-one/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Using booxi with Lightspeed Retail POS</title>
		<link>https://www.booxi.com/blog/using-booxi-with-lightspeed-retail-pos/</link>
		<comments>https://www.booxi.com/blog/using-booxi-with-lightspeed-retail-pos/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2016 19:19:35 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Astrid Bertout]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[benefits]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Lightspeed]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[point of sales]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.booxi.com/blog-dev/?p=33</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Read about all the benefices you can enjoy by using booxi combined with Lightspeed and bring your business to the next level by managing it with those solutions. ]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><div class="creativ-shortcode creativ-shortcode-cols  creativ-shortcode-cols-half-half "><div class="creativ-shortcode creativ-shortcode-col creativ-shortcode-col-a"><div class="creativ-shortcode-col-inner"><p>booxi combined with Lightspeed becomes one of the most powerful and affordable solution to manage every aspects of your business.</p>
</div></div></p>
<div class="creativ-shortcode creativ-shortcode-col creativ-shortcode-col-b"><div class="creativ-shortcode-col-inner"></div></div>
<ul>
<li>We provide a user-friendly integration with Lightspeed Retail POS</li>
<li>Businesses Using Lightspeed Retail, Get Ready to Gain in Efficiency With booxi</li>
<li>Businesses Using booxi Manage Your Sales Using Lightspeed Retail POS</div></li>
</ul>
<hr />
<p>While booxi is all about appointment management and customer relations, it does not provide point of sale features such as invoicing and inventory management; which is why booxi has partnered with Lightspeed, a top class Point Of Sale (POS) solution.</p>
<h3>We Provide a User-Friendly Integration With Lightspeed Retail POS</h3>
<p>Integrate booxi with Lightspeed Retail, and you obtain a featureful solution, which among many features, offers:</p>
<ul>
<li>A synchronized customer management (same customers in both solutions)</li>
<li>Scheduling and appointment tracking (with booxi)</li>
<li>Easy invoicing (sales or work orders) for appointments (a service), where you can add on products and discounts</li>
<li>Automated communications with your customers (with booxi)</li>
<li>Link services to sales item, and personnel to employees</li>
<li>Inventory management</li>
<li>Sales reports</li>
<li>And much more.<img class="shadow_medium aligncenter" style="color: #000000" src="https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/8-BXf8pbDdyZ9Cg3-4VV27U7H6Zux5lMUz-htEMD8V0LbwCYS2Gv99EMUYk5MdwoTzH_pw9goseLUIgmgzN2mLR7vR87Cf6n9MCpgbV9xqAwaIYb-z9gI7xYmb7fzmnkX3Y4Aog0" alt="use booxi and lightspeed" width="624" height="313" /></li>
</ul>
<p>The combined solution is very efficient and easy to use, thanks to its data synchronisation and simplicity to switch from appointments to sales in their respective browser tabs. You can right-click on an appointment in booxi and choose to create an invoice in Lightspeed Retail. booxi takes care of creating the Lightspeed customer if it is not already there, it creates an invoice, and adds the item associated with the provided service, all done automatically. You can then add more products to the sale, or close it right away. It is fast and efficient.</p>
<p><img class="shadow_medium aligncenter" src="https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/X4qi8CmmSvOGM5ADcAYKh9eCtCHW2EAfeBt_C4B_lyzfoux0TTmd16wuj-HfEVnovZP6mHeDoGgQGV31FNEmxmSZSoKbHSbVHS_k50eDGT_5JmArmMous1PM_GxU0gxwpUuwyz1q" alt="booxi interface on multiple devices" width="756" height="568" /></p>
<h3>Businesses Using Lightspeed Retail, Get Ready to Gain in Efficiency With booxi</h3>
<p>For businesses who offer services with appointments, and that already use Lightspeed Retail, the integration with booxi represents remarkable advantages, such as:</p>
<ul>
<li>Top class online appointment booking &#8211; reduce time spent on the phone</li>
<li>Automated appointment confirmation emails &#8211; enhance customer experience and reduce phone calls</li>
<li>Automated appointment reminders (email and SMS) &#8211; reduce no-show below 2%</li>
<li>Appointment history providing a better knowledge of your customer’s habits (including appointment notes)</li>
</ul>
<h3>Businesses Using booxi Manage Your Sales Using Lightspeed Retail POS</h3>
<p>For booxi users who sell items in addition to offer services, and who are seeking for POS (Point Of Sale) features such as invoicing, inventory management, and sales reports; Lightspeed Retail is a great addition that provides valuable features helping you be more efficient, and grow your business. Here are a few examples:</p>
<ul>
<li>Create invoices for the services you offer</li>
<li>Sell items or add items to a service invoice</li>
<li>Manage inventory</li>
<li>Export accounting data</li>
<li>Run and print sales reports<img class="shadow_medium aligncenter" src="https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/_HxmcynPk6284gJmzNQ0Xe8dLiohln_mVF2FVUo9YzVmmWuxv3X65RD9d9ulEaxFIq3bwSyu--OKbtMnlvoy4-Z6UQc7D4Re1CyMoN3ajGBL6ejx-PO0OjIc-brAm1pKNQY7V2yR" alt="create a sale from an appointment" width="852" height="586" /></li>
</ul>
<p>To learn how to integrate Lightspeed with booxi, read this <a href="https://www.booxi.com/blog/tutorial-use-lightspeed-with-booxi/">tutorial</a>.</p>
<p>To find out more about Lightspeed, click <a title="Lightspeed" href="https://www.lightspeedhq.com/%20">here</a>.</p>
<hr />
<p style="text-align: center">Manage all your appointments using booxi and save a lot of time.</p>
<a href="https://www.booxi.com/en" class="creativ-shortcode creativ-shortcode-button creativ-shortcode-button-colour-allgreen creativ-shortcode-button-size-medium creativ-shortcode-button-edge-straight" target="_blank">Read More ?</a>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.booxi.com/blog/using-booxi-with-lightspeed-retail-pos/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>How secure is booxi to store my data?</title>
		<link>https://www.booxi.com/blog/how-secure-is-booxi-to-store-my-data/</link>
		<comments>https://www.booxi.com/blog/how-secure-is-booxi-to-store-my-data/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2016 19:00:59 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Astrid Bertout]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Business Tips]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[benefits]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cloud]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[online]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.booxi.com/blog-dev/?p=20</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Find out why your data are safe with the cloud.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img class="float_top aligncenter wp-image-808 size-full" src="https://booxi-live-wp-storage.storage.googleapis.com/cloud_base.png" alt="cloud based solution" width="1200" height="800" /><div class="creativ-shortcode creativ-shortcode-cols  creativ-shortcode-cols-half-half "><div class="creativ-shortcode creativ-shortcode-col creativ-shortcode-col-a"><div class="creativ-shortcode-col-inner"><p>This article will help you understand how it works and how safe is your data with booxi.</p>
</div></div> <div class="creativ-shortcode creativ-shortcode-col creativ-shortcode-col-b"><div class="creativ-shortcode-col-inner"></div></div></p>
<ul>
<li>Hackers and viruses</li>
<li>The cloud</li>
<li>The benefits</div></li>
</ul>
<hr />
<p>Some of us are afraid of storing data on a remote computer, because we hear stories and we lack knowledge of how these things work. This article will help you understand how it works and how safe is your data with booxi.</p>
<h3>Hackers and viruses</h3>
<p>We all hear stories about criminal hackers, spyware, software viruses, stolen credit card numbers, and data or pictures leaked on the Internet. The reality is that most of these things take place on your computer, not in the cloud. Criminal hackers use various techniques which can easily be avoided by developing some simple habits to protect your computer, or accounts from being hacked. I would say that the cloud is much safer than your own computer, as long as you don’t give up your credentials (username and password).</p>
<h3>The Cloud</h3>
<p>What is the cloud? Imagine a series of computers with lots of data storage capacity for which the access is highly secured. Let say that when you access a website, only the user interface runs on your computer, the application runs on a remote computer, and for that reason, if your computer breaks, the website is not lost, it remains on the remote computer (or server) and you can still access it from any computer. The concept is similar with the cloud, where if you use cloud storage, your data are stored on a remote server, or if you use a web application or service, that application runs on a remote server. In fact, if you have a facebook account, you are a cloud computing service user. Other example of cloud services:</p>
<ul>
<li>Your email account (outlook, gmail and others)</li>
<li>Google docs</li>
<li>Social networks (Facebook, Twitter, Pinterest)</li>
<li>Banking portals</li>
</ul>
<p><img class="aligncenter wp-image-23 size-full" src="https://booxi-live-wp-storage.storage.googleapis.com/422493-best-cloud-storage-solutions.jpg" alt="cloud accessible from all devices" width="740" height="417" /></p>
<h3>The Benefits</h3>
<p>There are many benefits of using cloud service like booxi, which explains its growing popularity. As a starter: it prevents you from losing data; it provides more flexibility for the accessibility of your data; and it allows you to share data in the most convenient ways. <strong>Safe and Secure</strong> <img class="alignright wp-image-24 size-medium" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/WB-xyMnMXbrW1WfgyuECuujeyxT5vf75riqWhZmf_oBGsd0W0g0OVaGnyNPjWk_yyMBWDRkXrNdtFuPlbDS8nA=s300" alt="secure cloud computing" width="300" height="300" /> The access to your data is password protected. Only you, who know your password can access your booxi account and your data. No one can see your password, not even booxi&#8217;s customer support and software developers, as it is encrypted in our databases. No need to do backups. If your computer, tablet or smartphone is broken or stolen, you will not loose anything as nothing was on it. You can simply connect from a new computer and retrieve everything. <strong>Accessible</strong> Your data is centralized, which means you can access it from various devices at any time. You can also share the experience with members of your personnel, making it a team effort. <strong>No service interruption</strong> Another very important thing is that you get no service interruption, as you can rapidly access everything from your smartphone, a tablet or another computer in the event that your business computer stops working.</p>
<h3>Things to remember:</h3>
<ul>
<li>Your data is secured with your password.</li>
<li>You will never loose your data, so no backup is required.</li>
<li>No interruption of service, since you can access it from various device.</li>
<li>You can share booxi with your team.</li>
</ul>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.booxi.com/blog/how-secure-is-booxi-to-store-my-data/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>