<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>booxi &#187; affordable solution</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.booxi.com/blog/tag/affordable-solution/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.booxi.com/blog</link>
	<description>booxi</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2017 18:59:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
		<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
		<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>http://wordpress.org/?v=3.9.1</generator>
	<item>
		<title>booxi at The Salon de la beauté au CFP des Riverains</title>
		<link>https://www.booxi.com/blog/booxi-at-the-salon-de-la-beaute-au-cfp-des-riverains/</link>
		<comments>https://www.booxi.com/blog/booxi-at-the-salon-de-la-beaute-au-cfp-des-riverains/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2016 16:58:49 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Astrid Bertout]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[affordable solution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Owners]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[presentation]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.booxi.com/blog-dev/?p=73</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Did you know that booxi offers presentations and training? Find out all the details in this article.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The objective of this event was to introduce students and visitors to the latest innovations in the industry. booxi was there in partnership with <a href="http://toncoiffeur.com">toncoiffeur.com</a> to present its smart solution <img class="alignright" src="https://4.bp.blogspot.com/-l9iQMrxLW7k/Vz4vBZJYg3I/AAAAAAAAAYY/UVENGRAkPSkk5IZIwvw8aBIVqyhfyw9RQCLcB/s1600/toncoiffeur.JPG" alt="" />for businesses with multiple employees and self-employed professionals working alone. booxi is a <strong>breakthrough for students who want to start a business</strong>, an a game changer for established businesses.</p>
<p>Students and businesses see booxi as an opportunity to avoid spending between $3,000 to $10,000 to create a website, buy a legacy salon management software and networked computers. <strong>With a small budget</strong>, from $17 to $34 per month ($200 to $400 per year), <strong>they will have all they need</strong> : an automated website, a customers list (CRM), online booking solution, automated confirmation and reminders by text and email, and more. This very easy-to-use solution allows them to be, more efficient than most of their competitors in no time.</p>
<p><img class="alignleft" src="https://4.bp.blogspot.com/-0m5M65eFlEs/Vz4vLFgGVDI/AAAAAAAAAYc/OtjZnhwQaiwkKykA16vluEWHC7s2XDweQCLcB/s1600/formation.JPG" alt="" /></p>
<p>The solution enables them <strong>to get more results with less efforts</strong>, specifically by spending less time on the phone, on administrative tasks and on marketing. So <strong>they can focus on what they really love to do</strong>: spend time with their clients.</p>
<p>In the context of its mission to help professionals be more successful, booxi wishes to inform students of <strong>the importance to have a good online visibility</strong>, and use affordable / free and easy-to-use tools that are available to them to<strong> manage their business more efficiently.</strong></p>
<p>We invite students to talk about booxi to their teachers, and schools to contact us to help them inform their students of the challenges and opportunities that will be presented to them when they graduate, through an <strong>educational presentation provided by booxi</strong>.</p>
<hr />
<p>Do you want to learn more about our school training? Learn about the topics of our presentation and send us your request.</p>
<p style="text-align: left"><a href="https://docs.google.com/a/booxi.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLSfhxM5d9SHJazGz8_7gYLBpl2JBu7608RJoNVY1g1CRRspNjQ/viewform" class="creativ-shortcode creativ-shortcode-button creativ-shortcode-button-colour-allgreen creativ-shortcode-button-size-medium creativ-shortcode-button-edge-straight" target="_blank">Presentation Request</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.booxi.com/blog/booxi-at-the-salon-de-la-beaute-au-cfp-des-riverains/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>booxi Got The Attention of The Toronto ESI 2016</title>
		<link>https://www.booxi.com/blog/booxi-got-the-attention-of-the-toronto-esi-2016/</link>
		<comments>https://www.booxi.com/blog/booxi-got-the-attention-of-the-toronto-esi-2016/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2016 16:55:27 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Astrid Bertout]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[affordable solution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[appointment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[time saving]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.booxi.com/blog-dev/?p=71</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[The benefits of booxi through the amazing feedback of EIS Toronto attendees.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h3 style="text-align: center"><strong><img class="float_top aligncenter" src="https://3.bp.blogspot.com/-HIdZMFguUdQ/VyJT8nKDYnI/AAAAAAAAANk/Xu2vjk3QheAOL20YPfTILs_SeAxrssEhwCLcB/s400/IMG_0602.JPG" alt="" width="400" height="266" /><br />
booxi at the 2016 Toronto ESI (Esthetic SPA International) Show attracted hundreds of business owners and professionals with its smart solution.</strong></h3>
<p>Business owners and self-employed professionals are more and more conscious that they need to manage their business more efficiently, and that includes visibility and accessibility to their services by consumers, as well as an access to information on their business and an optimisation of their time. Which is why they are shopping for tools to help them.</p>
<p>They have definitely realized by now that their old and expensive salon management software needs to be replaced, and that there are better and less expensive solutions available in the market. Even professionals working alone understand that they can also profit from smart solutions like booxi.</p>
<p>It is the beauty and simplicity of booxi that catch their attention at first, and then when they find out about all it can do for them, and how easy to use and affordable it is, we can feel their relief. They have finally found something that will really change their life. The return on their investment is so big, that the fear and burden of using software goes away.</p>
<p>It was great to see them bringing more people to our booth, as they wanted to share their discovery, booxi. We had a great time with our visitors, presenting booxi and answering questions. We will be happy to help hundreds of professionals and business owner using booxi, to get more results with less effort.</p>
<p>Lots of graduating students will now have a chance to start their own business without investing money on a website or software, booxi will provide them all they need at a uncomparable affordable price and simplicity.</p>
<p>Professionals and business owners will have the opportunity to start using a cloud solution that finally meets their needs and budget, to help them get where they always wanted to be in their business.</p>
<p><strong>Thank you all for visiting us at EIS, and we wish you lots of success with your business using booxi.</strong></p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.booxi.com/blog/booxi-got-the-attention-of-the-toronto-esi-2016/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Booxi Made Lots of Happy Professionals and Business Owners at the 2016 Vancouver EIS This Year</title>
		<link>https://www.booxi.com/blog/booxi-made-lots-of-happy-professionals-and-business-owners-at-the-2016-vancouver-eis-this-year/</link>
		<comments>https://www.booxi.com/blog/booxi-made-lots-of-happy-professionals-and-business-owners-at-the-2016-vancouver-eis-this-year/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2016 16:52:08 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Astrid Bertout]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[affordable solution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[online booking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[time saving]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.booxi.com/blog-dev/?p=69</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[booxi was at the Vancouver ESI 2016. This overview highlights the great feedback received during the event.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong><img class="float_top aligncenter" src="https://4.bp.blogspot.com/-c-3z2Wuwl4U/VuxImJKXE8I/AAAAAAAAAE0/mR49JG1kax8VOos_zXMsk48Z1L4b5iKSA/s640/SHOW.PNG" alt="booxi founders" width="640" height="507" />booxi was at the 2016 Vancouver EIS (Esthetic SPA International) show at the beginning of March showcasing booxi to professionals from BC and the surroundings.</strong></p>
<p>The feedback we got was amazing and unanimous from the roughly 500 professionals we met with. They were surprised by the simplicity and pricing of booxi, as well as how fast they can start using it and how soon they start benefiting from it.</p>
<p>Professionals visiting EIS don’t really expect to see software in this type of trade show, they are mainly here for beauty products, equipment and new technologies or discovery and sessions for their industry. When they see software, they are reluctant thinking it is about website design, or expensive Salon system or Marketing tools. They don’t expect to find something like booxi that completely changes the game for them.</p>
<p>Even though they think this is not for them; within the first 30 seconds we talk to them, we describe the problems they face for which they all agree by saying that it is even worst, then when we start explaining the solution we have for them, they get very excited. Finally when we show the pricing, the reaction is always the same “Are you … serious!”. The entire two days were like that none stop, so it was very rewarding for us to see the reaction and how people saw us as their salvation.</p>
<p>For students who were planning on starting their own business, it was a true revelation. They will now be able to start their business without spending $3,000 to $8,000 for a website, a POS and computers. With a little budget of $17 to $34 a month ($200 to $400 a year) they’ll have everything they need including the website, the CRM, the appointment solution, the automated email and SMS and more. They will be more effective than most established businesses on day one and be able to focus on doing what they love the most: spending time with customers.</p>
<p>We have been working hard at booxi to reach this objective of providing professionals and small businesses a smart solution that works for them, enabling them to get more results with less efforts. One of the most important objective was to create something beautiful and very simple to use. We are very happy to confirm that the feedback we got at the show, and growing popularity of booxi just prove that this is mission accomplished <img src="https://www.booxi.com/blog/wp-includes/images/smilies/icon_smile.gif" alt=":)" class="wp-smiley" /> </p>
<p style="text-align: center">Thank you all for visiting us at EIS, and we wish you lots of success with your<br />
business using booxi.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.booxi.com/blog/booxi-made-lots-of-happy-professionals-and-business-owners-at-the-2016-vancouver-eis-this-year/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>