<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>booxi &#187; user experience</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.booxi.com/blog/tag/user-experience/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.booxi.com/blog</link>
	<description>booxi</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2017 18:59:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
		<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
		<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>http://wordpress.org/?v=3.9.1</generator>
	<item>
		<title>5 Easy Ways to Gain Customer Trust &#8211; Overcoming the Stigma of the Beauty Industry</title>
		<link>https://www.booxi.com/blog/gain-customer-trust/</link>
		<comments>https://www.booxi.com/blog/gain-customer-trust/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2017 19:18:15 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[booxi team​]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Business Tips]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[customer retention]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[user experience]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.booxi.com/blog/?p=1445</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[This article provides beauty salon owners with 5 easy (and actionable) ways on how to present their business as a modern and reliable establishment. ]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img class="float_top aligncenter wp-image-1481 size-full" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/MTwsWMqTEEss7OBeZeMMtLe3LCghFmQYBgw5uukFzqWQo2zvHDsOLJcJfoepnzIaH3wMn0yjNYxIAqzBJOD81fs=s0" alt="trusted beauty salon " width="1200" height="600" />Great customer service and professionalism should be the first things that pop into your head when reading the title.<br />
Beyond that, there are some aspects that aren’t so obvious to everyone. When it comes to their personal appearance, customers want the best they can get and many are reluctant to venture toward new beauty salons in fear of having a disappointing, or worse, an unprofessional experience.</p>
<p>This article provides beauty salon owners with 5 easy (and actionable) ways on how to present their business as a modern and reliable establishment. From working with an efficiency-boosting <a href="https://www.lightspeedhq.com/">POS</a> system and <a href="https://www.booxi.com/en">automated appointment management system</a> to paying close attention to the details of their salon’s physical and online aesthetic, beauty shop owners will access insightful suggestions to improve (or maintain) their image and gain new loyal customers.</p>
<p><strong>1. Offer personal suggestions</strong></p>
<p>Although customers expect your professional advice, they appreciate hearing about your personal experience with the products or services you’re selling. After all, everyone is different and sometimes practical feedback (as opposed to theoretical or technical) can be a little more relevant and relatable. Taking an interest in your client and connecting with them on a personal level shows them you care and you’re gathering the information you need to give them the best advice possible.</p>
<p>On the other hand, this also means you can’t shy away from giving your customer bad news; it’s ok if you’re unable to provide them with every solution in the book. There may come a time where you’ll need to point out that your product or company may not be the right fit for their needs. They’ll appreciate the honesty and you’ll be remembered as the one who gives real advice.</p>
<p>According to <a href="https://www.lightspeedhq.com/blog/2017/09/4-ecommerce-takeaways-lightspeed-speaker-series/">Simon Tooley</a>, Founder &amp; CEO at Maison Etiket, “if someone has that memorable experience, it&#8217;s not about the product they bought, it&#8217;s actually about [the] people they interacted with.” We couldn’t agree more.</p>
<p><strong>2. Listen<br />
</strong></p>
<p>Ever walked into a retail store with sales clerks selling on commission and get pestered about all kinds of products you’re just not interested in? Of course you have &#8211; and chances are you didn’t buy any of those items.</p>
<p>Learn from their mistakes; stick to what your customer is telling you and don’t push unrelated products on them. You won’t sell more and, in fact, you risk losing the entire sale over it. Your expert advice may have convinced a customer to purchase an item or service, but if you sound too eager to increase their basket size, your credibility is undermined and the first thing you sold them on may now be in jeopardy. Are you actually giving good advice or are you simply trying to make a quick sale and saying whatever it is you think they want to hear?</p>
<p>By keeping an open mind, customers will sense that you&#8217;ve got their best interests at heart and be much more receptive and trusting of your professional advice.</p>
<p><img class="aligncenter wp-image-1480 size-large" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/88Z8fCTVjTUCvgHAYvJedsBkGUCPPzdNOpwQKjdvygkSWSa7o8JJodXkwa_nX8nZJlTNMGaCzdsORSmEcP_I=s1024" alt="listen your customers" width="1024" height="1024" /></p>
<p><strong>3. Unleash your psychic skills</strong></p>
<p>This one applies to businesses who’ve cultivated their relationships with customers (which should be all of them!), who are knowledgeable of their offering and have their answers ready.</p>
<p>Chances are, most of your customers ask similar questions and those conversations often lead to the same solutions. Pay attention to what they’re saying, detect patterns in their purchasing behavior and needs, ask the right questions and predict what their next concern might be, addressing it with an easy solution before they even bring it up. Often, they won’t even know about this solution, which makes it your job to find it for them, “Ask them the questions to get to why they truly come.</p>
<p>Sometimes you have to dig a little”, explains Simon Tooley. They’ll appreciate the thorough service and feel like they’re in good hands. For example, a client inquires about one of your services they’d like to try for the first time but they seem unconvinced of its value.</p>
<p>Instead of just providing them with the straight-forward answer, read between the lines, tell them about an upcoming discount on the service they should wait for and take advantage of.</p>
<p><strong>4. Display positive reviews from other clients</strong></p>
<p>Your customers are walking, talking, “free” adverts for your business &#8211; keep this in mind at all times and only make promises you can keep. A good way to ensure that is to enforce a “under promise, over deliver” rule.</p>
<p>As you may already know, freebies and surprises tend to make customers really happy and getting them to recommend you is one of the best things you can do for your business. Naturally, people are much more inclined to try and trust a business who already has the seal of approval from someone they know and trust. To make referrals happen, <a href="https://www.lightspeedhq.com/blog/2016/06/10-ways-get-feedback-online-customers/">put systems and incentives in place</a>. This can be something as simple as offering a small discount for every new client they bring in. Not only can this boost business, it’s also a great way to see how customers view your business and where to make adjustments.</p>
<p><strong>5. Respond to crisis quickly</strong></p>
<p>In the event of a crisis &#8211; an unhappy customer claiming he or she was misinformed, for example &#8211; don’t sit on your hands and hope the problem goes away (it never does).</p>
<p><a href="https://www.lightspeedhq.com/blog/2016/12/how-to-respond-to-negative-reviews/">Be decisive and respond quickly</a> to show your customers you can be trusted. Remain objective and professional because a lot can be told about a business in the way they handle and remedy a tough situation. A customer’s journey has 3 parts: before, during and after, and it’s important not to neglect the last one as it holds all the power to make or break that customer’s overall experience and lasting perception.</p>
<p>Your product or service must be desirable with clear added value; however, without the customer&#8217;s trust, they&#8217;ll probably buy from someone else. Somebody they trust.</p>
<div class="creativ-shortcode creativ-shortcode-alertbox creativ-shortcode-alertbox-colour-border"><p class="creativ-shortcode creativ-shortcode-alertbox-content"><br />
Athena Kyriacou a.k.a. Tina, is a Content Specialist at Lightspeed POS, based in Montreal, Qc. She describes creating content as “being in her happy place”. After work hours you can find her spending time with her dog, editing videos for her youtube channel, advocating gender equality and then with her dog some more.</p></div>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.booxi.com/blog/gain-customer-trust/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Benefits of Online Reviews and Ratings</title>
		<link>https://www.booxi.com/blog/online-reviews/</link>
		<comments>https://www.booxi.com/blog/online-reviews/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2016 22:23:12 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Astrid Bertout]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Business Tips]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[online visibility]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[user experience]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.booxi.com/blog/?p=740</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[92% of consumers read online reviews before buying or booking. One good reason among others to allow your customers to share their experience with your business.
Let’s see why and how to do it. ]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.brightlocal.com/learn/local-consumer-review-survey/">91% of consumers read online reviews before buying or booking.</a> Indeed statistics show that the feedback from other customers are extremely important and trustworthy to them as they rely on reviews and ratings published online to make a purchase decision.</p>
<p>However many professionals and business owners don’t benefit from consumer feedback as their website and Facebook page do not offer any way to leave a feedback.</p>
<p>The main reason is because many of them express fear about it : the fear that an unsatisfied customer publishes a negative comment, or the fear that they don’t have enough time to properly manage and review comments.</p>
<p>As mentioned above, statistics show that consumers do consult online reviews to build their opinion on your business. Which is why, it is crucial that they easily find comments and reviews about your business and your services; if they can’t find any, they will most likely find another business with reviews.</p>
<p><img class="aligncenter wp-image-759 size-full" src="https://booxi-live-wp-storage.storage.googleapis.com/Untitled-7.png" alt="online rating and reviews" width="1200" height="600" /></p>
<h2 style="text-align: center"><span style="font-weight: 400">There is Much to Win, Nothing to Lose</span></h2>
<p>There are more positive than negative points in letting your customers give their feedback on your business:</p>
<ul>
<li>Testimonials help future customers to take a decision.</li>
<li>If an unsatisfied customer has the opportunity to express himself, and that you create a dialogue, chances are that you won’t lose that customer. In contrast, an unsatisfied customer who couldn’t express himself will probably never come back.</li>
<li>If you take a moment and answer to a negative review, you show to your futures customers how professional and caring about your customers you are.</li>
<li>Finally it is much better to have few negative comments online and to be aware of a problem in your business than it is to find out too late. For you it’s an opportunity to fix something before it becomes a costly problem.</li>
</ul>
<h2 style="text-align: center"><span style="font-weight: 400">Easy to Do and Simple to Managed</span></h2>
<p>Adding reviews and rating to your online presence is not that difficult of a task, and those reviews can be managed with little time investment.</p>
<p><b>How to activate it on your Facebook page?</b></p>
<ol>
<li>Go on<a href="https://www.booxi.com/blog/get-more-visibility-by-creating-your-facebook-page-for-your-local-business/"> your Facebook page</a>,</li>
<li>Then click on Settings,</li>
<li>Then click on General on the left,</li>
<li>In the section Reviews, click on Edit.<img class="shadow_medium aligncenter wp-image-755 size-full" src="https://booxi-live-wp-storage.storage.googleapis.com/activate-reviews.png" alt="turn on review on Facebook" width="932" height="198" /></li>
<li>Then choose the option Allow visitors to review this Page</li>
<li>Finally click on Save Changes.</li>
</ol>
<p><strong>Ask your current customers to leave a review on your Google My Business profile</strong><br />
After creating your <a href="https://www.booxi.com/blog/get-more-visibility-by-registering-with-google-my-business-2/">Google My Business profile</a>, to get the most out of your search results, ask your most loyal customers to <a href="https://support.google.com/maps/answer/6230175?visit_id=1-636312521334535531-1954460559&amp;rd=1&amp;hl=en">leave a review on your profile</a>. This is a really effective strategy to convert online visitors into real customers. Indeed <a href="http://searchengineland.com/88-consumers-trust-online-reviews-much-personal-recommendations-195803">88% of consumers</a> believe online reviews as much as a friend&#8217;s recommendation.</p>
<p><b>What do I do with it?</b></p>
<ul>
<li>Now all you have to do is to inform your customers they can leave a feedback online about your business and your services. Remember to ask all your happy customers to do it.</li>
<li>Schedule about 4 sessions of 15 minutes each during the week to review comments and answer them.</li>
<li>You can also ask to your customers to let their reviews on others platforms such as Tripadvisor for example.</li>
</ul>
<p>You are a booxi user and you want to give your review on our solution ?</p>
<p><a href="https://www.facebook.com/booxicom/reviews/?utm_source=article&amp;utm_campaign=the-benefits-of-online-reviews-and-ratings&amp;utm_medium=cta">Click here.</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.booxi.com/blog/online-reviews/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>How do successful small businesses retain their clients?</title>
		<link>https://www.booxi.com/blog/customer-retention/</link>
		<comments>https://www.booxi.com/blog/customer-retention/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 Aug 2016 18:53:14 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Astrid Bertout]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Business Tips]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[appointment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[customer retention]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[user experience]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.booxi.com/blog-dev/?p=155</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[48% of small-business owners worldwide said their customers drove their success however few businesses have real strategies to build strong relationship with their existing clients. Find out our best strategies to increase your customer satisfaction and build your customer loyalty. ]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img class="float_top shadow_large aligncenter wp-image-156" src="http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/JHPV6H7630XdPkT6aGGbYt4dbNOeCKLImj9rhG4hRqb7P49-i18E3Nvyp_2SQR6yXKK8HAX__SnumvA7zN1ltQ=s0" alt="loyal customer" width="750" height="490" /><br />
<a href="https://www.emarketer.com/Article/How-Small-Businesses-Get-Keep-Clients/1012460" target="_blank">48% of small-business owners worldwide said their customers drove their success,</a> however few businesses have real strategies to build strong relationship with their existing clients. Here are the best tips to increase customer satisfaction and build your customer loyalty.</p>
<h3>1 &#8211; Ask for Feedback</h3>
<p>Regularly ask your customers to provide feedback. They love that you care about what they think, and a customer that feel listened will communicate a positive message about your business to his surrounding.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>This feedback can also help you save an unsatisfied customer, who would probably not have expressed himself directly to you, and would have never come back. In fact from 1000 unsatisfied customers, only 40 will tell you, while 600 will go somewhere else next time*.</p>
<p>If a complaint is immediately and effectively managed, and a solution is provided; chances are that this unsatisfied customer will become a regular customer, and sometimes even an ambassador for your business.</p>
<p><img class="aligncenter wp-image-849 size-full" src="https://booxi-live-wp-storage.storage.googleapis.com/online-reviews.jpg" alt="online reviews" width="750" height="500" /></p>
<p><span class="bx_text14" style="color: #ffffff;background-color: #44ce5e;padding: 2px 8px"><strong>TIPS</strong></span></p>
<ul>
<li>Send an automated thank you message, with a link to leave a comment.</li>
<li>When a comment is posted online, make sure to answer quickly, to present your apologies, and ask to be called to manage this situation. Do not try to solve the problem publicly.</li>
</ul>
<h3>2 &#8211; Help Your Customers Remember Their Appointments</h3>
<p><img class="aligncenter wp-image-845 size-full" src="https://booxi-live-wp-storage.storage.googleapis.com/send-sms-reminder.jpg" alt="send-sms-reminder" width="1000" height="667" /></p>
<p>Just like you, customers don’t like having to call to ask for the address or the time of their appointment, because they forgot. And if they have taken their appointment long in advance, it is likely that they forget about it, and miss their appointment.</p>
<p>To avoid any risks, send a confirmation email to your customer after he booked an appointment with you, so he has the address and the time of the appointment handy. Also make it easy for him to add this appointment to his personal calendar using an ICS (Internet Calendar Subscription) attachment to the confirmation email. In the same way, you can send him an SMS reminder a little before the appointment. It improves the customer experience since you reduce the probability that he has to call you because he forgot, or that he misses his appointment.</p>
<p><span class="bx_text14" style="color: #ffffff;background-color: #44ce5e;padding: 2px 8px"><strong>TIPS</strong></span></p>
<ul>
<li>Use an appointment management system to automate your confirmations and reminders and save lots of time.</li>
</ul>
<h3>3 &#8211; Make Sure Your Customers Think About You</h3>
<p>Customers are constantly solicited by other service providers, so the opportunity to forget about you or try a new provider are very present. It is important to remind them you exist, and invite them to book a new appointment with you.</p>
<p>Keep track of their last appointment and send them an email invitation to book their next appointment with you. This personalized message reinforces the relationship, because every customer feels unique.</p>
<p>Use a CRM (software to manage the customer relationship) to track appointments and send these emails with the right timing. This small attention will make a huge difference and will decrease the risks that your customers book with the competition.</p>
<p><span class="bx_text14" style="color: #ffffff;background-color: #44ce5e;padding: 2px 8px"><strong>TIPS</strong></span></p>
<ul>
<li>Use a CRM (Customer Relationship Management) software to simplify all these tasks and automate the appointment tracking for each customer and make sure to send emails with the right timing.</li>
</ul>
<h3>4 - Improve the Customer Experience</h3>
<p>If a customer is satisfied about your services, he is likely to come back. That seems pretty simple, but be careful, other factors can influence this relationship. For example, customers hate to leave voicemails, but love immediate access to information such as your availability. So if you are temporarily unreachable, you take the risk that your customer forget to call back, or worst, book an appointment with the competition.</p>
<p>The best way to avoid this situation, is to take appointment bookings 24/7, which means even outside your open hours. You can accomplish that using an <a href="https://www.booxi.com/features#online-appointment-booking">online appointment booking solution</a> that is affordable and easy to use. Customers love it, and you save lots of time off the phone; besides, it obviously much cheaper than a receptionist.</p>
<p><img class="aligncenter wp-image-851 size-full" src="https://booxi-live-wp-storage.storage.googleapis.com/online-appointment-booking1.png" alt="online-appointment-booking" width="1200" height="600" /></p>
<p><span class="bx_text14" style="color: #ffffff;background-color: #44ce5e;padding: 2px 8px"><strong>TIPS</strong></span></p>
<ul>
<li><a href="https://www.booxi.com/blog/add-online-booking-to-facebook/">Add online appointment booking directly to your Facebook page </a>and your website, as well as in all your online profiles and posts.</li>
</ul>
<h3>5 &#8211; Reward your Best Customers</h3>
<p>The more customers are loyal, the more they talk about you, and the more they bring new customers your way. Give them a special attention after their appointment, or periodically. For example: send them a thank you message after their appointment; give them exclusive and limited promotions such as a 10% discount for both, when they bring a friend; or give a gift card to your top 10 customers. They will be so proud that they’ll speak about it and make good publicity for your business.</p>
<p><span class="bx_text14" style="color: #ffffff;background-color: #44ce5e;padding: 2px 8px"><strong>TIPS</strong></span></p>
<ul>
<li>Use a CRM or an appointment management solution to <a href="https://www.booxi.com/features#client_profiles">build better relationships with your clients</a> by automatically sending thank you messages, running reports to identify your best customers, and preparing mail campaign to send exclusive promotions.</li>
</ul>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h3>Apply All These Tips in Simplicity</h3>
<p>It may look like a lot of effort, but it is not when you use the right tools.<br />
These tasks can be completely automated using a cloud appointment management solution like booxi. It is very easy to use, affordable, and it provides more results with less effort; thus representing a huge return on a little time and money investment.</p>
<hr />
<p style="text-align: left">Get a CRM and build a better relationship with your customers.<br />
Try it right now &#8211; no credit card required.</p>
<p style="text-align: center"><a href="https://www.booxi.com/features#client_profiles" class="creativ-shortcode creativ-shortcode-button creativ-shortcode-button-colour-allgreen creativ-shortcode-button-size-medium creativ-shortcode-button-edge-straight" target="_blank">Read More </a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.booxi.com/blog/customer-retention/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Get More Customers Through Internet ?</title>
		<link>https://www.booxi.com/blog/get-more-customers-through-internet/</link>
		<comments>https://www.booxi.com/blog/get-more-customers-through-internet/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2016 16:29:34 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[booxi-admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Business Tips]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[online visibility]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[user experience]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[website]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.booxi.com/blog-dev/?p=60</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Today 86% of customers use Internet. Then it is a great opportunity for you to get more clients. Here are some tips to optimize your chances to convert your online traffic into real customers.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img class="float_top shadow_large aligncenter wp-image-391 size-full" src="https://booxi-live-wp-storage.storage.googleapis.com/photo_1460954037_temp.jpg" alt="Use Internet to get more customers" width="1050" height="700" /><br />
<div class="creativ-shortcode creativ-shortcode-cols  creativ-shortcode-cols-half-half "><div class="creativ-shortcode creativ-shortcode-col creativ-shortcode-col-a"><div class="creativ-shortcode-col-inner"><p>Whether you have just started your business or you are already well settled, you invest time to develop new customers. To be sure to invest your efforts in a good way, here are some guidelines to get more customers through Internet</p>
</div></div></p>
<div class="creativ-shortcode creativ-shortcode-col creativ-shortcode-col-b"><div class="creativ-shortcode-col-inner"></div></div>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<ul>
<li>Increase your visibility</li>
<li>Enhance the user experience</li>
<li>Involve Your Current Customers To Attract New Ones</div></li>
</ul>
<hr />
<h3>Increase Your Visibility</h3>
<p>The first step is to be easily and professionaly available online. You don’t need to be a technology expert, there is a lot of solutions to create a website in a few clics, even for limited budgets. For example, 85 % of the consumers have a Facebook account. That’s why create a business Facebook page is a good start. Later an automated website from booxi, or from <a href="http://www.appyourself.com/fr-ca">appyourself</a>, or <a href="http://en.webself.net/">Webself</a> for example, will provide you a website on a little budget. Then increase the visibility of your website by sharing useful content regularly on your social networks. You can, for example, inform them about your news, your promotions, a change in your open hours or give them advice. You don’t need to be on all the social networks. The most efficient communication is the one that use the tool that your customers actually use. For example :</p>
<ul>
<li>Twitter to announce a slot last minute with a discount</li>
<li><span style="line-height: 21.6px">Facebook, to share information about your promotions or to post articles</span></li>
<li><span style="line-height: 21.6px">Instagram or Pinterest, greatly facilitate sharing photos and pictures, if your business plays in the beauty, visual and creativity industries.</span></li>
<li><span style="line-height: 21.6px">Finally keep in mind that it is usual to publish the same message on different platforms, as long as the format is adapted.</span></li>
</ul>
<h3>Enhance The User Experience</h3>
<p>Once your customers find you online, be sure that it is very simple for them to book an appointment with you. First, you have to be easily reachable by adding the information of all the means to contact you. Clearly indicate your details on your website and maybe add the online appointment booking. Your customers can make an appointment at the time that suit them best, even out of your open hours and without having to leave a voice message. You would be surprised to see how much people prefer to avoid the phone. When they have the opportunity to do it, around 20% of customers will book online. If your customers have to make an additional effort to reach you, they won’t do it.</p>
<h3>Involve Your Current Customers To Attract New Ones</h3>
<p>Finally your current customers are your best ambassadors. You can encourage them to testimony, by sharing their reviews on you social networks. And the more they will comment, like and share your publications, the more your visibility will increase.</p>
<ul>
<li>Likes and shares increase the visibility of your publication on news feed</li>
<li><span style="line-height: 21.6px">Comments will be display on their friends news feed</span></li>
<li><span style="line-height: 21.6px">People rely heavily on advice from their friends</span></li>
<li><span style="line-height: 21.6px">Finally, the more interactions you have on your page, the more your page will appear and reach people.</span></li>
</ul>
<p>To conclude, online presence is imperative, the use of social networks will bring new customers to discover your business and to make online appointment with you.</p>
<hr />
<p style="text-align: center">booxi can help you to easily complete those steps. Try it for free during 30 days &#8211; no credit card required.</p>
<p style="text-align: center"><a href="https://www.booxi.com/en" class="creativ-shortcode creativ-shortcode-button creativ-shortcode-button-colour-allgreen creativ-shortcode-button-size-medium creativ-shortcode-button-edge-straight" target="_blank">Read More ?</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.booxi.com/blog/get-more-customers-through-internet/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Export Your Clients List, Referral Data and Much More!</title>
		<link>https://www.booxi.com/blog/export-your-clients-list-referral-data/</link>
		<comments>https://www.booxi.com/blog/export-your-clients-list-referral-data/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2016 19:15:06 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Astrid Bertout]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Product Features]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[customer]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[optimization]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[user experience]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.booxi.com/blog-dev/?p=30</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Improve your communication with your clients thanks to our new features : send them thank-you message, promotions or newsletter, and know how they heard about you.  ]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><div class="creativ-shortcode creativ-shortcode-cols  creativ-shortcode-cols-half-half "><div class="creativ-shortcode creativ-shortcode-col creativ-shortcode-col-a"><div class="creativ-shortcode-col-inner"><p>In response to your requests, we’ve just released a new version of booxi, to improve your experience with several new features:</p>
</div></div></p>
<div class="creativ-shortcode creativ-shortcode-col creativ-shortcode-col-b"><div class="creativ-shortcode-col-inner"></div></div>
<ul>
<li>Export your clients list</li>
<li>Add a referral question</li>
<li>Offer services by phone or by video conference</li>
<li>Book appointments directly from a client record</li>
<li>Automatically send thank you messages to your clients after their appointments</div></li>
</ul>
<hr />
<h3>Export Your Clients List</h3>
<p>We’ve added a feature that allows you to export the contact details of all or a subset of your clients in CSV format (compatible with Excel and XLSX). With this new feature you can easily use the software of your choice (ex :<a href="//mailchimp.com"> http://mailchimp.com</a>) to send emails for promotions, newsletters, or even invite inactive clients to come back.</p>
<p>You can export your clients list from the following criteria:</p>
<ul>
<li>Clients whose birthday is soon.</li>
<li>Clients who recently had an appointment, or those who have not come for a long time.</li>
<li>Clients who had an appointment with a specific member of your personnel.</li>
<li>You can exclude customers who have requested not to receive emails.</li>
<li>You can include additional information on the frequency of appointment, cancellation, no-show, etc.</li>
</ul>
<p>Complete the following steps :</p>
<ol>
<li>Click on the Clients section from the main menu on the left side to access your client list.</li>
<li>Then click on the button <img src="https://1.bp.blogspot.com/-GPLN2SDkfew/V2mKP-NvKDI/AAAAAAAAAfU/J7UyEWJ9E-UsxdQAGFV2PZ8Z5Fm6QwDbQCLcB/s1600/options.png" alt="" width="60" height="32" /> at the top of the client list, and then on the Export the client list option.<img class="shadow_medium aligncenter" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/wiKQXemPLaPu0gTLgQW9jh_xZCpiE3gJ9HOqZ93aY2RewILx1_q1oB4FMEsw6cmMEvCmT022wb6kYgemqFP4trJsMQyRQionWmVWO5p-R9E_58_k7U6e_0y6QBhaoFJMxSFCVW6Y" alt="export the client list from booxi" width="865" height="412" /></li>
<li>Adjust your export criteria to identify which clients and what information will be exported. For example to mark a birthday, bring back former clients, or to target the clients of a specific member of your personnel.</li>
<li>Click on Export, and if everything went well, a pop-up with a link to download the CSV file should appear on the screen. If no client could be exported, review your export criteria.</li>
<li>Click on the link Click here to download the exported clients and that’s it. You should receive the list at the bottom of your web browser.</li>
</ol>
<h3><img class="shadow_medium aligncenter" style="font-weight: normal;color: #000000" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/3imfv22EW2BpCxb2zvxAH-t_wYWPclYVLdJz3k3R7UT4LmRh4znfKwwlTapI4Cke3NFCOf1aBUf4hUV-AApmnmRYSgFLJYwIz6rcyhf6C248roEYLc-U46yD-2lEN0ccdIDfWx9Y" alt="choose criteria before the export" width="624" height="436" /><br />
Add a Referral Question</h3>
<p>To know how your clients heard about you, you can now choose to activate a referral question that will be asked to new clients. This question will be asked to your client when they book online, or to you when you add an appointment.<br />
The answer will be available in the appointment form, and in the client details as well. You can also customize the question and its responses.</p>
<p>Complete the following steps :</p>
<ol>
<li>Click on the My Business section from the main menu, and then on the Appointment Rules sub-section.</li>
<li>Scroll down to Enable the new client referral question and activate the option.</li>
<li>Next you can customize the question and its responses. Don’t forget to click on Save to keep the changes you made.</li>
</ol>
<p><img class="shadow_medium aligncenter" src="https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/j900AA9K_ECRe5XMuZnBHihQZGDNAwtdtoskX_RM0KAgJKSN26vvYoo7QNWW31ph-DGhp-t8PrUZDkZY8iwhhhcUeQtYSJik1hzV6YwXgULSZCAOwZcdxdxoFmpHz0hBvHTrJNH8" alt="enable referral question during online booking" width="589" height="571" /><br />
The question will appear when a new client completes his first online appointment booking.</p>
<p><img class="shadow_medium aligncenter" style="font-weight: normal;color: #000000" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/BzrfAr7UWElJV20fmTrWegECIWKdt1enujV9Ar1Jg7t1PvEbGEXVqXR5SfC3dtB2HUH6zGKyJ-ZpJh0f7FBAgKdLWfxotx54GBwLfYIxjgxeFfJMkD8YprXczK4Pz1zrZCROZXtd" alt="referral question for new customer" width="624" height="376" /></p>
<p>The client can select the option that best matches his situation, then click on the Send your answers button, and he’s done!</p>
<p><img class="shadow_medium aligncenter" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/1eGMV6ta9HC8J7Y0sWc2SSLc3MiEzFSCwAAsnFwK5mkBpa7mn_P9bykMumW2L6IETnXqB9x04WEupzgiIOuTFTLamN0ROciCaVgwx58DJRm0FNnJuj1lUMEWCnstwDL7JDj7rLfB" alt="thank you message for answering online" width="963" height="581" /></p>
<p>If you book the appointment by phone, booxi allows you to answer the referral question on behalf of your client.</p>
<p><img class="shadow_medium aligncenter" src="https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/o35-n5lcHOQFp_C0jBecoxrlk8fzG1GEoEAC-DbnXVuh73QBlwRMhic5_enPH-6b3fgC-JCFhVWXyzdV6UcFqUtx1ohID1kGvyz4mIfxPPuz4qlU-p9DswDp3lKwaoYT-aua9m6i" alt="answer the referral question by phone" width="584" height="602" /></p>
<p>The answer is also available in the appointment form and in the client details. We will soon be offering a statistic report for the referral question answers.</p>
<h3>Offer Services by Phone or by Video Conference</h3>
<p>You can now offer and book appointments for remote services provided by phone or by video conference using booxi. Simply change the location of the service using the options By phone or By video conference which are offered in addition to the options At Home or At My Business.</p>
<p>Complete the following steps :<br />
1. Click on the Services section from the main menu on the left side, then select a service.<br />
2. Click on Service Details and change the location.<br />
3. Do not forget to click Save to keep your changes.</p>
<p><img class="shadow_medium aligncenter" style="font-weight: normal;color: #000000" src="https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/wccVYIw24qWKBFxoZl2pCP8wD-CGBABq9pkEGHhjGoUVyiGD7Uo9buI_KK4vVp6qRTCMQiod9D7rxXBStSMrAE1fvjEjuZ69liTJhFTV4yORROdDoU5z7PpaNbVl9sms0TRWtcwb" alt="location options for appointment" width="584" height="478" /></p>
<p>When adding or reviewing an appointment, you can specify a phone number for the location By Phone, and you can add a web link for the location By Video Conference in the Instructions section.This information will be incorporated in the appointment confirmation and reminder messages sent to clients.</p>
<h3>Book Appointments Directly from a Client Record</h3>
<p>To save even more time, booxi now provides you the ability to add an appointment directly from a client record.<br />
To do so, simply click the <img style="font-weight: normal;color: #000000" src="https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/jzvxdQ-SNzvSKK0-a-YXgHov41HH7alNPrtToQ5GDAIeMtXC8LvhJp_SQ2pLZqrgZG8htKkJ58HNuC3h9cJdFjdmsKaqyljM2XnORr1xzqWLuqNWixIZSGKj0vAjYFMu239dUJzF" alt="" width="37" height="31" /> New appointment button at the top right of the Client Summary.</p>
<p><img class="shadow_medium aligncenter" src="https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/LbdzbgSeogo_MB4IHN9m2935qj6yri7icu0SWkVUzEvcH43b4Hj-3braM0qcGSsrdqml_yTPD5jcrKGwcCcglmdPXo1FeHc2ilwc7CfcRNV5rZjNJVNzVIeTjVIQVpDvcWR8rUsM" alt="add an appointment from client file" width="1203" height="470" /></p>
<h3>Automatically Send a Thank You Message After an Appointment</h3>
<p>This new feature allows you to automatically send thank you emails to your clients once their appointment is completed.</p>
<p>Complete the following steps :</p>
<ol>
<li>Click on the My Business section from the main menu on the left, then on the sub-section Appointment Rules.</li>
<li>Scroll down to Enable automated thank you message and activate the option. Click Save to keep your changes.</li>
</ol>
<p><img class="shadow_medium aligncenter" src="https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/_JXgk45DFUYe-w609aApF-f5JggVLATatj2OEfGYBu-XD8Uz73WE--aQpD5Lp-TIXLdrb_uhr3Xxb7uko5pvLNDlrRTwL2iObzZOVF6682sBdSya_Q35h2j3dK2AvOmUFQ9F5rRJ" alt="enable thank you message" width="581" height="124" /></p>
<p>The messages will be sent in the preferred language of the client, as soon as the appointment is completed. A small attention that greatly improves your customer experience.</p>
<p><img class="shadow_medium aligncenter" src="https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/9b4GnLL8DllR_XkYTvG5PFEdzKwtr-0ofzpkrlM18xH3evrtJZw_xLVfY0fzWgXdjflrKr_C5sxIajylKn1z41xuWbQcjaLD6-sYCLMZXHen-jcgN_xDX9ONW30IKHxWEPUKFx_8" alt="thank you message " width="388" height="385" /></p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.booxi.com/blog/export-your-clients-list-referral-data/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>