<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>booxi &#187; customer retention</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.booxi.com/blog/tag/customer-retention/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.booxi.com/blog</link>
	<description>booxi</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2017 18:59:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
		<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
		<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>http://wordpress.org/?v=3.9.1</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Increase Your Customer Retention With Automated Appointment Recall Reminders</title>
		<link>https://www.booxi.com/blog/automated-appointment-recall-reminder/</link>
		<comments>https://www.booxi.com/blog/automated-appointment-recall-reminder/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2017 21:11:04 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Astrid Bertout]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[customer retention]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[online booking]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.booxi.com/blog/?p=1416</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Build repeat business with automated rebooking reminders. An efficient way to boost your customer retention. ]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img class="float_top aligncenter wp-image-1568 size-full" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/7QdBPh1WkLbGHc8JE3HzLF9U3PjwoO4XHaF1mfB8iK-hr5mLerl6ckWn4li7ZQOPwYLxNGMqFBK3d_kDQlWvpw=s0" alt="appointment recall reminder" width="1200" height="600" /></p>
<p>You can now easily schedule automated message to remind your customers to book a new appointment with you, in due time. Since calling every customers is not a viable option, most service providers suffer the lost. Which is why booxi can do it all for you and simplify things even more.</p>
<ul>
<li>Enable Appointment Recall in booxi</li>
<li>Schedule Recall Reminders in One Click</li>
<li>Book A Next Appointment While the Customer is There</li>
<li>Automate Everything</li>
</ul>
<p><b>Enable Appointment Recall<br />
</b>You can easily enable the Appointment Recall feature from your Business Appointment Rules. You can set a default delay, for example 20 days, if you would like booxi to send your customer an email reminder in 20 days, for most of your appointments. You will be able to change this delay for every appointment recall reminders.</p>
<p><img class="shadow_small aligncenter wp-image-1453 size-full" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/tPFOrVrXsuJlz_jwMz1df0pceIWcukzdjG3nwhdNQ4fCegOtHlmJ7KvP3jGFADchiMgyVv88GWnQHe3TZGQzpA=s0" alt="appointment recall " width="586" height="298" /></p>
<p><b>Schedule Recall Reminders in One Click<br />
</b>Once you have enabled Appointment Recall, you will be able to set an automated reminder for your customer, whenever you complete an appointment. Simply click on Complete and you’re done, disable the reminder or adjust the reminder settings prior to completing the appointment. Since recall reminders are sent via email, if the customer did not provide an email address, you will be able to add one at this time.</p>
<p><img class="aligncenter wp-image-1566 size-full" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/E877n1Qf9rZGyOEimN-fDKlvbW9Ugqco288Vkvi5hc3Zwd_3XUJuCuMkItk-0f_U1T4vC3Rq2JRDuym_KH0Y=s0" alt="complete this appointment" width="935" height="770" /></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<ol>
<li>Right-Click on the appointment and select Complete. The Complete confirmation popup will be displayed, providing you more options.</li>
<li>You can choose to schedule a recall reminder, complete without reminder, or Book the next appointment now. Choose to Schedule a recall reminder.</li>
<li>Select the service to propose, which is by default set to the same service as the appointment you are about to complete.</li>
<li>Select the personnel to propose, which is by default also set to the same personnel as the appointment you are about to complete.</li>
<li>Adjust the delay, or a specify a date on which the reminder will be sent.</li>
<li>You may also add an additional message, or simply leave it blank.</li>
<li>Finally, click on Complete and the appointment recall reminder will be scheduled and automatically sent in due time.</li>
<li>If you choose to Complete without reminder, or Book the next appointment now, no recall reminder will be scheduled.</li>
</ol>
<p>If you or your client book a new appointment for the same service and client before the automated recall reminder is sent, that reminder will be automatically cancelled, avoiding any confusion for your customer.</p>
<p>You can cancel or change the appointment recall reminder by reopening the appointment, and complete it again. Whenever a completed appointment is reopen, the associated scheduled appointment recall reminder is automatically cancelled.</p>
<p><b>Book A Next Appointment While the Customer is There<br />
</b>You can now book a next appointment faster, while your customer is still at your store. When you complete an appointment, you can now choose to Book the next appointment now. It creates a new appointment identical to the current one, and you simply set a different date and time.</p>
<ol>
<li>Right-Click on the appointment and select Complete.</li>
<li>Choose Book the next appointment now in the confirmation dialog.</li>
<li>Click on Complete at the bottom of the dialog, and a new copy of the appointment will open on the right.</li>
<li>Simply change the appointment date and time, and click on Save.</li>
</ol>
<p><b>Automate Everything<br />
</b>You can save even more time by putting your appointment on auto complete. If you set the Complete Appointment Business Appointment Rule to automatic and adjust the delay, appointments will be automatically completed past that delay after the appointment. When completed, the appointment recall reminder will also automatically be scheduled using the default delay and for clients with an email adresse.</p>
<ul>
<li>Make sure the Appointment Recall feature is on with a delay that suits most of your services.</li>
<li>Turn the Complete Appointment feature on, and adjust the delay.</li>
<li>Both features can be found in your Business Appointment Rules.<img class="shadow_small aligncenter wp-image-1455 size-full" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/yrftYJtQW8VrYMO1FKGIwrPJB69lhc9wEo-dEW8Pv5EUZB8SS0vWsAV8xTElG6h-HZr-rPNXeCcE8itZpMXvqA=s0" alt="complete appointment" width="584" height="296" /></li>
</ul>
<p>Booking a next appointment, or sending a reminder to book again to your customer will contribute greatly in increasing your customer retention, and help you improve your revenues.</p>
<p style="text-align: center"><strong><br />
Boost your customer retention by using booxi<br />
</strong><br />
<a href="https://www.booxi.com/business/signup" class="creativ-shortcode creativ-shortcode-button creativ-shortcode-button-colour-allgreen creativ-shortcode-button-size-medium creativ-shortcode-button-edge-rounded" target="_blank">Get Started </a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.booxi.com/blog/automated-appointment-recall-reminder/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>5 Easy Ways to Gain Customer Trust &#8211; Overcoming the Stigma of the Beauty Industry</title>
		<link>https://www.booxi.com/blog/gain-customer-trust/</link>
		<comments>https://www.booxi.com/blog/gain-customer-trust/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2017 19:18:15 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[booxi team​]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Business Tips]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[customer retention]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[user experience]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.booxi.com/blog/?p=1445</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[This article provides beauty salon owners with 5 easy (and actionable) ways on how to present their business as a modern and reliable establishment. ]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img class="float_top aligncenter wp-image-1481 size-full" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/MTwsWMqTEEss7OBeZeMMtLe3LCghFmQYBgw5uukFzqWQo2zvHDsOLJcJfoepnzIaH3wMn0yjNYxIAqzBJOD81fs=s0" alt="trusted beauty salon " width="1200" height="600" />Great customer service and professionalism should be the first things that pop into your head when reading the title.<br />
Beyond that, there are some aspects that aren’t so obvious to everyone. When it comes to their personal appearance, customers want the best they can get and many are reluctant to venture toward new beauty salons in fear of having a disappointing, or worse, an unprofessional experience.</p>
<p>This article provides beauty salon owners with 5 easy (and actionable) ways on how to present their business as a modern and reliable establishment. From working with an efficiency-boosting <a href="https://www.lightspeedhq.com/">POS</a> system and <a href="https://www.booxi.com/en">automated appointment management system</a> to paying close attention to the details of their salon’s physical and online aesthetic, beauty shop owners will access insightful suggestions to improve (or maintain) their image and gain new loyal customers.</p>
<p><strong>1. Offer personal suggestions</strong></p>
<p>Although customers expect your professional advice, they appreciate hearing about your personal experience with the products or services you’re selling. After all, everyone is different and sometimes practical feedback (as opposed to theoretical or technical) can be a little more relevant and relatable. Taking an interest in your client and connecting with them on a personal level shows them you care and you’re gathering the information you need to give them the best advice possible.</p>
<p>On the other hand, this also means you can’t shy away from giving your customer bad news; it’s ok if you’re unable to provide them with every solution in the book. There may come a time where you’ll need to point out that your product or company may not be the right fit for their needs. They’ll appreciate the honesty and you’ll be remembered as the one who gives real advice.</p>
<p>According to <a href="https://www.lightspeedhq.com/blog/2017/09/4-ecommerce-takeaways-lightspeed-speaker-series/">Simon Tooley</a>, Founder &amp; CEO at Maison Etiket, “if someone has that memorable experience, it&#8217;s not about the product they bought, it&#8217;s actually about [the] people they interacted with.” We couldn’t agree more.</p>
<p><strong>2. Listen<br />
</strong></p>
<p>Ever walked into a retail store with sales clerks selling on commission and get pestered about all kinds of products you’re just not interested in? Of course you have &#8211; and chances are you didn’t buy any of those items.</p>
<p>Learn from their mistakes; stick to what your customer is telling you and don’t push unrelated products on them. You won’t sell more and, in fact, you risk losing the entire sale over it. Your expert advice may have convinced a customer to purchase an item or service, but if you sound too eager to increase their basket size, your credibility is undermined and the first thing you sold them on may now be in jeopardy. Are you actually giving good advice or are you simply trying to make a quick sale and saying whatever it is you think they want to hear?</p>
<p>By keeping an open mind, customers will sense that you&#8217;ve got their best interests at heart and be much more receptive and trusting of your professional advice.</p>
<p><img class="aligncenter wp-image-1480 size-large" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/88Z8fCTVjTUCvgHAYvJedsBkGUCPPzdNOpwQKjdvygkSWSa7o8JJodXkwa_nX8nZJlTNMGaCzdsORSmEcP_I=s1024" alt="listen your customers" width="1024" height="1024" /></p>
<p><strong>3. Unleash your psychic skills</strong></p>
<p>This one applies to businesses who’ve cultivated their relationships with customers (which should be all of them!), who are knowledgeable of their offering and have their answers ready.</p>
<p>Chances are, most of your customers ask similar questions and those conversations often lead to the same solutions. Pay attention to what they’re saying, detect patterns in their purchasing behavior and needs, ask the right questions and predict what their next concern might be, addressing it with an easy solution before they even bring it up. Often, they won’t even know about this solution, which makes it your job to find it for them, “Ask them the questions to get to why they truly come.</p>
<p>Sometimes you have to dig a little”, explains Simon Tooley. They’ll appreciate the thorough service and feel like they’re in good hands. For example, a client inquires about one of your services they’d like to try for the first time but they seem unconvinced of its value.</p>
<p>Instead of just providing them with the straight-forward answer, read between the lines, tell them about an upcoming discount on the service they should wait for and take advantage of.</p>
<p><strong>4. Display positive reviews from other clients</strong></p>
<p>Your customers are walking, talking, “free” adverts for your business &#8211; keep this in mind at all times and only make promises you can keep. A good way to ensure that is to enforce a “under promise, over deliver” rule.</p>
<p>As you may already know, freebies and surprises tend to make customers really happy and getting them to recommend you is one of the best things you can do for your business. Naturally, people are much more inclined to try and trust a business who already has the seal of approval from someone they know and trust. To make referrals happen, <a href="https://www.lightspeedhq.com/blog/2016/06/10-ways-get-feedback-online-customers/">put systems and incentives in place</a>. This can be something as simple as offering a small discount for every new client they bring in. Not only can this boost business, it’s also a great way to see how customers view your business and where to make adjustments.</p>
<p><strong>5. Respond to crisis quickly</strong></p>
<p>In the event of a crisis &#8211; an unhappy customer claiming he or she was misinformed, for example &#8211; don’t sit on your hands and hope the problem goes away (it never does).</p>
<p><a href="https://www.lightspeedhq.com/blog/2016/12/how-to-respond-to-negative-reviews/">Be decisive and respond quickly</a> to show your customers you can be trusted. Remain objective and professional because a lot can be told about a business in the way they handle and remedy a tough situation. A customer’s journey has 3 parts: before, during and after, and it’s important not to neglect the last one as it holds all the power to make or break that customer’s overall experience and lasting perception.</p>
<p>Your product or service must be desirable with clear added value; however, without the customer&#8217;s trust, they&#8217;ll probably buy from someone else. Somebody they trust.</p>
<div class="creativ-shortcode creativ-shortcode-alertbox creativ-shortcode-alertbox-colour-border"><p class="creativ-shortcode creativ-shortcode-alertbox-content"><br />
Athena Kyriacou a.k.a. Tina, is a Content Specialist at Lightspeed POS, based in Montreal, Qc. She describes creating content as “being in her happy place”. After work hours you can find her spending time with her dog, editing videos for her youtube channel, advocating gender equality and then with her dog some more.</p></div>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.booxi.com/blog/gain-customer-trust/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Create an effective satisfaction survey in 7 simple steps</title>
		<link>https://www.booxi.com/blog/create-an-effective-satisfaction-survey-in-7-simple-steps/</link>
		<comments>https://www.booxi.com/blog/create-an-effective-satisfaction-survey-in-7-simple-steps/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2017 16:02:02 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Astrid Bertout]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Business Tips]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Customer Acquisition]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[customer retention]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.booxi.com/blog/?p=1299</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Keeping customers happy is crucial to ensuring customer retention. It also helps greatly with new customer acquisition. Find out our best practice guide to create a relevant satisfaction survey and get a very accurate feedback. ]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img class="float_top aligncenter wp-image-1357 size-full" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/aCpigFxVn3sqZEIeHsUWzWrd-U-qYaikKK5ZLwtM5o-w85KBznS6MQtPf9kLuTDEp2Yc0OX7eLDangMr3CTS=s0" alt="create your own survey" width="1200" height="600" />Did you know that <a href="http://www.trackur.com/96-of-unhappy-customers-wont-complain-to-you-but-will-tell-15-friends-infographic" target="_blank">96% of unhappy customers</a> won’t complain and 91% of them will simply never return?</p>
<p>Given this, it’s easy to understand that you need to:</p>
<p>1- Ensure that your customers are happy with the services you offer as well as the overall customer experience you provide.</p>
<p>2- Send a survey on a regular basis to measure their satisfaction and see if there’s anything you need to improve upon.</p>
<p>Customer satisfaction is the key to your success: not only does it ensure customer loyalty, but it also helps attract new customers thanks to positive word-of-mouth.</p>
<p>Getting customer feedback regarding all the steps of your customer journey is therefore essential.</p>
<p style="text-align: center">In this guide, you’ll learn how to create a satisfaction survey with ease.</p>
<p><img class="img_zoom aligncenter wp-image-1300 size-full" src="https://booxi-live-wp-storage.storage.googleapis.com/form-animation.gif" alt="create your form" width="360" height="363" />Source : <a href="https://gsuite.google.com/learning-center/products/forms/get-started/" target="_blank">Google Inc</a></p>
<p>1. Determine all the steps throughout your customer journey, from initial contact to rebooking.<br />
Here’s an example of a customer journey:</p>
<p><strong>→ Before the appointment</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Find all the necessary information about the business quickly and easily</li>
<li>Contact the business quickly and easily.</li>
<li>Book an appointment quickly and easily.</li>
<li>Receive an appointment reminder.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>→ During the appointment</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Receive a warm welcome.</li>
<li>Receive excellent service.</li>
<li>Be listened to and receive assistance</li>
<li>Have a positive experience during payment.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong> → After the appointment</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Be able to book the next appointment quickly and easily.</li>
<li>Have incentive to return. For example, through a loyalty program.</li>
<li>Enjoy a personalized customer experience.</li>
</ul>
<p>2. For each of the steps you identify, make sure to ask your customers relevant questions.</p>
<p>Here’s an example for the first step in the “Before the appointment” section:</p>
<p><em>- How did you hear about our business?</em><br />
<em> Through Facebook</em><br />
<em> Through a friend</em><br />
<em> Through Instagram</em><br />
<em> By doing online research</em><br />
<em> While passing by</em></p>
<p><strong>Tip: </strong>After the questions,make sure to leave some space so customers can give their opinions, feedback and recommendations. They might bring up a point you didn’t think about.</p>
<p>3. Creating the survey</p>
<p>Once you’ve determined all your questions, you can start to build the survey. There are</p>
<p>many platforms that’ll help you do it for free. For example, you can use Google Forms.</p>
<p>*Here’s <a href="https://gsuite.google.com/learning-center/products/forms/get-started/" target="_blank">all the information you’ll need</a> to create your Google Forms account. From there, you’ll quickly learn how to create your first survey.<br />
<br />
<strong>Tip #1</strong> &#8211; At the end of the survey, make sure to add a section to thank your customers for taking the time to answer your questions.<br />
<br />
<strong>Tip #2</strong> &#8211; Estimate the time needed to complete the form and make sure to mark it clearly. This way, your clients will see their progress as they answer the questions. In general, try to be as concise as possible, and avoid creating a form that takes more than 5 minutes to complete.</p>
<p>You can even add a progress bar to encourage them.</p>
<p><a href="https://gsuite.google.com/learning-center/products/forms/get-started/"><img class="shadow_medium aligncenter wp-image-1301 size-full" src="https://booxi-live-wp-storage.storage.googleapis.com/progress-bar.jpg" alt="progress bar" width="324" height="73" /></a></p>
<p>4. Send out your survey</p>
<p>Once your survey is ready, send it out to get as many answers as possible, in order to get as much useful information as possible.</p>
<p>Send it out on all your communication channels:</p>
<ul>
<li>Create a post on your Facebook page, and on every other social network that you use for business. Don’t forget to mention how long it’ll take to complete the survey.</li>
<li>If you have a client list, send the survey by email. They’ll be able to fill it out when they have some time.
<p><strong>Tip #1</strong> – Personalize the email subject header in order to increase the chances that your customers willopen it and complete the survey. It’s an effective strategy to increase your open rate.<em>Here’s an example:<br />
</em><em>[Fname], your opinion matters to me!</em></p>
<p><strong>Tip #2 </strong>– Don’t forget to explain why they’re receiving the email.For example, it can be: “Thanks for visiting us. In order to offer you the best experience possible, we would like to ask you some questions.”</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li>You can even send them the link by text message at the end of their appointment. Between 92 and 98% of all texts are read, making it the media with the highest open rate. In comparison, emails are only read 22% of the time.</li>
</ul>
<p>5. Analyze the answers</p>
<p>Once you start to receive answers, take time to analyze them. Determine your strengths as well as the steps during the customer journey that need to be improved.</p>
<p>Don’t forget to take into account all the additional suggestions and comments made by your customers.</p>
<p>It’s also important to identify how many times the same point is brought up by different customers. This will let you know what to focus on first.</p>
<p>6. Build for the future:</p>
<p>Based on the answers you receive and your analysis of them, prioritize future actions in order to improve your customer experience.</p>
<p><em>For example:</em></p>
<p>If the main issue raised by your customers is that it’s hard to find your business online, focus your efforts on promoting your business and building an online visibility strategy.</p>
<p>If their main frustration is that it takes a lot of time to book an appointment, why not offer online appointment booking to your customers?</p>
<p>And so on.</p>
<p>Then, for all the changes you need to make in order to improve customer satisfaction, establish deadlines and respect them.</p>
<p>7. Finally, send out your satisfaction survey regularly.</p>
<ul>
<li>This will help you monitor your improvements and see if they’ve had a positive impact on customer satisfaction.</li>
<li>Because customers’ expectations can quickly change, you need to make sure you meet them all the time.</li>
</ul>
<p>You now have all the information you need to create an effective satisfaction survey, and to implement changes that will help you offer a standout customer experience.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.booxi.com/blog/create-an-effective-satisfaction-survey-in-7-simple-steps/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to turn new customers into repeat customers?</title>
		<link>https://www.booxi.com/blog/turn-new-customers-into-repeat-customers/</link>
		<comments>https://www.booxi.com/blog/turn-new-customers-into-repeat-customers/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2017 19:24:48 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Astrid Bertout]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Business Tips]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[customer retention]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[loyalty program]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.booxi.com/blog/?p=1126</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Making sure that new customers become regular customers is an effective strategy that will have a positive impact on your bottom line. Here are 4 strategies to convert your visitors into loyal customers.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/larrymyler/2016/06/08/acquiring-new-customers-is-important-but-retaining-them-accelerates-profitable-growth/#1df6387a6671%20" target="_blank"><img class="float_top aligncenter wp-image-1131 size-full" src="https://booxi-live-wp-storage.storage.googleapis.com/product-recommendation.png" alt="customer experience" width="1200" height="600" /><br />
60-80% of customers</a> who describe themselves as satisfied do not go back to do more business with the company that initially satisfied them1.</p>
<p>Why does this happen? Simple. Too often, no solid relationship is established between the business and the customer. And with all the options available on the market, if no real connection is made, customers will try other businesses.</p>
<p>However, here are four strategies you can quickly implement to establish a lasting relationship with your customers, thus ensuring that they become regulars &#8211; which in turn will have a positive impact on your bottom line.</p>
<ul>
<li>
<h3>Provide a great experience and make sure your customers are satisfied</h3>
</li>
</ul>
<p>This may seem obvious, but it’s the first step to converting a new customer into a regular customer.</p>
<p>If customers are disappointed with their first visit, they’ll never come back to see you. So make sure to pamper them from the get-go. Spend a few minutes at the beginning of the appointment to ask them some questions and understand exactly what their needs are.</p>
<p><span style="text-decoration: underline">Work with the right tools</span></p>
<p>During their first visit, a client will appreciate it if you ask them a few questions. It shows that you’re interested in them and that you’re taking the time to get to know them. And from a business standpoint, it’s important to know what their expectations are, which of your services they may be interested in, and how they heard about your business in the first place.</p>
<p>All of these questions are important to ask during the first appointment as they help establish initial contact and form the basis of a relationship.</p>
<p>But if you ask the same questions during their second visit, you’ll risk frustrating them. Everything will have a familiar ring to it, and they’ll interpret your questions as a way of making conversation as opposed to genuine interest on your part.</p>
<p>If you don’t want to take any risks, use CRM (a tool that helps you manage customer relationships) and make sure to jot down the information you received.</p>
<p>During their next visit, a quick glance at your notes will help you remember your previous conversation with them &#8211; even the smallest details.</p>
<p>The customer will be flattered and impressed by the great customer experience you offer. By making them feel that they’re not just a number, you’ll establish a trusting relationship.</p>
<ul>
<li>
<h3>Add online appointment booking</h3>
</li>
</ul>
<p>Did you know that 35% of clients try to book their appointments outside of opening hours and that 25% of people under the age of 35 only book appointments online?</p>
<p><a href="https://www.booxi.com/blog/testimonial-esthetique-isa-belle/" target="_blank">People are trying to simplify their lives</a>. If you help them save time, they’ll appreciate it and come back to see you.</p>
<p>By adding a “Book Now” button directly <a href="https://www.booxi.com/blog/add-online-booking-to-facebook/" target="_blank">on your Facebook page</a> or your website, you’ll make it easier for visitors and give them a good reason to keep doing business with you.</p>
<p>So make sure you offer online appointment booking. Not only will it keep you competitive, but it&#8217;s also a very effective way to start collecting customer email addresses.</p>
<p><img class="img_zoom aligncenter size-full wp-image-779" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/oNOI6q05eem6KgtCexIW-j9pOA5a35DbYRegSeVo0aoZvlz1GB0462BPKHlIzWdxuqLTUA9FZaPKt-221BrLLA=s0" alt="get customers to book online" /></p>
<ul>
<li>
<h3>Build a list of clients and communicate with them regularly</h3>
</li>
</ul>
<p>Be sure to build a client database that includes their email addresses. Then make sure to send them promotions or information about your business on a regular basis. If you stay top of mind with your customers, they’re more likely to book their next appointment with you rather than with the competition.</p>
<p>Here are a few kinds of messages you can send to customers to start building a lasting relationship with them:</p>
<p>After their visit, send them a message to thank them for booking an appointment with you. You can also take the opportunity to ask them how their experience went.</p>
<p>One month later you can send them a message to remind them to book an appointment. This message will have even more impact if you tell them about a promotion at the same time.</p>
<p>In addition, thanks to your customer database you’ll be able to <a href="https://www.facebook.com/business/help/170456843145568" target="_blank">target them directly with Facebook ads</a>. For example one month or two later, use Local Awareness Ads from Facebook to target them with promotion : they should book an appointment shortly.</p>
<ul>
<li>
<h3>Set up a loyalty program and give people incentive to become regular customers</h3>
</li>
</ul>
<p><a href="http://info.bondbrandloyalty.com/2016-loyalty-report" target="_blank">81% of consumers</a> are more likely to continue doing business with brands that offer loyalty programs.</p>
<p>There are many options available to you. One of the most effective methods is to set up a point accumulation system that allows customers to receive special promotions or obtain rewards.</p>
<p>For example:<br />
Every dollar spent is worth one point.<br />
Every new appointment you book directly at the end of the current appointment is worth 150 points.<br />
When a customer refers a friend, they’ll get 2000 points.</p>
<p>Once a customer reaches 5000 points, offer them a discount on a product or service.</p>
<p>You can also offer a free service after the 10th appointment.</p>
<p><span style="text-decoration: underline">Here’s a helpful hint:</span><br />
Make sure you only reward your regular customers by adding a few conditions.<br />
For example, you can decide that after one year of inactivity, any points that have been accumulated will be lost.</p>
<p>To make sure that as many customers as possible want to be a part of your program, offer them even greater benefits.</p>
<p>This could include birthday discounts, invitations to private sales, or invitations to events that feature an expert in your field or an influential blogger.</p>
<p>If you want to make sure that you’re offering benefits that your customers actually want, ask them what their expectations are, and what it is that brings them back to your business on a regular basis.</p>
<p><img class="img_zoom aligncenter size-full wp-image-1127" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/yoCIdjstmxCOb_BvQwsN34dzScP3BQ88RcYUVMQv6hiVuOAFzRleppXV9aZ36tHThDAQi0ba7qrgxQpT0NW_iw0=s0" alt="loyalty program" /></p>
<p>To conclude, if you want to turn new customers into regulars, you need to make them feel important, and you need to a build a trusting relationship with them over the long term.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.booxi.com/blog/turn-new-customers-into-repeat-customers/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>7 Marketing Ideas to Get the Most Out of Valentine&#8217;s Day</title>
		<link>https://www.booxi.com/blog/7-marketing-ideas-to-get-the-most-out-of-valentines-day/</link>
		<comments>https://www.booxi.com/blog/7-marketing-ideas-to-get-the-most-out-of-valentines-day/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2017 21:22:33 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Astrid Bertout]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Business Tips]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[customer retention]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social network]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.booxi.com/blog/?p=908</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Seasonal events are good opportunities to establish strategies that will allow you to build your customer loyalty, get more customers, and increase sales. As Valentine's Day approaches, here are 7 promotion ideas to get the most out of this day.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img class="float_top aligncenter wp-image-911 size-full" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/dyb43YUGuykueGPLzASV4auOsouV37Nt3XVtHPizm4Z1FhFI3QnLlKEvBOvfxL-P66Yt0Csyz7vSVemG2A2Eqw=s0" alt="heart for Valentine Day" width="1200" height="600" /></p>
<p>Seasonal events are good opportunities to establish strategies that will allow you to build your customer loyalty, get more customers, and increase sales. As Valentine&#8217;s Day approaches, here are 7 promotion ideas to get the most out of this day.</p>
<ol>
<li>
<h2>Spread the Love</h2>
<p><a href="https://www.booxi.com/blog/get-the-most-out-of-your-client-list/" target="_blank">Easily export your customer list to import it into your free mailing solution</a>, such as <a href="https://mailchimp.com/" target="_blank">Mailchimp</a>, and surprise your customers.</p>
<p>♥ For example, you can send gift suggestions “For Him” or “For Her”, with products and services that you offer.<br />
♥ You can also send a coupon for a limited period of time (until february 14th), and with specific conditions to encourage your customers to use it during less busy hours.<br />
♥ Take advantage of this to remind your customers that Valentine’s week is very busy, so that they can book an appointment online to be sure to reserve their place.</li>
<li>
<h2>Get More Customers</h2>
<p>Invite your customers to refer their friends using invitation cards. For example the referred friend will enjoy a discount on his first appointment booked, while the customer who made that reference will receive a product or a sample as a reward. It’s a great time to create new businesses opportunities.</li>
<li>
<h2>Create Promotions to Increase Your Product&#8217;s Sales</h2>
<p>Since margins on products are higher than on services, you should take advantage of Valentine’s day to offer product combinations and increase your sales.</p>
<p>♥ For example you can offer a package with two products of the same line for a special price.<br />
♥ On the purchase of selected products, you can offer a second one at half-price.<br />
♥ If your customers can buy your products online, offer a free shipping or give them a specific promocode for Valentine’s Day.</p>
<p><img class="img_zoom aligncenter size-full wp-image-913" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/uegIf-OvJEsW7fMpPnyGgFMju_4FG2sOCmx6rpqO_5ZD1ccdAdlF4pPBXcLAiEsa3po5tiQzjqKZdO3-r16q1IU=s0" alt="Promotion for Valentine Day" /></li>
<li>
<h2>Highlight One of Your Partner</h2>
<p>You can take advantage of this day to establish joint strategies with one of your partner; a good way to take advantage of each other&#8217;s notoriety.<br />
It can be a product combination with your partner, or a promotion on a service offered by your partner for each visit to your shop during Valentine’s Day week and vice versa.<br />
You don’t have any partner yet? Create one! You could as example contact one of the local flower shops and offer a partnership for this occasion!</li>
<li>
<h2>Make Promotion on Your Social Networks</h2>
<p>Make the most out of Valentine’s Day by regularly publishing on your social networks and creating interaction on your pages.</p>
<p>♥ Share gift suggestions using products and services you offer.<br />
♥ Start a contest with little effort and in a few minutes. For example, you can ask your customers to comment on your publication with the name of a person with whom they would like to enjoy one of your services. Then make a draw where both names drawn will win a free appointment.</p>
<p><img class="img_zoom aligncenter size-full wp-image-912" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/AX9CYO5kC2DuLh2L5tHtCKm7K1b93sQopcOX9Eu0s31SGGjO02P4a56mINcy8tLDC84-cESt5ZZGQNWSpfVx=s0" alt="promotion for couple" /></p>
<p>♥ Make sure to share your current promotions on your social networks to optimize their impact.<br />
♥ You can also announce that there will be some surprise in your store on February 14th, or even for the entire week.</li>
<li>
<h2>Rewards Your Best Customers</h2>
<p>Valentine&#8217;s Day can be an opportunity to increase customer loyalty. If you have a small budget for this specific day you can spoil your customers during their visit on February 14th:</p>
<p>♥ Offer them chocolates, samples or discounts on their next appointment (make sure to keep a note not forget it).Use a tool that allows you to track appointments history and keep notes per customer.<br />
♥ Want to go even further? Send flowers to your three best customers! The positive word of mouth that this will generate is well worth it!</li>
<li>
<h2>Create an atmosphere in your store</h2>
<p>Make a romantic playlist using <a href="https://www.youtube.com/?hl=en&amp;gl=CA" target="_blank">Youtube</a> or <a href="http://8tracks.com/" target="_blank">8Tracks</a> for example and search words like “Love”. Add candles and chocolates on your counter, and at the end of an appointment offer a few samples… There are a lot of special attentions that you can offer during this day! It&#8217;s up to you to find the ones that suit you best.</li>
</ol>
<p>In most of our tips the visual you add to your message is crucial. Take a look at these 6 tools to find the perfect images.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.booxi.com/blog/7-marketing-ideas-to-get-the-most-out-of-valentines-day/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>How do successful small businesses retain their clients?</title>
		<link>https://www.booxi.com/blog/customer-retention/</link>
		<comments>https://www.booxi.com/blog/customer-retention/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 Aug 2016 18:53:14 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Astrid Bertout]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Business Tips]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[appointment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[customer retention]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[user experience]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.booxi.com/blog-dev/?p=155</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[48% of small-business owners worldwide said their customers drove their success however few businesses have real strategies to build strong relationship with their existing clients. Find out our best strategies to increase your customer satisfaction and build your customer loyalty. ]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img class="float_top shadow_large aligncenter wp-image-156" src="http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/JHPV6H7630XdPkT6aGGbYt4dbNOeCKLImj9rhG4hRqb7P49-i18E3Nvyp_2SQR6yXKK8HAX__SnumvA7zN1ltQ=s0" alt="loyal customer" width="750" height="490" /><br />
<a href="https://www.emarketer.com/Article/How-Small-Businesses-Get-Keep-Clients/1012460" target="_blank">48% of small-business owners worldwide said their customers drove their success,</a> however few businesses have real strategies to build strong relationship with their existing clients. Here are the best tips to increase customer satisfaction and build your customer loyalty.</p>
<h3>1 &#8211; Ask for Feedback</h3>
<p>Regularly ask your customers to provide feedback. They love that you care about what they think, and a customer that feel listened will communicate a positive message about your business to his surrounding.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>This feedback can also help you save an unsatisfied customer, who would probably not have expressed himself directly to you, and would have never come back. In fact from 1000 unsatisfied customers, only 40 will tell you, while 600 will go somewhere else next time*.</p>
<p>If a complaint is immediately and effectively managed, and a solution is provided; chances are that this unsatisfied customer will become a regular customer, and sometimes even an ambassador for your business.</p>
<p><img class="aligncenter wp-image-849 size-full" src="https://booxi-live-wp-storage.storage.googleapis.com/online-reviews.jpg" alt="online reviews" width="750" height="500" /></p>
<p><span class="bx_text14" style="color: #ffffff;background-color: #44ce5e;padding: 2px 8px"><strong>TIPS</strong></span></p>
<ul>
<li>Send an automated thank you message, with a link to leave a comment.</li>
<li>When a comment is posted online, make sure to answer quickly, to present your apologies, and ask to be called to manage this situation. Do not try to solve the problem publicly.</li>
</ul>
<h3>2 &#8211; Help Your Customers Remember Their Appointments</h3>
<p><img class="aligncenter wp-image-845 size-full" src="https://booxi-live-wp-storage.storage.googleapis.com/send-sms-reminder.jpg" alt="send-sms-reminder" width="1000" height="667" /></p>
<p>Just like you, customers don’t like having to call to ask for the address or the time of their appointment, because they forgot. And if they have taken their appointment long in advance, it is likely that they forget about it, and miss their appointment.</p>
<p>To avoid any risks, send a confirmation email to your customer after he booked an appointment with you, so he has the address and the time of the appointment handy. Also make it easy for him to add this appointment to his personal calendar using an ICS (Internet Calendar Subscription) attachment to the confirmation email. In the same way, you can send him an SMS reminder a little before the appointment. It improves the customer experience since you reduce the probability that he has to call you because he forgot, or that he misses his appointment.</p>
<p><span class="bx_text14" style="color: #ffffff;background-color: #44ce5e;padding: 2px 8px"><strong>TIPS</strong></span></p>
<ul>
<li>Use an appointment management system to automate your confirmations and reminders and save lots of time.</li>
</ul>
<h3>3 &#8211; Make Sure Your Customers Think About You</h3>
<p>Customers are constantly solicited by other service providers, so the opportunity to forget about you or try a new provider are very present. It is important to remind them you exist, and invite them to book a new appointment with you.</p>
<p>Keep track of their last appointment and send them an email invitation to book their next appointment with you. This personalized message reinforces the relationship, because every customer feels unique.</p>
<p>Use a CRM (software to manage the customer relationship) to track appointments and send these emails with the right timing. This small attention will make a huge difference and will decrease the risks that your customers book with the competition.</p>
<p><span class="bx_text14" style="color: #ffffff;background-color: #44ce5e;padding: 2px 8px"><strong>TIPS</strong></span></p>
<ul>
<li>Use a CRM (Customer Relationship Management) software to simplify all these tasks and automate the appointment tracking for each customer and make sure to send emails with the right timing.</li>
</ul>
<h3>4 - Improve the Customer Experience</h3>
<p>If a customer is satisfied about your services, he is likely to come back. That seems pretty simple, but be careful, other factors can influence this relationship. For example, customers hate to leave voicemails, but love immediate access to information such as your availability. So if you are temporarily unreachable, you take the risk that your customer forget to call back, or worst, book an appointment with the competition.</p>
<p>The best way to avoid this situation, is to take appointment bookings 24/7, which means even outside your open hours. You can accomplish that using an <a href="https://www.booxi.com/features#online-appointment-booking">online appointment booking solution</a> that is affordable and easy to use. Customers love it, and you save lots of time off the phone; besides, it obviously much cheaper than a receptionist.</p>
<p><img class="aligncenter wp-image-851 size-full" src="https://booxi-live-wp-storage.storage.googleapis.com/online-appointment-booking1.png" alt="online-appointment-booking" width="1200" height="600" /></p>
<p><span class="bx_text14" style="color: #ffffff;background-color: #44ce5e;padding: 2px 8px"><strong>TIPS</strong></span></p>
<ul>
<li><a href="https://www.booxi.com/blog/add-online-booking-to-facebook/">Add online appointment booking directly to your Facebook page </a>and your website, as well as in all your online profiles and posts.</li>
</ul>
<h3>5 &#8211; Reward your Best Customers</h3>
<p>The more customers are loyal, the more they talk about you, and the more they bring new customers your way. Give them a special attention after their appointment, or periodically. For example: send them a thank you message after their appointment; give them exclusive and limited promotions such as a 10% discount for both, when they bring a friend; or give a gift card to your top 10 customers. They will be so proud that they’ll speak about it and make good publicity for your business.</p>
<p><span class="bx_text14" style="color: #ffffff;background-color: #44ce5e;padding: 2px 8px"><strong>TIPS</strong></span></p>
<ul>
<li>Use a CRM or an appointment management solution to <a href="https://www.booxi.com/features#client_profiles">build better relationships with your clients</a> by automatically sending thank you messages, running reports to identify your best customers, and preparing mail campaign to send exclusive promotions.</li>
</ul>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h3>Apply All These Tips in Simplicity</h3>
<p>It may look like a lot of effort, but it is not when you use the right tools.<br />
These tasks can be completely automated using a cloud appointment management solution like booxi. It is very easy to use, affordable, and it provides more results with less effort; thus representing a huge return on a little time and money investment.</p>
<hr />
<p style="text-align: left">Get a CRM and build a better relationship with your customers.<br />
Try it right now &#8211; no credit card required.</p>
<p style="text-align: center"><a href="https://www.booxi.com/features#client_profiles" class="creativ-shortcode creativ-shortcode-button creativ-shortcode-button-colour-allgreen creativ-shortcode-button-size-medium creativ-shortcode-button-edge-straight" target="_blank">Read More </a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.booxi.com/blog/customer-retention/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>