<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>booxi &#187; no-show</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.booxi.com/blog/tag/no-show/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.booxi.com/blog</link>
	<description>booxi</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2017 18:59:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
		<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
		<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>http://wordpress.org/?v=3.9.1</generator>
	<item>
		<title>No shows are the worst; they represent both a loss of time and money.</title>
		<link>https://www.booxi.com/blog/no-shows-are-the-worst-they-represent-both-a-loss-of-time-and-money/</link>
		<comments>https://www.booxi.com/blog/no-shows-are-the-worst-they-represent-both-a-loss-of-time-and-money/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 Aug 2016 19:41:13 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Astrid Bertout]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Business Tips]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[no-show]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[reminder]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tips]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.booxi.com/blog-dev/?p=170</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[No shows are a waste of time and money. Here are solutions to avoid them.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img class="float_top shadow_large aligncenter wp-image-171 size-full" src="https://booxi-live-wp-storage.storage.googleapis.com/Hair_Salon_No_Show_EN.png" alt="find solution to avoid no-shows" width="1199" height="600" /></p>
<p>But you can easily prevent them, and this article covers the 3 most efficient ways to avoid no-shows.</p>
<h3>1 &#8211; Charge Cancellation Fees</h3>
<p>Although it may not suit all businesses and it may not be for you, charging a cancellation fee remains the most effective option. But it also requires important efforts on your part, and it may scare clients away. This method has proven to be effective for businesses that have a long waiting list to get an appointment with those.</p>
<p>We are basically talking about asking your client’s credit card via the phone, or via online appointment booking (if you use an appointment management solution). You can request a deposit or a full payment.</p>
<p><span class="bx_text14" style="color: #ffffff;background-color: #44ce5e;padding: 2px 8px"><strong>PROS</strong></span></p>
<p>The customer will show up for sure, and if he does not, you still get paid.</p>
<p><span class="bx_text14" style="color: #ffffff;background-color: #ff7070;padding: 2px 8px"><strong>CONS</strong></span></p>
<p>Not all clients will be comfortable to give your their credit card number over the phone, and many will not book online because a credit card is required.</p>
<p><span class="bx_text14" style="color: #ffffff;background-color: #33bcf2;padding: 2px 8px"><strong>ALTERNATIVE</strong></span></p>
<p>Let them book online, and ask their credit card in the confirmation email; using a secure payment method. Some appointment management solutions supports this. This way you do not have to ask the credit card over the phone, and the client will complete the online booking as no credit card will be asked at this time. If the payment is not completed, at least you know that your client wants an appointment, and you can contact him to complete the transaction. Make sure to make it clear that a prepayment is required.</p>
<h3>2 &#8211; Reminding Your Customers</h3>
<p>If we combine the efficiency with the customer experience factors, reminding your clients is truly the best option. Although if you plan on doing this manually by calling each client, it represents a huge time investment; while there are simple ways to automate this.</p>
<p>Some appointment management solutions automatically send email or SMS reminders a few hours or a day before the appointment; no matter if the appointment was taken online, or by phone. This means you cover almost 100% of your appointments, leaving you with only a few calls to make, or very few no-shows.</p>
<p><span class="bx_text16 bx_text14" style="color: #ffffff;background-color: #44ce5e;padding: 2px 8px"><strong>PROS</strong></span></p>
<p>You have nothing to do, or little efforts; your clients love reminders, and they show up.</p>
<p><span class="bx_text14" style="color: #ffffff;background-color: #ff7070;padding: 2px 8px"><strong>CONS</strong></span></p>
<p>You have to quite using a paper calendar and work more efficiently. Solutions are not free, but some starts at $9 per month which is nothing compare to the hours and hundreds of dollars you lose every month because of no-shows.</p>
<h3>3 &#8211; Follow Up After a No-Show</h3>
<p>You can develop the habit of calling back clients for each no-show, so they have to explain themselves, and feel guilty enough to double their attention next time they have an appointment with you. This method will help prevent some no-shows, but is far from being as efficient as the other two methods.</p>
<p>Some appointment management solutions will send automatically an email to no-show clients reminding them of your cancellation policies, so you do not need to call them.</p>
<p><span class="bx_text16 bx_text14" style="color: #ffffff;background-color: #44ce5e;padding: 2px 8px"><strong>PROS</strong></span></p>
<p>Helps sensitize your clients about no-shows.</p>
<p><span class="bx_text14" style="color: #ffffff;background-color: #ff7070;padding: 2px 8px"><strong>CONS</strong></span></p>
<p>It does not help preventing no-shows.</p>
<hr />
<blockquote><p> Clearly the best solution that fits all businesses is a combination of #2 and #3, which requires you to use an appointment solution.</p></blockquote>
<hr />
<p style="text-align: center">We recommend booxi as it is the easiest solution to use, and one of the most affordable one, plus clients love its online appointment booking.<br />
Try booxi for free during 30 days and delete all your no-shows!</p>
<p style="text-align: center"><a href="https://www.booxi.com/booxi?book=now" class="creativ-shortcode creativ-shortcode-button creativ-shortcode-button-colour-allgreen creativ-shortcode-button-size-medium creativ-shortcode-button-edge-straight" target="_blank">Request Demo</a> <a href="https://www.booxi.com/" class="creativ-shortcode creativ-shortcode-button creativ-shortcode-button-colour-white creativ-shortcode-button-size-medium creativ-shortcode-button-edge-straight" target="_blank">Learn More</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.booxi.com/blog/no-shows-are-the-worst-they-represent-both-a-loss-of-time-and-money/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tired to Spend Most of Your Time on the Phone to Manage Your Appointments?</title>
		<link>https://www.booxi.com/blog/tired-to-spend-most-of-your-time-on-the-phone-to-manage-your-appointments/</link>
		<comments>https://www.booxi.com/blog/tired-to-spend-most-of-your-time-on-the-phone-to-manage-your-appointments/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 Aug 2016 18:34:14 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Astrid Bertout]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Business Tips]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[no-show]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[online booking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[time saving]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.booxi.com/blog-dev/?p=153</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Stop wasting time and focus on what you really like to do : be with your customers.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img class="float_top aligncenter wp-image-781 size-full" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/59sO0o50pVl2u-ry-B7_6tiqhr-sKAIjh0QZA28AM10lrPpJhk8gHqu__QodLsILHHIdaEM1DHmigP8j5xyV75E=s0" alt="woman spending too much time on the phone" width="1200" height="600" /><div class="creativ-shortcode creativ-shortcode-cols  creativ-shortcode-cols-half-half "><div class="creativ-shortcode creativ-shortcode-col creativ-shortcode-col-a"><div class="creativ-shortcode-col-inner"><p>Juggling with appointments, sales, marketing, customer service while managing a business can turn into real headache. Some solutions may actually help you to save a lot of time. Take a management solution for appointment as booxi and see the benefits it offers.</p>
</div></div></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<div class="creativ-shortcode creativ-shortcode-col creativ-shortcode-col-b"><div class="creativ-shortcode-col-inner"></div></div>
<ul>
<li>Gain Efficiency</li>
<li>Reduce No-Shows</li>
<li>Get More Satisfied Customers</li>
<li>Automate your Client List</li>
<li>Get More Online Visibility and More Appointments</div></li>
</ul>
<hr />
<h3>Gain Efficiency</h3>
<p>You’ll save time by spending less time on the phone.<br />
You lose around 6 minutes per phone call to book an appointment, asking for personal information, confirmation of the date, time and so on. Reduce that phone time with booxi. It will manage part of your appointments by encouraging your clients to book online. At least 6 hours saving per month!</p>
<h3>Reduce No-Shows</h3>
<p>For each appointment, booxi sends an automated confirmation with all information at hand for the customer. Customers are less likely to call back to ask about the date or the address. In addition, the platform offers the possibility to send an automated reminder (by email or text message). No-shows will decrease from 13% to less than 2%! Automate your business !</p>
<h3>Get More Satisfied Customers</h3>
<p>Allow your customers to book their appointment when they have time.</p>
<p>20% of customers prefer booking online over talking to someone on the phone, also they can do it when they have time and as soons as they think about it (even when your business is closed). They save time, just as you do. Focus on customer experience!</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h3>Automate Your Client List</h3>
<p>When you use an online booking solution, you collect your customers emails (with their consent). As they book online and you add new appointments, you automatically build up your client list with valuable details. You can also access each customer’s appointment history (and notes for each appointment). It’s a good way to impress them by knowing when was their last visit and the service they received. In addition, thanks to automated recall you can send emails to invite them to book a new appointment, with an impeccable timing.</p>
<h3>Get More Online Visibility and More Appointments</h3>
<p>With solution like booxi for example, you can also add the Book Now button to your website, your Facebook page, and in all your messages (2 sources for new appointments). Finally, add your link on specialized online directory. All roads lead to a new appointment !</p>
<p style="text-align: center"><strong>The solution works for you and you can focus on what you like to do.</strong><br />
<strong>Amazing, this online appointment booking. What could be better ?</strong></p>
<hr class="dash" />
<p style="text-align: center;font-weight: 200"><span class="bx_text24">Try booxi for free</span></p>
<h5 style="text-align: center">14 days &#8211; No credit card required</h5>
<p style="text-align: center"><a href="https://www.booxi.com/business/signup" class="creativ-shortcode creativ-shortcode-button creativ-shortcode-button-colour-allgreen creativ-shortcode-button-size-medium creativ-shortcode-button-edge-straight" target="_blank">Get Started</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.booxi.com/blog/tired-to-spend-most-of-your-time-on-the-phone-to-manage-your-appointments/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>