<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>booxi &#187; time saving</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.booxi.com/blog/tag/time-saving/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.booxi.com/blog</link>
	<description>booxi</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2017 18:59:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
		<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
		<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>http://wordpress.org/?v=3.9.1</generator>
	<item>
		<title>&#8220;No Phone When I am With Customers!&#8221;</title>
		<link>https://www.booxi.com/blog/testimonial-esthetique-isa-belle/</link>
		<comments>https://www.booxi.com/blog/testimonial-esthetique-isa-belle/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2017 21:48:53 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Astrid Bertout]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Testimonials]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Owners]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[time saving]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.booxi.com/blog/?p=1029</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Find out how Isabelle Perrault, self-employed professional and owner of Esthétique Isa-Belle, has saved a lot of time and has increased her clientele since she started using booxi.
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img class="float_top" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/N_AOSkHZovkvY0mKW0Eei80pi9NgnWyY0WC75anS3hn0ceN9-qayvSBindfBiwhaFJBcoeHTXxyAnvD0HsXFkQ=s0" alt="IsabellePerrault_PostImage_Test2" /><br />
Isabelle is a self-employed professional in esthetic and the owner of <a href="https://www.facebook.com/EsthetiqueIsabelle82/">Esthétique Isa-Belle</a>.</p>
<p>5 years ago she was still very attached to her paper agenda. However her husband convinced her that online appointment booking had become a real competitive advantage, and that she needed to simplify the way customers book with her. In addition she was aware of the insane amount of time she spends over the phone to manage her schedule. These arguments brought her to use an appointment booking solution.</p>
<p>Isabelle had evaluated several solutions available on the market and started to use one of them for a while, to only find out about booxi later. When she tried booxi, she was immediately pleased withthe design, the simplicity of using it and by the booking experience it offers to her customers. So she decided to switch to booxi, and in few hours only she was ready to run her business with it.</p>
<p>Ever since, <em><span style="color: #999999">«this change has only been positive»</span></em> for Isabelle.</p>
<h3 style="text-align: center">  <b>90% of her customers book online, a huge timesaving.<br />
</b></h3>
<p><img class="vertitop_right wp-image-1038 aligncenter" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/Dz1mz4MceOZLHc61Bdxr0T6MFWwfUqXr5zRCZtHYmStgTWEUtKz-6fjQJF3FhKO--XjzI49Fw3av6Gq7i2gFdA=s0" alt="online appointment" width="290" height="290" /><br />
Why?</p>
<p style="text-align: center"><em><span style="color: #999999">«Because they can book appointments whenever they want, wherever they are, and it’s easy to do it.»</span></em></p>
<p>Moreover, Isabelle has noticed that most appointments are booked after 9 PM. Some of them are even booked during the night or very early in the morning, while she is closed. Customers no longer need to call during their work hours, and they no longer hit the voicemail.</p>
<p>Appointments are automatically booked and Isabelle has a full schedule while hardly receiving any calls nor getting messages on her voicemail.</p>
<h3 style="text-align: center"><b>A huge decrease in phone calls.<img class="img_zoom aligncenter  wp-image-1037" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/2uf9BAKEO2WhSqSctNTx5apNvrTI-iWsikfqmDDkG52Qb81gpVcGBsDyk8mjshVPNCcZr3plfre4VVL-P_Ip=s0" alt="simplify-appointment-booking" width="465" height="423" /></b></h3>
<p>Isabelle has always carefully respected one important rule:</p>
<p style="text-align: center"><em><span style="color: #999999">«No phone when I’m with a customer!»</span></em></p>
<p>Which is why before using booxi, her customers were leaving voicemails, which she had to take on her free time to call them back by appointments priority, at the risk of getting in their voicemail in her turn, leaving another message. This endless exchange was a huge waste of time for both her and her customers.</p>
<p>Now, with booxi, Isabelle is much more efficient: if customers call and they get the voicemail, the message tells them they can book online or leave a message. No more waste of time on the phone.</p>
<p>She has increased the frequency of existing customers’ appointments, because they can now book when it’s the best time for them, and they find that really easy.</p>
<h3 style="text-align: center"></h3>
<h3 style="text-align: center"><b>Simplified booking with instant adoption by customers</b></h3>
<p>Finally with the “spacing after” feature, it’s easy for Isabelle to automatically include a busy time slot after each appointment without changing the customer’s appointment duration, and avoiding any confusion. Isabelle knows that she will have the time to clean up and to prepare the room for the next appointment, even when customers book appointments themselves. With booxi customers know how long their appointment is, and Isabelle can optimize her schedule.</p>
<p><img class="img_zoom size-full wp-image-1039 aligncenter" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/ioVJ2X8Dn-eMInopCISGYfqhpADUUmi8c9QAZd9gDxl-lTDvNjyN3HUuFzQeJ4f_NU6mK_zRYKdhGWEfg7cmocw=s0" alt="busy time slot" /></p>
<p>Isabelle found booxi very easy to set up and to use. It’s also the feedback of her customers: <em><span style="color: #999999">«It’s simple and easy to understand. Moreover one of my customer is 73 years old and she easily books her appointments with booxi.»</span></em></p>
<p>Since Isabelle started offering online appointment booking with booxi, she has acquired lots of new customers!</p>
<p style="text-align: center"><em><span style="color: #999999">«People want to simplify their lives, so if you help them to do it they will be happy and talk about it.»</span></em></p>
<p style="text-align: left">Online appointment booking is a great competitive advantage and Isabelle knows it.</p>
<p style="text-align: center"><a href="https://www.booxi.com/business/signup" class="creativ-shortcode creativ-shortcode-button creativ-shortcode-button-colour-allgreen creativ-shortcode-button-size-medium creativ-shortcode-button-edge-rounded" target="_blank">Get Started</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.booxi.com/blog/testimonial-esthetique-isa-belle/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Send instant SMS and Emails Messages to Your Clients</title>
		<link>https://www.booxi.com/blog/send-personalized-sms-and-emails-to-your-clients-2/</link>
		<comments>https://www.booxi.com/blog/send-personalized-sms-and-emails-to-your-clients-2/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2017 19:55:47 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Astrid Bertout]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Product Features]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[optimization]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[time saving]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.booxi.com/blog/?p=691</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Notify your clients without picking up the phone and save precious time. booxi introduces you a brand new feature to send instant email and SMS messages to your clients.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img class="float_top aligncenter wp-image-704 size-full" src="https://booxi-live-wp-storage.storage.googleapis.com/Article_NotifyClient.png" alt="send personalized message to customers" width="800" height="594" /><br />
Businesses like pet shops and repair shops, need to inform their clients once a service is done, just like any business may have to communicate quickly with a customer, for example if they are late with their appointments, and want to notify the next customer of a delay. With booxi it is now quick and easy to do it! Let’s take the example of a customer who booked an appointment to drop off his pet for grooming, bike, car or smartphone for repair. The customer is not present during the service, but has to be informed when it’s done. You currently have to call each customer; while with booxi you could:</p>
<ul>
<li>Send a notification as soon as the service is completed.</li>
<li>Quickly select a predefined message.</li>
<li>View all the messages you sent for a specific appointment or to a specific customer.</li>
</ul>
<p style="text-align: center"><b>How Does it Work?</b></p>
<p><b>Send a Message From an Appointment</b></p>
<p>You can notify a customer from an appointment in your booxi calendar.</p>
<ol>
<li>Right click on an appointment and select Notify Client.<img class="aligncenter wp-image-696 size-full" style="padding-top: 30px" src="https://booxi-live-wp-storage.storage.googleapis.com/notifyclient.png" alt="notify client option" width="368" height="434" /></li>
<li>A form appears, where you can select the way you want to notify your customer (by email, by SMS or by phone/call) and the message (create one or select a predefined message).<img src="https://booxi-live-wp-storage.storage.googleapis.com/notifyby.png" alt="ways to notify clients" width="564" height="337" /></li>
<li>Click on Send and your customer will instantly receive the message in their inbox or on their smartphone.</li>
<li>For notifications by phone, you simply take note of what have been discussed with the customer and click on Save.</li>
<li>You can now see, directly in your calendar, that a notification was sent for that appointment with the icon <a href="https://booxi-live-wp-storage.storage.googleapis.com/notify.jpg"><img class="verti_top" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/K_Gs41_ttH2CSSHNdvwUiKsnAAKMsdxiJB6sUXpgJxlLfNWRZxTtlysjRTH0nPjRGmcqEIMpVrM79LKbGs7Eaw=s0" alt="notify" /></a>.</li>
<li>From the appointment form you have access to all the messages sent for this specific appointment.<img class="img_zoom aligncenter wp-image-699 size-full" style="padding-top: 30px" src="https://booxi-live-wp-storage.storage.googleapis.com/viewmessagelist.png" alt="list of sent messages" width="368" height="434" /></li>
</ol>
<p><b>Edit and Add Predefined Messages</b><br />
You can predefined messages that suit your needs, you can modify it once it is created or add a new one.</p>
<ol>
<li>To do it, simply right click on the appointment and select Notify Client.</li>
<li>From there, select how you want to notify your customer (email, SMS or Phone Call).</li>
<li>In the section Preset message, click on the Add <img class="verti_top" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/FqosDAQStX3ANTUl1xC8ebNg7XG8Q1824PkTA9zKMejO8dtnQzAQVXb_tvoZvzYLbdvQvA7sK6luWUX-bOzr=s0" alt="add" /> icon. You can then add a name for the predefined message. Write the text you want and click on Save. Your preset message is saved. You can now use it by clicking on the drop down menu on the Preset message section. If you need to modify it, select the predefined message and click on the Edit <img class="verti_top" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/X_V8TYMTLWPlK4u3x59JFEiLaopdsTJ65JZXZBhooeuzH_3kj_c9BS2KpAumH81PbvVcz2T5AwFjr1qAb3T_=s0" alt="modifier" />icon. The Edit predefined message popup will appear and you will be able to modify the message. Click on Save to keep your changes, or Delete to delete that predefined message.</li>
<li>To add a new predefined message, select Custom Message and click on the Add  icon.</li>
</ol>
<p><b>View the Message History</b><br />
You can access the list of messages sent for a specific appointment or to a specific customer at any time.</p>
<ul>
<li>From the Appointment Form, use the menu at the top right and click on the option View Message History.</li>
<li>From the Client Summary (in the client list), select the option Message History.<img class="aligncenter wp-image-701 size-full" style="padding-top: 30px" src="https://booxi-live-wp-storage.storage.googleapis.com/messagehistory.png" alt="history of sent messages" width="1181" height="508" /></li>
</ul>
<p>With this personalized message feature you can improve your customer experience and save even more time.</p>
<hr class="dash" />
<p style="font-size: 30px;font-weight: 200;color: #888;text-align: center">Try it for free</p>
<p style="font-size: 16px;text-align: center;color: #555">14 days &#8211; No credit card required</p>
<p style="text-align: center"><a href="https://www.booxi.com/business/signup" class="creativ-shortcode creativ-shortcode-button creativ-shortcode-button-colour-allgreen creativ-shortcode-button-size-medium creativ-shortcode-button-edge-straight" target="_blank">Get Started</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.booxi.com/blog/send-personalized-sms-and-emails-to-your-clients-2/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Post on Your Social Networks in an efficient way</title>
		<link>https://www.booxi.com/blog/post-on-your-social-networks-in-just-15-minutes-a-week/</link>
		<comments>https://www.booxi.com/blog/post-on-your-social-networks-in-just-15-minutes-a-week/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2016 20:33:53 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Astrid Bertout]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Business Tips]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[time saving]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.booxi.com/blog/?p=565</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Find out how to manage your social networks like a Pro by publishing relevant content in just a few minutes per week. Here are some tips.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img class="float_top aligncenter wp-image-586 size-full" src="https://booxi-live-wp-storage.storage.googleapis.com/social_networks.jpg" alt="most popular social networks" width="1200" height="600" /><br />
Finding original ideas and relevant content and then publishing them on your social networks requires a significant time investment. Between managing your business and serving your customers, you often have not time left to take care of your social networks.</p>
<p>That is why we decided to offer you some advice to help you manage your social networks like a Pro by regularly publishing relevant content without spending hours on them.</p>
<h3 style="text-align: center">Take Notes During the Week</h3>
<p>The best way to waste time is to block time in your schedule to sit in-front of your computer and get lost on the internet looking for ideas for your posts.</p>
<p>A simple way to be more effective, is to take notes about events, inspirations and ideas as they come.</p>
<p>For example,</p>
<ul>
<li>Talk about new products</li>
<li>Announce a change in business hours</li>
<li>Remind people that you offer online booking</li>
<li>Share highlights of your business with your audience</li>
<li>Advertise your or your business participation to an event</li>
<li>Share articles that are related to your business</li>
<li>Introduce a new employee</li>
<li>Ask your customers about their opinion</li>
<li>Share content published by your partners</li>
</ul>
<p>This way, when the time comes to create your pots, you have ideas at hand.</p>
<p><strong>Tips<br />
</strong><br />
Publications with images are 94% more likely to be seen. Do not forget to illustrate each of your publications. Here is an article to help you easily find pictures related to your publications : <a href="https://www.booxi.com/blog/6-tools-for-stunning-photos-for-your-website/">https://www.booxi.com/blog/6-tools-for-stunning-photos-for-your-website/</a></p>
<h3 style="text-align: center">Keep Links to Relevant Articles and Websites</h3>
<p>During the week you are exposed to content, images and information from different networks that you follow. Either you don’t have the time to read and forget about to come back to it, or you don’t have time to publish right away and forget when the time comes; while this content would surely be relevant to your customers.</p>
<p>Create a folder in your bookmarks and add links to content that have drawn your attention during the week; thus you will be able to read it at a more convenient time and keep only the relevant links to include them into your weekly posts.</p>
<p>With Facebook, you can keep a link on a facebook post by clicking on the top right of a post, and on “Save link” or video or other content.</p>
<p><img class="border_grey border_round aligncenter wp-image-570 size-full" src="https://booxi-live-wp-storage.storage.googleapis.com/savelink.jpg" alt="save link on facebook" width="494" height="528" /></p>
<p>You can then review it at a later time that suits you better by clicking “Saved” to the left of your home page.</p>
<p><img class="border_grey border_round aligncenter wp-image-568 size-full" src="https://booxi-live-wp-storage.storage.googleapis.com/saved-post.jpg" alt="find a saved link on facebook" width="260" height="308" /></p>
<h3 style="text-align: center">Use Automation And Save Even More Time</h3>
<p>Use a solution that will allow you to program posts simultaneously on different social accounts. Such tools will make your life much easier by allowing you to schedule your publications at the most effective hours, and manage your social networks without having to login multiple accounts.</p>
<p>Examples of solutions :</p>
<p><a href="https://hootsuite.com/">Hootsuite</a> — The solution offers a free plan that allows you to manage publications on three different accounts and keep an eye on your metrics.</p>
<p><a href="https://buffer.com/">Buffer </a>— The solution also offers a free plan that allows you to manage multiple accounts, but does not provide much metrics.</p>
<p>If you have a Facebook account, you can use the scheduling feature of Facebook to program the date and time at which your posts will be published.</p>
<p><img class="border_grey border_round aligncenter wp-image-571 size-full" src="https://booxi-live-wp-storage.storage.googleapis.com/Schedule-post.jpg" alt="Schedule a facebook post" width="502" height="309" /></p>
<h3 style="text-align: center">Stay Tuned</h3>
<p>Keep an eye on your social network accounts and keep a personalized interaction. You don’t have to be logged in 24 hour, but make sure to reply to comments in a respectable delay and thank people who share your content.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.booxi.com/blog/post-on-your-social-networks-in-just-15-minutes-a-week/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Get More Revenues by Working Less ?</title>
		<link>https://www.booxi.com/blog/how-to-get-more-revenues-by-working-less/</link>
		<comments>https://www.booxi.com/blog/how-to-get-more-revenues-by-working-less/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2016 16:00:52 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Astrid Bertout]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Business Tips]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[online booking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[optimization]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[time saving]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.booxi.com/blog-dev/?p=290</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Stop loosing time and energy. Choose the right tool that works for you to increase your income, improve your customer service, and enjoy your evenings and week-end. ]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>You might think “Everyone knows that less work brings less income and not the opposite&#8230;&#8221;, but yet we always end up meeting someone who works less than us and gets more revenues. It is often because they find a way to make other people work for them, or work with tools that do the job for them.</p>
<p>With that in mind, let’s have a look on two examples based on real life cases and see how these people manage to increase their incomes by working less.</p>
<h3 style="text-align: center">For Michelle, Change Was Perceived as an Uphill Battle</h3>
<p>Michelle, a mother of two owns a massage therapy center with 6 employees and has almost no time left to see her clients as her business and appointment management occupies nearly all of her time. To avoid as much as possible no-shows, she spends hours sending emails and calling customers to remind them of their appointment for the next day. Unfortunately she has no time to take care of her website, her visibility and her marketing and she is unable to grow her business.</p>
<p>She hits a wall and has to change something, but change feels like an uphill battle for her. Michelle finally decides and begins to use a tool that she was considering for several months, but yet was delaying the implementation date.</p>
<p>The transition is very easy, employees adapt quickly, and the uphill battle becomes a small step. Customers love it, nearly 20% of them book appointments without calling, and get an automated confirmation email. Reminders are also automatically sent by email and/or SMS, which completely takes away the associated workload while eliminating no-shows. Her client list automatically update, so she no more needs Excel nor paper notes because her appointment solution does all the work for her.</p>
<p>After only one month using it, she realizes that managing appointments is not time consuming anymore, her employees have access to their appointments and the tool does the rest, “It’s like magic” she says. Given this work reduction, which Michelle estimates to be 28 hours a week, she starts seeing customers and even hires a new therapist. And after two months of using the tool she hires another therapist.</p>
<p>Two months ago, Michelle could not see the day her business would grow and now it is performing better than ever while Michelle works less.</p>
<h3 style="text-align: center">Julie Used to Spend Her Evenings Calling Back Clients,<br />
on Top of Paying Two Daytime Receptionists</h3>
<p>Julie owns a beauty salon in Quebec with a good clientele, many beauticians and two shared receptionists which costs nearly $36,000 a year. Despite her good business management, she spends her evenings and part of her weekends to call back clients as no-shows quickly becomes a problem if she doesn’t so.</p>
<p>She decides to &#8220;take the technology turn&#8221; she said. Right from the first week employees are comfortable with the tool and inform their customers that they can now book appointments online from their website or directly from their facebook page.</p>
<p>Julie starts having more free time instantly, and she can enjoy her evenings and weekends. After her first month, she reduces her reception to one receptionist, a saving that she estimates to $ 18,000 a year.</p>
<p>She provides a better customer service than ever, her employees love the tool, her business is more profitable than ever and Julie works less.</p>
<h3>Work Smarter Not Harder</h3>
<p>The previous cases clearly show how easy it can be to increase income by working less, if you work more efficiently.</p>
<p>Now let&#8217;s take a fictional example by calculating a possible increase in income, while using actual statistics.</p>
<h3>Professional NOT Using a Tool:</h3>
<p><strong>$40</strong> per 30 min appointment ( $80/hr).<br />
<strong>64</strong> appointments per week for a total of 32 hours (+ $2,560).<br />
<strong>7.5</strong> hours spent on the phone weekly.<br />
<strong>13%</strong> missed appointments (4 missed appointments per week &#8211; $320).</p>
<p><strong>40</strong> hours (or more) of work per week.<br />
<strong>$2,240</strong> in revenues ( $2,560 &#8211; $320) per week.</p>
<p><strong>30</strong> hours on the phone each month.<br />
<strong>$8,960</strong> in gross revenue per month.<br />
<strong>$43,000</strong> a year before tax, with a profit margin of 40% after expenses.</p>
<h3>Professional Using a Tool:</h3>
<p><strong>8</strong> hours less the phone time per month (+ 16 appointments $640).<br />
<strong>2%</strong> no-shows only (+ 13 appointments per month $520).<br />
<strong>$5,568</strong> per year for a total annual income of $48,568 before tax.<br />
<strong>2,729%</strong> return on your investment of $204 per year for the management tool.</p>
<h3 style="text-align: center">Gross Revenue increase of $27,840<br />
At an additional cost of only $408</h3>
<p>The same scenario can easily be used to estimate that a business of 5 employees could get a revenue increase of $27,840 at the sole cost of $408.</p>
<p>You too, can “take the technology turn” to increase your revenues, improve your customer service, and enjoy your evenings and weekends, or for all these reasons.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.booxi.com/blog/how-to-get-more-revenues-by-working-less/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tired to Spend Most of Your Time on the Phone to Manage Your Appointments?</title>
		<link>https://www.booxi.com/blog/tired-to-spend-most-of-your-time-on-the-phone-to-manage-your-appointments/</link>
		<comments>https://www.booxi.com/blog/tired-to-spend-most-of-your-time-on-the-phone-to-manage-your-appointments/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 Aug 2016 18:34:14 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Astrid Bertout]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Business Tips]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[no-show]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[online booking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[time saving]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.booxi.com/blog-dev/?p=153</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Stop wasting time and focus on what you really like to do : be with your customers.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img class="float_top aligncenter wp-image-781 size-full" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/59sO0o50pVl2u-ry-B7_6tiqhr-sKAIjh0QZA28AM10lrPpJhk8gHqu__QodLsILHHIdaEM1DHmigP8j5xyV75E=s0" alt="woman spending too much time on the phone" width="1200" height="600" /><div class="creativ-shortcode creativ-shortcode-cols  creativ-shortcode-cols-half-half "><div class="creativ-shortcode creativ-shortcode-col creativ-shortcode-col-a"><div class="creativ-shortcode-col-inner"><p>Juggling with appointments, sales, marketing, customer service while managing a business can turn into real headache. Some solutions may actually help you to save a lot of time. Take a management solution for appointment as booxi and see the benefits it offers.</p>
</div></div></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<div class="creativ-shortcode creativ-shortcode-col creativ-shortcode-col-b"><div class="creativ-shortcode-col-inner"></div></div>
<ul>
<li>Gain Efficiency</li>
<li>Reduce No-Shows</li>
<li>Get More Satisfied Customers</li>
<li>Automate your Client List</li>
<li>Get More Online Visibility and More Appointments</div></li>
</ul>
<hr />
<h3>Gain Efficiency</h3>
<p>You’ll save time by spending less time on the phone.<br />
You lose around 6 minutes per phone call to book an appointment, asking for personal information, confirmation of the date, time and so on. Reduce that phone time with booxi. It will manage part of your appointments by encouraging your clients to book online. At least 6 hours saving per month!</p>
<h3>Reduce No-Shows</h3>
<p>For each appointment, booxi sends an automated confirmation with all information at hand for the customer. Customers are less likely to call back to ask about the date or the address. In addition, the platform offers the possibility to send an automated reminder (by email or text message). No-shows will decrease from 13% to less than 2%! Automate your business !</p>
<h3>Get More Satisfied Customers</h3>
<p>Allow your customers to book their appointment when they have time.</p>
<p>20% of customers prefer booking online over talking to someone on the phone, also they can do it when they have time and as soons as they think about it (even when your business is closed). They save time, just as you do. Focus on customer experience!</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h3>Automate Your Client List</h3>
<p>When you use an online booking solution, you collect your customers emails (with their consent). As they book online and you add new appointments, you automatically build up your client list with valuable details. You can also access each customer’s appointment history (and notes for each appointment). It’s a good way to impress them by knowing when was their last visit and the service they received. In addition, thanks to automated recall you can send emails to invite them to book a new appointment, with an impeccable timing.</p>
<h3>Get More Online Visibility and More Appointments</h3>
<p>With solution like booxi for example, you can also add the Book Now button to your website, your Facebook page, and in all your messages (2 sources for new appointments). Finally, add your link on specialized online directory. All roads lead to a new appointment !</p>
<p style="text-align: center"><strong>The solution works for you and you can focus on what you like to do.</strong><br />
<strong>Amazing, this online appointment booking. What could be better ?</strong></p>
<hr class="dash" />
<p style="text-align: center;font-weight: 200"><span class="bx_text24">Try booxi for free</span></p>
<h5 style="text-align: center">14 days &#8211; No credit card required</h5>
<p style="text-align: center"><a href="https://www.booxi.com/business/signup" class="creativ-shortcode creativ-shortcode-button creativ-shortcode-button-colour-allgreen creativ-shortcode-button-size-medium creativ-shortcode-button-edge-straight" target="_blank">Get Started</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.booxi.com/blog/tired-to-spend-most-of-your-time-on-the-phone-to-manage-your-appointments/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>booxi is proud to have contributed to the success of the Hair Fashion Night of L&#8217;Oréal Professionnel event.</title>
		<link>https://www.booxi.com/blog/booxi-is-proud-to-have-contributed-to-the-success-of-the-hair-fashion-night-of-loreal-professionnel-event/</link>
		<comments>https://www.booxi.com/blog/booxi-is-proud-to-have-contributed-to-the-success-of-the-hair-fashion-night-of-loreal-professionnel-event/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2016 17:01:54 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Astrid Bertout]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[online booking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[time saving]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[trade show]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.booxi.com/blog-dev/?p=75</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Thanks to its easy-friendly use and its features, booxi contributed to the success of an event organized by L'Oréal Professionnel, that required a smart solution to manage appointments.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img class="float_top shadow_large aligncenter wp-image-360 size-full" src="http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/GhcZhwYtr4idtL68KNiCkYLV8W_pzTsV0llAxECwzG9jUsOrEQasd1fDLiZEnvJyxo98O4pql_hoQYJnolxd=s0" alt="Loreal_Cover4" width="1200" height="600" /></p>
<p>On May 12th 2016, booxi participated to the successful Hair Fashion Night in Toronto event organized by L&#8217;Oréal Professionnel. With a progressive opening of places and with more than 700 appointments made in only 4 days, the event was rapidly sold out.</p>
<p>In order to support this complex logistic of automatically assigning attendees to one of the 50 stylists, according to the available time slots per stylist, L&#8217;Oréal Professionnel has chosen booxi.</p>
<p>Attendees were able to reserve online from the L’Oréal Professionnel booxi page, Facebook and a custom mobile app, then receive a confirmation by email with their designated time and stylist. A major time savings for the organizers, and a great experience for the participants.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><img class="shadow_medium aligncenter wp-image-361" src="http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/Auz3AfHmV67b0p63MQeJK-21rbR89-Bf7DCUOYLOSzWVwtxy2DgyDOywNU-odhLq5DLmK6D3obXrlqke2yOkP3Y=s0" alt="oreal_1" width="494" height="172" /></p>
<blockquote><p><span class="bx_text24">Appointment online booking was suspended because all time slots were filled, and resumed 3 days later, following the opening of 150 new spaces by L&#8217;Oréal Professionnel.</span></p></blockquote>
<p><img class="shadow_medium aligncenter wp-image-362" src="http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/6KwQu9V3IFzVVg2Gt4WgPMvUuFw9HDX-4dWR1mlgs4tDXyQQ_mwv-pD56_VopBspu5R9mrS55Q-vre2VPcC8=s0" alt="oreal_2" width="498" height="135" /></p>
<blockquote><p><span class="bx_text24">The event was a success and booxi is happy to have helped a company as large as L&#8217;Oréal Professionnel, as it daily supports SMEs and self-employed workers.</span></p></blockquote>
<p><img class="aligncenter" src="https://2.bp.blogspot.com/-xEIlz816Utk/V0W-H6kTUjI/AAAAAAAAAZs/z293ho-9J7Y44wwF09xf0ewVMLM8S9sgQCLcB/s1600/hairfashionnight.png" alt="" /></p>
<hr />
<h3 style="text-align: center"><strong>About L’Oréal</strong></h3>
<p>L’Oréal has devoted itself to beauty for over 105 years. With its unique international portfolio of 32 diverse and complementary brands, the Group generated sales amounting to 22.5 billion euros in 2014 and employs 78,600 people worldwide. As the world’s leading Beauty Company, L’Oréal is present across all distribution networks: mass market, department stores, pharmacies and drugstores, hair salons, travel retail and branded retail.</p>
<p>Research and innovation, and a dedicated research team of 3,700 people, are at the core of L’Oréal’s strategy, working to meet beauty aspirations all over the world and attract one billion new consumers in the years to come. L’Oréal’s new sustainability commitment for 2020 “Sharing Beauty With All”sets out ambitious sustainable development objectives across the Group’s value chain.</p>
<p style="text-align: center"><a href="http://www.loreal.fr/media/press-releases/2016/apr/loreal-partenaire-de-hello-tomorrow" class="creativ-shortcode creativ-shortcode-button creativ-shortcode-button-colour-white creativ-shortcode-button-size-medium creativ-shortcode-button-edge-rounded" target="_blank">Visit Website</a></p>
<hr class="dash" />
<h3 style="text-align: center"><strong>About booxi</strong></h3>
<p>booxi is a very easy to use smart appointment solution that provides just what business and self-employed professionals need: Online visibility (with an automated website), a collaborative appointment solution, a customer list (CRM), communication and marketing automation, and an integration with point of sale (POS) systems.</p>
<hr />
<p style="text-align: center">Do you want to know more about booxi, and learn about all the features?</p>
<p style="text-align: center"><a href="https://www.booxi.com/business/signup"><a href="https://www.booxi.com/business/signup" class="creativ-shortcode creativ-shortcode-button creativ-shortcode-button-colour-allgreen creativ-shortcode-button-size-medium creativ-shortcode-button-edge-straight" target="_blank">Try it for free</a></a> <a href="https://www.booxi.com/features#online-appointment-booking"><a href="https://www.booxi.com/features#online-appointment-booking" class="creativ-shortcode creativ-shortcode-button creativ-shortcode-button-colour-white creativ-shortcode-button-size-medium creativ-shortcode-button-edge-straight" target="_blank">Learn More</a></a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.booxi.com/blog/booxi-is-proud-to-have-contributed-to-the-success-of-the-hair-fashion-night-of-loreal-professionnel-event/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>booxi Got The Attention of The Toronto ESI 2016</title>
		<link>https://www.booxi.com/blog/booxi-got-the-attention-of-the-toronto-esi-2016/</link>
		<comments>https://www.booxi.com/blog/booxi-got-the-attention-of-the-toronto-esi-2016/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2016 16:55:27 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Astrid Bertout]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[affordable solution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[appointment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[time saving]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.booxi.com/blog-dev/?p=71</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[The benefits of booxi through the amazing feedback of EIS Toronto attendees.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h3 style="text-align: center"><strong><img class="float_top aligncenter" src="https://3.bp.blogspot.com/-HIdZMFguUdQ/VyJT8nKDYnI/AAAAAAAAANk/Xu2vjk3QheAOL20YPfTILs_SeAxrssEhwCLcB/s400/IMG_0602.JPG" alt="" width="400" height="266" /><br />
booxi at the 2016 Toronto ESI (Esthetic SPA International) Show attracted hundreds of business owners and professionals with its smart solution.</strong></h3>
<p>Business owners and self-employed professionals are more and more conscious that they need to manage their business more efficiently, and that includes visibility and accessibility to their services by consumers, as well as an access to information on their business and an optimisation of their time. Which is why they are shopping for tools to help them.</p>
<p>They have definitely realized by now that their old and expensive salon management software needs to be replaced, and that there are better and less expensive solutions available in the market. Even professionals working alone understand that they can also profit from smart solutions like booxi.</p>
<p>It is the beauty and simplicity of booxi that catch their attention at first, and then when they find out about all it can do for them, and how easy to use and affordable it is, we can feel their relief. They have finally found something that will really change their life. The return on their investment is so big, that the fear and burden of using software goes away.</p>
<p>It was great to see them bringing more people to our booth, as they wanted to share their discovery, booxi. We had a great time with our visitors, presenting booxi and answering questions. We will be happy to help hundreds of professionals and business owner using booxi, to get more results with less effort.</p>
<p>Lots of graduating students will now have a chance to start their own business without investing money on a website or software, booxi will provide them all they need at a uncomparable affordable price and simplicity.</p>
<p>Professionals and business owners will have the opportunity to start using a cloud solution that finally meets their needs and budget, to help them get where they always wanted to be in their business.</p>
<p><strong>Thank you all for visiting us at EIS, and we wish you lots of success with your business using booxi.</strong></p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.booxi.com/blog/booxi-got-the-attention-of-the-toronto-esi-2016/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Booxi Made Lots of Happy Professionals and Business Owners at the 2016 Vancouver EIS This Year</title>
		<link>https://www.booxi.com/blog/booxi-made-lots-of-happy-professionals-and-business-owners-at-the-2016-vancouver-eis-this-year/</link>
		<comments>https://www.booxi.com/blog/booxi-made-lots-of-happy-professionals-and-business-owners-at-the-2016-vancouver-eis-this-year/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2016 16:52:08 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Astrid Bertout]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[affordable solution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[online booking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[time saving]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.booxi.com/blog-dev/?p=69</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[booxi was at the Vancouver ESI 2016. This overview highlights the great feedback received during the event.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong><img class="float_top aligncenter" src="https://4.bp.blogspot.com/-c-3z2Wuwl4U/VuxImJKXE8I/AAAAAAAAAE0/mR49JG1kax8VOos_zXMsk48Z1L4b5iKSA/s640/SHOW.PNG" alt="booxi founders" width="640" height="507" />booxi was at the 2016 Vancouver EIS (Esthetic SPA International) show at the beginning of March showcasing booxi to professionals from BC and the surroundings.</strong></p>
<p>The feedback we got was amazing and unanimous from the roughly 500 professionals we met with. They were surprised by the simplicity and pricing of booxi, as well as how fast they can start using it and how soon they start benefiting from it.</p>
<p>Professionals visiting EIS don’t really expect to see software in this type of trade show, they are mainly here for beauty products, equipment and new technologies or discovery and sessions for their industry. When they see software, they are reluctant thinking it is about website design, or expensive Salon system or Marketing tools. They don’t expect to find something like booxi that completely changes the game for them.</p>
<p>Even though they think this is not for them; within the first 30 seconds we talk to them, we describe the problems they face for which they all agree by saying that it is even worst, then when we start explaining the solution we have for them, they get very excited. Finally when we show the pricing, the reaction is always the same “Are you … serious!”. The entire two days were like that none stop, so it was very rewarding for us to see the reaction and how people saw us as their salvation.</p>
<p>For students who were planning on starting their own business, it was a true revelation. They will now be able to start their business without spending $3,000 to $8,000 for a website, a POS and computers. With a little budget of $17 to $34 a month ($200 to $400 a year) they’ll have everything they need including the website, the CRM, the appointment solution, the automated email and SMS and more. They will be more effective than most established businesses on day one and be able to focus on doing what they love the most: spending time with customers.</p>
<p>We have been working hard at booxi to reach this objective of providing professionals and small businesses a smart solution that works for them, enabling them to get more results with less efforts. One of the most important objective was to create something beautiful and very simple to use. We are very happy to confirm that the feedback we got at the show, and growing popularity of booxi just prove that this is mission accomplished <img src="https://www.booxi.com/blog/wp-includes/images/smilies/icon_smile.gif" alt=":)" class="wp-smiley" /> </p>
<p style="text-align: center">Thank you all for visiting us at EIS, and we wish you lots of success with your<br />
business using booxi.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.booxi.com/blog/booxi-made-lots-of-happy-professionals-and-business-owners-at-the-2016-vancouver-eis-this-year/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to easily improve communication with your clients?</title>
		<link>https://www.booxi.com/blog/how-does-booxi-improve-communication-with-your-clients/</link>
		<comments>https://www.booxi.com/blog/how-does-booxi-improve-communication-with-your-clients/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2016 19:22:47 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Astrid Bertout]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Business Tips]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[online booking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[reminder]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[time saving]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.booxi.com/blog-dev/?p=34</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[A successful management of appointment booking depends on communication. booxi enables you to communicate easily and clearly with your clients in a way that increases the quality level of your service and saves you lots of time. Let's see how booxi does it.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><div class="creativ-shortcode creativ-shortcode-cols  creativ-shortcode-cols-half-half "><div class="creativ-shortcode creativ-shortcode-col creativ-shortcode-col-a"><div class="creativ-shortcode-col-inner"><p>Let&#8217;s see how booxi does it, so you understand when and what messages are sent to your clients throughout the booking process.</p>
</div></div></p>
<div class="creativ-shortcode creativ-shortcode-col creativ-shortcode-col-b"><div class="creativ-shortcode-col-inner"></div></div>
<ul>
<li>What messages does booxi send ?</li>
<li>When are the messages sent ? </div></li>
</ul>
<hr />
<p style="text-align: justify">Managing appointments is all about communication, and booxi enables you to communicate easily and clearly with your clients in a way that increases the quality level of your service and saves you lots of time.<br />
<img class="alignright wp-image-104" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/i79hdnbLe1le6Nx0o1HrmJ6rfCgW7bXcURhYIVSpYWEjKp-hhfLKqOXFzqRFT6S3K8paExlsMhj5BIBIx7PUAw=s0" alt="Confirmation Email with booxi" width="409" height="560" /></p>
<p style="text-align: justify">From the moment you book for a client or a client self-book an appointment with you using booxi, the communication flow starts with the objective of informing and assisting your client. Messages are automatically sent via email or SMS, and no effort is required on your part, although you still have control over this. The choice of email or SMS is determined by the client preferences and the importance of the message.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify">These preferences can be specified by you when you book an appointment for your client or by your client when he self-books online. You may also modified these preferences in your client record.</p>
<h3>What messages does booxi send?</h3>
<p>booxi sends messages according to the appointment’s status, so clients always receive comprehensive messages such as confirmation, rescheduling, cancellation, reminders and other notifications. We have included a list of the most important messages at the end of this article.</p>
<p>Some messages will ask your client to confirm a time or a change, while others will simply inform your client, providing him with the possibility of rescheduling or cancelling the appointment. These messages include buttons (with web links) for your client to use, to perform these actions, and instantly notify you in booxi. These simple options will save you valuable time off the phone.</p>
<ul>
<li>Your clients get all appointment details handy.</li>
<li>They can modify or cancel an appointment (optionally).</li>
<li>You can add notes to any appointment to inform your client.</li>
<li>You can get them to confirm without picking up the phone.</li>
</ul>
<h3>When are messages sent?</h3>
<p>Confirmation and notification messages are sent as soon as the appointment changes while reminders are sent at a specific time, which you can configure.</p>
<p>A confirmation is sent when you approve an appointment request, and notifications are sent whenever you modify, reschedule or cancel an appointment with the option to notify the client (which is by default).</p>
<ul>
<li>You can change the delay for the reminder (by default it is 24 hours before the appointment).</li>
<li>You can decide for each appointment to send or not send a notification message (by default, it won&#8217;t send it).</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Reminders</strong></p>
<p>Sending reminders to your clients is one of the most effective ways to prevent no shows. Every time an appointment is booked using booxi, you make sure the client will show up.</p>
<p>Both email and SMS reminders provide the time and the address of the appointment which also saves you time, since statistics shows that many customers call to get the address just before their appointments.</p>
<p><strong>Messages</strong></p>
<p>Here is a list of some of the messages booxi sends.</p>
<table>
<tbody>
<tr>
<td style="width: 675px;padding-bottom: 1em">Messages</td>
<td style="width: 75px">Emails</td>
<td style="width: 50px">SMS</td>
</tr>
<p><!-- Row 1 --></p>
<tr>
<td style="padding-right: 1em;padding-bottom: 1em">A confirmation of reception is sent when a client books online an appointment that requires your approval. This message will inform the client of the next steps to expect.</td>
<td>X</td>
<td></td>
</tr>
<p><!-- Row 2 --></p>
<tr>
<td style="padding-right: 1em;padding-bottom: 1em">An appointment confirmation is immediately sent when the appointment is approved manually by you or automatically by booxi (if you told booxi to do so).</td>
<td>X</td>
<td>X</td>
</tr>
<p><!-- Row 3 --></p>
<tr>
<td style="padding-right: 1em;padding-bottom: 1em">If you reschedule or modify an appointment, a notification message is sent to the client. If the appointment has not been modified with the client on the phone, you can ask the client to confirm the change using the buttons embedded in the email. This will save you some time off the phone. SMS are only sent for reschedule (if you told booxi to do so).</td>
<td>X</td>
<td>X</td>
</tr>
<p><!-- Row 4 --></p>
<tr>
<td style="padding-right: 1em;padding-bottom: 1em">A notification is sent to inform the client that the appointment has been canceled (if you told booxi to do so). SMS are only sent for last minute cancellations.</td>
<td>X</td>
<td>X</td>
</tr>
<p><!-- Row 5 --></p>
<tr>
<td style="padding-right: 1em;padding-bottom: 1em">Reminders are sent sometimes before the appointment to remind the client of the time and place of the appointment and make sure the appointment is not missed.</td>
<td>X</td>
<td>X</td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>
<div class="clearfix"></div>
<h3 style="text-align: left">Things to remember:</h3>
<ul>
<li style="text-align: left">Clients love email and SMS confirmations and reminders.</li>
<li style="text-align: left">You save lots of time with the automated communications of booxi.</li>
<li style="text-align: left">Reminders help reducing no shows.</li>
<li style="text-align: left">Communication increases your quality of service.</li>
<li style="text-align: left">You still have control over it.</li>
<li style="text-align: left">Use booxi for all your appointments, save time and make no-shows history.</li>
</ul>
<hr />
<p style="text-align: center">Send email and SMS to your customers : save a lot of time and improve your communication with your clients.</p>
<p style="text-align: center">
<a href="https://www.booxi.com/features#client_profiles" class="creativ-shortcode creativ-shortcode-button creativ-shortcode-button-colour-allgreen creativ-shortcode-button-size-medium creativ-shortcode-button-edge-straight" target="_blank">Read More ?</a></p>
<p><span id="more-34"></span></p>
<p><!--more--></p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.booxi.com/blog/how-does-booxi-improve-communication-with-your-clients/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>12 H Time Format, Cancellation Policy per Service, Compact Schedule</title>
		<link>https://www.booxi.com/blog/update-12-h-time-format-cancellation-policy-per-service-compact-schedule/</link>
		<comments>https://www.booxi.com/blog/update-12-h-time-format-cancellation-policy-per-service-compact-schedule/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2016 19:12:07 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Astrid Bertout]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Product Features]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[agenda]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[schedule]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[time saving]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.booxi.com/blog-dev/?p=28</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Learn more about the calendar features that make you save even more time. ]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><div class="creativ-shortcode creativ-shortcode-cols  creativ-shortcode-cols-half-half "><div class="creativ-shortcode creativ-shortcode-col creativ-shortcode-col-a"><div class="creativ-shortcode-col-inner"><p>We’ve just released a booxi update with a few small improvements explained in this articles.</p>
</div></div><div class="creativ-shortcode creativ-shortcode-col creativ-shortcode-col-b"><div class="creativ-shortcode-col-inner"></div></div></p>
<ul>
<li>Improved Date and Time Localisation</li>
<li>Compact Daily Schedule Report</li>
<li>Cancellation Policy per Service</li>
<li>Current Timeline in Calendar</li>
<li>Precise Gray Schedule Zones in Calenda</div></li>
</ul>
<hr />
<h3>Improved Date and Time Localisation</h3>
<h3><a href="https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/sKDFQNAuHSEcO1qqI5xar5MInD1NWUZyILfT_4ZCb1JUpYIyR5BuV1c0gaJotIhi5d6PGYVc0vqtXt88_4fV0i1F1Z_Hx5W5QAkUW7cDLV8QhRMiOhn2_fdKWinmQwN1RUQqdiIA"><img class="shadow_medium alignright" title="use_banner" src="https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/sKDFQNAuHSEcO1qqI5xar5MInD1NWUZyILfT_4ZCb1JUpYIyR5BuV1c0gaJotIhi5d6PGYVc0vqtXt88_4fV0i1F1Z_Hx5W5QAkUW7cDLV8QhRMiOhn2_fdKWinmQwN1RUQqdiIA" alt="set up hours" width="241" height="132" border="0" /></a></h3>
<p>We improved the support for differences in date and time formatting for various countries. The support of both, 24 hours and Military AM/PM time has been applied everywhere in the application.</p>
<h3>Compact Daily Schedule Report</h3>
<p>We added a new Daily Calendar View report which lists up to 24 appointments per page instead of only 8 appointments per page for the Detailed Schedule Report.<a style="font-weight: normal" href="https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/djVWmG-HhdA9iPJgIV3ATpTKUkHkJu25mYSd6tAH7o4tZ9EuZy8F7z0FZuCzF7GLxqjpzNx2poutPYiU-TA63RWfPcNTzQDwdsa3t6sWA4i5NwUAGcaVRC55NmlynQsq3EZMHTdQ"><img class="shadow_medium alignright" src="https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/djVWmG-HhdA9iPJgIV3ATpTKUkHkJu25mYSd6tAH7o4tZ9EuZy8F7z0FZuCzF7GLxqjpzNx2poutPYiU-TA63RWfPcNTzQDwdsa3t6sWA4i5NwUAGcaVRC55NmlynQsq3EZMHTdQ" alt="print schedule" width="259" height="164" border="0" /></a></p>
<p>To access the Compact Schedule Report:</p>
<ol>
<li>Go to your calendar day view</li>
<li><span style="line-height: 21.6px">Click on the action menu button <img style="font-weight: normal;color: #000000" src="https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/bAK47s-rP2ZE9TRNjjOmmQRrd9WGq941rMY6dxD10SUGZgw1Wz1JE0PHV9V95bCfd6kF0rDtJCFb1o3sYbSSvkw0VzReJxduioUaF7TARnRV4CDIoUKcTeZxmzNXtz15PaGQiS2i" alt="" /></span></li>
<li><span style="line-height: 21.6px">Select Print compact schedule.</span></li>
</ol>
<p>With the Google Chrome Browser, you can always Print or save a report in PDF format.</p>
<p><a style="font-weight: normal" href="https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/RLJhFysAyIQfw6z-y__FR2rPuRJ7DVJelpwVaAZ_8L8yRy7GZXbL6UlegveeTJ9xaiTYaEBrlW4HhqimlvPHBa8gE-loVbWhlsjiGnuoRjs_ekdHKRvGW1wfN-SMimww5Ruq4DF0"><img class="aligncenter" src="https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/RLJhFysAyIQfw6z-y__FR2rPuRJ7DVJelpwVaAZ_8L8yRy7GZXbL6UlegveeTJ9xaiTYaEBrlW4HhqimlvPHBa8gE-loVbWhlsjiGnuoRjs_ekdHKRvGW1wfN-SMimww5Ruq4DF0" alt="Daily schedule" width="309" height="400" border="0" /></a></p>
<h3>Cancellation Policy per Service</h3>
<p>You can now customize the cancellation policies for each service. By default, all services use the business cancellation policy, but you can specify a different one.</p>
<p><img class="alignright" src="https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/ySuzQM4Es5TSCt8KbmvMNTQGtgTWg3S57oC0mAUvpC4Gv8Mr3VBK7vdPQDzz_4YqmrO3dscD37C_pBSYH-D79P7nT1_SkRQsu5eMVwHusEPC-OzGzL9gmWKlm6ps5es1umGQofMM" alt="appointment rules per service" width="320" height="249" border="0" /></p>
<p>To set a different cancellation policy for a specific service:</p>
<ol>
<li>Go to your service list</li>
<li><span style="line-height: 21.6px">Select the service of your choice</span></li>
<li><span style="line-height: 21.6px">Click on Appointment Rules</span></li>
<li><span style="line-height: 21.6px">Turn on the Cancellation Policy <img style="font-weight: normal;color: #000000" src="https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/BFkDc_VSvdcUbz-dmdmuiFEhNJgx4_vWRul0XDjQ6I4DUHw6gx96A5X0GJrnfm-ZycZOuSGzw4TBS367GpY5Z7gg6U3U1Xx9v-9R-N9YVA0A0IBLzmyN9iH5guESyVbWMsp-w_Q-" alt="" /></span></li>
<li><span style="line-height: 21.6px">Customize its settings, and click Save.</span></li>
</ol>
<h3>Current Timeline</h3>
<p>We added a thin light blue line that appears on top of your calendar to show you at all time where is the current time in your schedule.</p>
<h3>Precise Gray Schedule Zones in Calendar</h3>
<p>You can always see your work hours schedule or business open hours (depending on your schedule settings) as a grey color in your calendar background. Now if your appointment interval was set to 60 min and your day started at 8h30, the calendar was grayed starting from 9h00, not 8h30, which was confusing. We improved this feature by coloring the background with a precision of 5 mins. So you get the exact information on your work schedule.</p>
<p><img class="shadow_medium aligncenter" src="https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/FTt_OPoyNnD4scmDBLAN26rz6euBK7z2jTLfgMGPwcbMvpnMbMHUdxWMMeFZXmhKzylcvo-5nzvd5_1U5VehQVB1Dih82TPTM_GuFI0SyiOcNCzbX2ZPsNThsJ_MV0OKGg4U5kEh" alt="more precise schedules" width="833" height="482" /></p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.booxi.com/blog/update-12-h-time-format-cancellation-policy-per-service-compact-schedule/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>