<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>booxi &#187; Testimonials</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.booxi.com/blog/category/testimonials/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.booxi.com/blog</link>
	<description>booxi</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2017 18:59:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
		<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
		<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>http://wordpress.org/?v=3.9.1</generator>
	<item>
		<title>“A solution for my client files!”</title>
		<link>https://www.booxi.com/blog/testimonial-permanent-makeup/</link>
		<comments>https://www.booxi.com/blog/testimonial-permanent-makeup/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2017 15:15:05 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Astrid Bertout]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Testimonials]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Owners]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.booxi.com/blog/?p=1153</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Discover why Annie Banville can’t live without booxi and why she thinks it helps her customer experience stand out.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img class="float_top aligncenter wp-image-1161 size-full" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/cbFZSUWnZFyiklgFZ67448xCJ2CDQqi_kuWFv4d_Kocqd0IghGPP09R_WtgTWO-ptB_oGIp3AsMnRl_vVFoO9wA=s0" alt="testimonial annie banville " width="1200" height="390" />Annie Banville is a cosmetic beautician who’s been passionate about cosmetology for more than 20 years. A make-up artist recognized by <a href="http://www.apeseq.ca/">APESEQ</a>, she opened <a href="http://maquillagepermanentab.com/" target="_blank">Maquillage Permanent AB</a> salon in 2010, fulfilling a long-time dream. And she’s been living her passion ever since! She specializes in permanent and professional makeup, and her delicate touch and experience lets her offer personalized service to each and every one of her customers.</p>
<p>Today, Annie tell us how booxi helps her run her salon and be a more efficient businesswoman.</p>
<h2>What made you try booxi in October 2016?</h2>
<p>“10 years ago I wasn’t very good with technology; I worked on paper a lot. My calendar, my customer files, even my accounting – everything was on paper. But in permanent makeup, customers can come back 10 years after an appointment to get a retouch, for example, so I could never destroy any files. As a result, my files quickly piled up and took up a ton of storage space. I had to find a solution.</p>
<p>That’s why I wanted to try booxi. My challenge was to find an effective way to manage my customer files. I heard about booxi through <a href="http://www.apeseq.ca/">APESEQ</a>, and I saw that they had a &#8220;Client Files&#8221; feature online. I signed up for the free trial and that’s when I realized online appointment booking could be useful, too. I found it interesting because as a self-employed professional, I don’t have a receptionist working for me, so when I’m with a customer I don’t answer my phone.</p>
<p>That’s why it sometimes took me up to 3 days to book an appointment with a customer. Everything went through voicemail: the customer would leave me a message, I’d call her back to give my availabilities, then she’d call back to let me know that the dates didn’t work for her…sometimes it would take a few days to find a date that worked for both of us.</p>
<p>It made me realize there was a problem. That’s why I decided to give online booking a shot during the free trial. Right away, I saw how much it simplified my life.</p>
<p>As soon as I launched my online account, a customer booked an appointment without having to call me. And then the bookings just kept on coming. It was incredibly convenient.</p>
<p>At the same time, I started transferring all my paper client files to booxi.”<br />
<img class="img_zoom aligncenter size-full wp-image-1158" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/ZyLEqao7PYGXhkla2UqdopZuqgQU0S4kr1OT1M1LguEV1Adwu9HgrNTfE0-vIcgdvJQkLyfKdip4vFUWS5HXhRE=s0" alt="salon maquillage permanent" /></p>
<h2><b>How</b><b> has booxi </b><b>changed your</b><b> daily </b><b>routine?</b></h2>
<p>&#8220;Before using booxi, when I was still working with paper, I’d spend one or two evenings a week calling all my clients to remind them about their upcoming appointments. Now I don’t need to do that because they automatically receive a reminder.</p>
<p>Beyond the huge time savings, it also eliminated a task I didn’t like doing. People don’t really like getting phone calls in the evening, so I sometimes felt it wasn’t the right time for my customers. Besides, I didn’t necessarily want to make phone calls at night, either.&#8221;</p>
<p>“When I started using booxi, I thought it would mostly interest my younger customers. But I’ve noticed that my older clients use it, too, and they like receiving text reminders. I was surprised that people use online appointment booking as often as they do. Because I’m in permanent makeup, I assumed that people would rather meet me or talk to me before booking an appointment, but that isn’t the case. Many women that I don’t know personally, who haven’t necessarily been referred by one of my customers, book appointments online. They find it convenient to know my availability so quickly. It’s a comment I hear all the time.”</p>
<p>&#8220;I spend a lot less time on the phone thanks to online appointment booking. Before, I used to listen to my voicemails at the end of each appointment, and I always had a ton of them. I rarely have to call back clients anymore, yet my calendar is fully booked for the next two months. In fact, I have more appointments than I had last fall, before I started using booxi. &#8221;</p>
<p>&#8220;Another thing I noticed, and it’s something that I found very surprising, is that I used to have a waiting list. So if I ever had a cancellation, some clients asked me to call them and offer the available time slot.</p>
<p>Now when I have a cancellation, another appointment quickly replaces the time slot that became available. I realize that my customers are often on the lookout, and they’ve started going to my website to see if there are any available time slots. They have the opportunity to book their appointment before I even have time to call them back. It’s wonderful.&#8221;</p>
<p>&#8220;I even had to make small adjustments to the way I managed appointment bookings. I offer a free retouching session, 4 to 6 weeks after the first appointment. Before using booxi I used to schedule the free retouching, directly with the customer, during the appointment. Today, because I’m booked two months in advance, I encourage my customers to go online and book their free session immediately. This way they’ll get a spot as quickly as possible.&#8221;</p>
<p><img class="img_zoom aligncenter size-full wp-image-1159" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/QQHRo2TbyftrqlpuqhodQd1UxebOFHc7H3dAMDlEb-4CiUaZndGfn7vzmT6E3vIh8_GlnzI8FyKTMhmIzcQfmw=s0" alt="annie banville services" /></p>
<h2><b>Do you have a </b><b>favourite</b><b> feature?</b></h2>
<p>“Patient files!</p>
<p>Because I can link a customer file to a photo in just a few clicks, it makes it super simple to do follow ups. When I was working with paper files, I had to print my pictures every week and file them without making a mistake, which took a lot of extra time.</p>
<p>Now everything is easily and quickly within reach: photos, notes from each appointment and even notes from conversations. It really helps me with my follow-ups. I can easily remember all my customers and the treatments they’ve had long before they arrive, even after several years. Obviously, I was keeping tracking of all this when I was using paper files, but today it’s more visual and I can access everything much faster and remember the face of every customer before their appointment. This helps ensure a much personalized customer experience.”</p>
<p>&#8220;Another feature that saves me a lot of time is the ability to link a health form in a confirmation email. It’s sent automatically and my customers can fill it out before their appointment. Again, everything is online, so it’s helped me eliminate paper completely, which in turns helps me save lots of space. What’s more, when customers arrive for their appointments, the form is already completed. That saves about 20 minutes, which used to be spent at the beginning of each appointment.&#8221;</p>
<p>“Finally, I really like the thank you message that’s automatically sent to my customers once their appointment is done. It really puts a bow on the customer experience.”</p>
<h2>How was your first experience with booxi?</h2>
<p>&#8220;booxi got me out of my comfort zone. At first I was uncomfortable without my paper agenda, but I knew I had to do it. I was super comfortable with paper, but I read an article that said by 2020, more than 80% of all people will shop and book online. I was well aware that this was the future and I think it was important to face up to it. Of course it was uncomfortable to change, but the feeling was very temporary and the results have definitely been worth it. Really, it’s only been positive since I made the switch.”</p>
<p>&#8220;It was very simple to set up the account and I liked doing it. It was really easy to understand. It took me about two weeks to set it up, but I’m very perfectionist, so I spent a lot of time choosing photos and thinking about what I was going to write in my descriptions. Only when my account was just right did I put it online.”</p>
<p>&#8220;All my customers, whatever their age, love using it and tell me that it’s part of the customer experience. Even customers older than 60 use it. They all arrive at their appointment very satisfied. The confirmation message, the reminders and the thank you message all have a positive impact. Being self-employed, I really feel that it sets my business, and my service, apart.”</p>
<p>“There’s no way I’d be able to work without it today. I’m so happy I took the leap. When I hear people having doubts about using this kind of system, I think to myself “if they only knew”. I feel so much more zen since I started using booxi. It reduced my workload and allowed me to really focus on my passion and creativity.&#8221;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.booxi.com/blog/testimonial-permanent-makeup/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>&#8220;No Phone When I am With Customers!&#8221;</title>
		<link>https://www.booxi.com/blog/testimonial-esthetique-isa-belle/</link>
		<comments>https://www.booxi.com/blog/testimonial-esthetique-isa-belle/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2017 21:48:53 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Astrid Bertout]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Testimonials]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Owners]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[time saving]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.booxi.com/blog/?p=1029</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Find out how Isabelle Perrault, self-employed professional and owner of Esthétique Isa-Belle, has saved a lot of time and has increased her clientele since she started using booxi.
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img class="float_top" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/N_AOSkHZovkvY0mKW0Eei80pi9NgnWyY0WC75anS3hn0ceN9-qayvSBindfBiwhaFJBcoeHTXxyAnvD0HsXFkQ=s0" alt="IsabellePerrault_PostImage_Test2" /><br />
Isabelle is a self-employed professional in esthetic and the owner of <a href="https://www.facebook.com/EsthetiqueIsabelle82/">Esthétique Isa-Belle</a>.</p>
<p>5 years ago she was still very attached to her paper agenda. However her husband convinced her that online appointment booking had become a real competitive advantage, and that she needed to simplify the way customers book with her. In addition she was aware of the insane amount of time she spends over the phone to manage her schedule. These arguments brought her to use an appointment booking solution.</p>
<p>Isabelle had evaluated several solutions available on the market and started to use one of them for a while, to only find out about booxi later. When she tried booxi, she was immediately pleased withthe design, the simplicity of using it and by the booking experience it offers to her customers. So she decided to switch to booxi, and in few hours only she was ready to run her business with it.</p>
<p>Ever since, <em><span style="color: #999999">«this change has only been positive»</span></em> for Isabelle.</p>
<h3 style="text-align: center">  <b>90% of her customers book online, a huge timesaving.<br />
</b></h3>
<p><img class="vertitop_right wp-image-1038 aligncenter" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/Dz1mz4MceOZLHc61Bdxr0T6MFWwfUqXr5zRCZtHYmStgTWEUtKz-6fjQJF3FhKO--XjzI49Fw3av6Gq7i2gFdA=s0" alt="online appointment" width="290" height="290" /><br />
Why?</p>
<p style="text-align: center"><em><span style="color: #999999">«Because they can book appointments whenever they want, wherever they are, and it’s easy to do it.»</span></em></p>
<p>Moreover, Isabelle has noticed that most appointments are booked after 9 PM. Some of them are even booked during the night or very early in the morning, while she is closed. Customers no longer need to call during their work hours, and they no longer hit the voicemail.</p>
<p>Appointments are automatically booked and Isabelle has a full schedule while hardly receiving any calls nor getting messages on her voicemail.</p>
<h3 style="text-align: center"><b>A huge decrease in phone calls.<img class="img_zoom aligncenter  wp-image-1037" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/2uf9BAKEO2WhSqSctNTx5apNvrTI-iWsikfqmDDkG52Qb81gpVcGBsDyk8mjshVPNCcZr3plfre4VVL-P_Ip=s0" alt="simplify-appointment-booking" width="465" height="423" /></b></h3>
<p>Isabelle has always carefully respected one important rule:</p>
<p style="text-align: center"><em><span style="color: #999999">«No phone when I’m with a customer!»</span></em></p>
<p>Which is why before using booxi, her customers were leaving voicemails, which she had to take on her free time to call them back by appointments priority, at the risk of getting in their voicemail in her turn, leaving another message. This endless exchange was a huge waste of time for both her and her customers.</p>
<p>Now, with booxi, Isabelle is much more efficient: if customers call and they get the voicemail, the message tells them they can book online or leave a message. No more waste of time on the phone.</p>
<p>She has increased the frequency of existing customers’ appointments, because they can now book when it’s the best time for them, and they find that really easy.</p>
<h3 style="text-align: center"></h3>
<h3 style="text-align: center"><b>Simplified booking with instant adoption by customers</b></h3>
<p>Finally with the “spacing after” feature, it’s easy for Isabelle to automatically include a busy time slot after each appointment without changing the customer’s appointment duration, and avoiding any confusion. Isabelle knows that she will have the time to clean up and to prepare the room for the next appointment, even when customers book appointments themselves. With booxi customers know how long their appointment is, and Isabelle can optimize her schedule.</p>
<p><img class="img_zoom size-full wp-image-1039 aligncenter" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/ioVJ2X8Dn-eMInopCISGYfqhpADUUmi8c9QAZd9gDxl-lTDvNjyN3HUuFzQeJ4f_NU6mK_zRYKdhGWEfg7cmocw=s0" alt="busy time slot" /></p>
<p>Isabelle found booxi very easy to set up and to use. It’s also the feedback of her customers: <em><span style="color: #999999">«It’s simple and easy to understand. Moreover one of my customer is 73 years old and she easily books her appointments with booxi.»</span></em></p>
<p>Since Isabelle started offering online appointment booking with booxi, she has acquired lots of new customers!</p>
<p style="text-align: center"><em><span style="color: #999999">«People want to simplify their lives, so if you help them to do it they will be happy and talk about it.»</span></em></p>
<p style="text-align: left">Online appointment booking is a great competitive advantage and Isabelle knows it.</p>
<p style="text-align: center"><a href="https://www.booxi.com/business/signup" class="creativ-shortcode creativ-shortcode-button creativ-shortcode-button-colour-allgreen creativ-shortcode-button-size-medium creativ-shortcode-button-edge-rounded" target="_blank">Get Started</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.booxi.com/blog/testimonial-esthetique-isa-belle/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Grow your beauty salon’s revenues by more than 17&#160;000$ per year</title>
		<link>https://www.booxi.com/blog/grow-your-beauty-salons-revenues-by-more-than-17000-per-year/</link>
		<comments>https://www.booxi.com/blog/grow-your-beauty-salons-revenues-by-more-than-17000-per-year/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2017 15:14:23 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Astrid Bertout]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Testimonials]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.booxi.com/blog/?p=891</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Through Marie's success, find out how to make a beauty salon successful and quickly increase the income!]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img class="float_top aligncenter wp-image-1148 size-full" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-ekaUZ1mt0Q5Tc6cj6wTqiddu3VmoWKYIh19X0mAe5ykYHvBJm-h4T01OWMJVUD88kl_vz8tl3FSseJj_92u=s0" alt="Marie Leblanc testimonial" width="1200" height="390" />Marie is the owner of the beauty <a href="http://www.esthetiquemarieleblanc.com/">Salon Marie Leblanc Esthétique</a>. With a team of 5 people and very busy weeks with more than 140 appointments, the management of her members’ schedules was taking her too much time. In addition a lot of customers were forgetting about their appointment.</p>
<h2><img class="verti_top alignleft wp-image-925" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/DJiMoF2e1wDQjeYTbpARUPfgMqnkY63FZgfxa5H-73-i4TyOh_36rXLRJ-iqYWANNX9PvPRYRIE4IDfyyIogRw=s0" alt="no more no-shows" width="69" height="69" /></h2>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h2>No more no-shows!</h2>
<p>Before using booxi, Marie had about 5 no-shows per week. Now she has a maximum of 1. At about 40$ per appointment, that’s about 160$ per week, or 640$ per month. It means more than 7680$ of additional revenues per year.</p>
<p style="text-align: center"><em> </em></p>
<p style="text-align: center"><img class="img_zoom aligncenter size-full wp-image-926" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/4rWvDxwBQu0Z1EK9TqCfj4X0whRrLi0oy3qnREg1n5dEQy8bxmsMLHk08CJ5tDMOPve1TaH8-NX3CeVrdPZl_w=s0" alt="marie-leblanc-team" /><br />
<span style="color: #999999">“All my customers get a reminder by sms. I love it, I have full confidence, they know that they have an appointment at a certain time the next day. A radical change for us!”</span><br />
<span style="color: #808080">— Marie Leblanc</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Marie is a special case: a receptionist was managing all the calls and appointments for the beauty salon and for the hair salon next door. Marie was spending 800$ each month.</p>
<p>With booxi, 40% of her customers book now online, directly from her website or <a href="https://www.facebook.com/Centre-dEsth%C3%A9tique-Marie-Leblanc-267430483278142/">her Facebook page</a>. As she doesn’t have a receptionist anymore, she earns an additional 9600$ per year.</p>
<h2><img class="verti_top alignleft wp-image-923" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/1Q1ZVOcTudMAqz0oru68nsaE3Jjl8Pl-DMWUxc3U7doMUcehzqFaOEAynz_0LXTcBmhfw0-9Py6If9qi8Pd0Qw4=s0" alt="clients_plus_b" width="69" height="69" /><br />
New customers</h2>
<p>In addition booxi brings her new customers. In 6 months, about 15 news customers have chosen her salon because she offers online appointment booking. Online appointment booking is a real competitive advantage and a considerable source of revenues.</p>
<p>Just imagine that these 15 new customers only came once in the past 6 months. At about 40$ per appointment, it represents: 40$ x 15 = 600$.</p>
<h2><img class="verti_top wp-image-935 alignleft" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/IwYzexK5lZazgcnXeW0SHIqqismAxmjU3xNLPyGv8p-Ps-_pzxL41Hl76ztqRQMc1HFZDmFFP-mcAjbu-0ceJwg=s0" alt="augmenter la fréquence des rendez-vous" width="69" height="69" /><br />
Increased frequency of visits</h2>
<p>Finally Marie has also noted that her customers come more regularly. Indeed before using booxi, customers were wasting time trying to book an appointment. First they had to think about it during open hours, that means often during their own working hours, and then they had to wait until the receptionist is free.<br />
Now, with booxi, they can book wherever they are and when they think about it, even passed midnight, taking the time they want.</p>
<hr class="dash" />
<p><span class="bx_text28"><span style="color: #555555">At the end of the year,</span></span><strong><span class="bx_text28"> Marie <span style="color: #555555">gets more than </span><span style="color: #44ce5e">17 300$</span> </span></strong><span class="bx_text28"><span style="color: #555555">using booxi.</span></span></p>
<p>With a yearly plan at less than 480$ per year, the return on investment*, about 3500%, has been largely proven.</p>
<div class="creativ-shortcode creativ-shortcode-cols  creativ-shortcode-cols-half-half "><br />
<div class="creativ-shortcode creativ-shortcode-col creativ-shortcode-col-a"><div class="creativ-shortcode-col-inner"><p><a href="https://booxi-live-wp-storage.storage.googleapis.com/cost_en.png"><img class="img_zoom aligncenter wp-image-945 size-full" src="https://booxi-live-wp-storage.storage.googleapis.com/cost_en.png" alt="" width="380" height="200" /></a></p>
</div></div><div class="creativ-shortcode creativ-shortcode-col creativ-shortcode-col-b"><div class="creativ-shortcode-col-inner"><p><img class="img_zoom aligncenter wp-image-968 size-full" src="https://booxi-live-wp-storage.storage.googleapis.com/return_on_investment.png" alt="return on investment" width="380" height="200" /></p>
</div></div></div>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p style="text-align: center;font-weight: 200"><span class="bx_text24"><img class="img_zoom alignnone wp-image-939" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/W3dTBSKBB-Nld5tBxydix2TiBrNVCQrVkPH7tO_6oS8dxwLY0rT9FoEp2KMNGpi18bvNHVbN2SVSMX8UnM5wrg=s0" alt="roi-calculation" width="476" height="87" /></span></p>
<h5 style="text-align: center">Calculate how much more your business could earn</h5>
<p style="text-align: center"><a href="https://www.booxi.com/roi?utm_source=blog&amp;utm_campaign=testimonial-marie-eng&amp;utm_medium=CTA" class="creativ-shortcode creativ-shortcode-button creativ-shortcode-button-colour-allgreen creativ-shortcode-button-size-medium creativ-shortcode-button-edge-straight" target="_blank">Take the test</a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.booxi.com/blog/grow-your-beauty-salons-revenues-by-more-than-17000-per-year/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>