<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>booxi &#187; Call to Action</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.booxi.com/blog/tag/call-to-action/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.booxi.com/blog</link>
	<description>booxi</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2017 18:59:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
		<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
		<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>http://wordpress.org/?v=3.9.1</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Bring your website to the top of Search Engines results</title>
		<link>https://www.booxi.com/blog/bring-your-website-to-the-top-of-search-engines-results/</link>
		<comments>https://www.booxi.com/blog/bring-your-website-to-the-top-of-search-engines-results/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2016 20:58:38 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Astrid Bertout]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Business Tips]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Call to Action]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[online visibility]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.booxi.com/blog/?p=473</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Our partner Webself explains how to bring your website to the top of Search Engines results for free. ]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img class="float_top aligncenter wp-image-483" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/2xuORUCqGcmtmCT1lEjJM15QDe9UXmShd4GC8-OmZpFl1sQhZDOKjkHvhhDT2uMsx0qAEmI1jj22eFaZFBYBmA=s0" alt="improve SEO ranking" width="850" height="425" /><br />
You probably have asked yourself this question before: why isn’t my website on the first page of results on search engines? There are several explanations and answers to this question, but if you put effort into the SEO optimization of your website, you increase your chances to find yourself at the top of the list! First of all, <a href="http://www.webopedia.com/TERM/S/SEO.html">search engine optimization</a> is a methodology of strategies, techniques and tactics used to increase the amount of visitors to a website by obtaining a high-ranking placement in the search results page of a search engine (SERP) &#8212; including Google, Bing, Yahoo and other search engines.</p>
<p>Unfortunately, SEO is not done in one easy task! In fact, for Google or other search engines to give you as much importance as you deserve, you must make a constant effort in optimizing different aspects of your site. Meta descriptions, tags and H title, content and links. Today our partner <a href="http://en.webself.net/">Webself </a>presents the different kinds of links and their importance for the SEO optimization of your website!</p>
<h2>Internal links</h2>
<p>Internal links are simple redirections to other pages of your website. Internal links can be used differently, like <a href="http://en.webself.net/blog/2016/07/12/how-to-maximize-the-impact-of-your-call-to-action-buttons-">Call-to-Action buttons</a>, or clickable words / sentences. For example, many choose to add a &#8220;Contact&#8221; button on their homepage to quickly redirect clients to their contact information if needed. Another example may be a particular service company, like a interior designer or a house painter. A button &#8220;Click here for a quote,&#8221; may be interesting for the customers who don’t want to waste time searching for the submission form everywhere on the website. The more internal links you have, the more visitors spend time on your site, which will greatly increase the credibility (according to search engines) of your site, therefore the SEO.<br />
<img class="shadow_medium aligncenter wp-image-477" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/hjOn3hkJM4N2Bp4hfSMAcrP7yG9F9-ialm35Mm1CVF8JOB9tXomDmL4aFofrAQ-xHhB0hH7iulIGBZ6zR4_6=s0" alt="call to action" width="824" height="504" /></p>
<h2>External links</h2>
<p>Backlinks are all links that will make your visitors “enter” your website. First, it is important to “get links” from popular pages and prioritize quality over quantity. There are several choices available to you if you are wondering how to get those backlinks directed to your website. Have you ever heard of comparison websites? If you sell a web product, these sites are product comparators made by people who have tried several and ranking them according to their experience as well as some comments and tips. Being on these sites gives visibility to your site, but only if those comments are positive, obviously. Another example? If you are a hotel, it would be nice to get links from sites like <a href="https://www.tripadvisor.ca/">TripAdvisor</a>, but also directory sites, tourist offices or your local website. No matter your industry, you will find many websites where you you could increase your web traffic by figuring on them. You can also create partnerships with companies that have either a similar target audience or an audience you want to reach. Building partnerships can be interesting in terms of visibility, but also for services trades, blog article exchanges, promotion on social networks, and much more! Speaking of social networks, link them to your website to reach as many people as possible.</p>
<p>Other ideas</p>
<ul>
<li>Participating in industry-related forums</li>
<li>Contact newspapers, bloggers, etc. to increase your visibility</li>
</ul>
<h3>Outgoing links</h3>
<p>You guessed it, outbound links are links that leave your site and redirect your visitors to another website than yours! Remember to redirect people to another site using a new tab or pop-up window (so they don’t “actually” leave your website). The goal is not to make people leave, but to redirect them to pages or websites that might interest them. For example, a partner website, an important source of information or tools to maximize their customer experience!</p>
<p>To conclude, it is important to focus on quality over quantity. Review your website several times a month to make sure that the links still work, you don’t want to send your visitors to a page that is &#8220;closed&#8221;, &#8220;missing&#8221; or that simply do not exist!</p>
<hr />
<p><a href="http://en.webself.net/">Webself </a>is a free and easy tool to create website. Choose your design, add your texts and pictures and publish your website on the Internet. It has never been easier to create a website! No computer knowledge required, only your imagination ! Start building your own website today.</p>
<p><a href="http://en.webself.net/"><img class="aligncenter wp-image-289 size-full" src="https://booxi-live-wp-storage.storage.googleapis.com/2016-08-26.jpg" alt="webself banner" width="1440" height="600" /></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.booxi.com/blog/bring-your-website-to-the-top-of-search-engines-results/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Add Online Booking to Facebook</title>
		<link>https://www.booxi.com/blog/facebook-online-appointment-booking/</link>
		<comments>https://www.booxi.com/blog/facebook-online-appointment-booking/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2016 16:35:38 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Astrid Bertout]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Tutorials]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Facebook Page]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Call to Action]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[online booking]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.booxi.com/blog-dev/?p=66</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Social networks receive a lot of daily traffic, why not get the most out of your Facebook page and turn some of those visitors into customers. This article will introduce Facebook Business Pages as well as adding online booking to your facebook page.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="float_top creativ-shortcode creativ-shortcode-video-embed"><iframe class="post_vid_iframe" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/Z4h1FK88C_E" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div>
<p>As you know consumers increasingly spend time on social networks. Most of you, self-employed professionals and small business owners, probably already have a Facebook business page. The main reason for that, is to get additional visibility and new customers. Some of you may even receive appointment requests by Facebook messages which is time consuming as you and your customers may not always answer promptly.</p>
<p>Obviously, the main objective of this visibility is to get customers to book appointments.<br />
Let’s see how to get more appointments with less effort using your Facebook Business Page.</p>
<h3>How to Add Online Appointment Booking to Your Facebook Page?</h3>
<p>If you already use an online appointment booking solution, like booxi, you can easily add online appointment booking directly from your Facebook Business page. It allows your customers to instantly book an appointment with you, so they won&#8217;t forget or book with your competitors. Some of you may still be using a paper calendar, so I would strongly suggest to take a look at a simple solution like booxi to enable online appointment booking and save hours off the phone. 20% of your customers will start booking online as soon as you have online booking, that is a 6 to 8 hours of time savings per month.</p>
<p>Some online appointment booking solutions give you the opportunity to confirm and control every online booking, as well as automatically send confirmation by emails for all your booking. In addition it can send reminders by emails or text messages (SMS). All these features save you a tone of time, decrease your no-shows, and improve the quality of your service.</p>
<h3>Facebook</h3>
<p>Add online appointment booking directly from your Facebook page is a cinch.</p>
<p>Let’s start by copying your booxi URL</p>
<p>From your booxi account, complete the following steps:</p>
<ol>
<li>Click on My Business tab from the main menu.</li>
<li>Click on Business Details.</li>
<li>Scroll down to the section booxi site.<img class="shadow_medium aligncenter wp-image-184 size-large" src="http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/RuOxJ-u079o5r8lwPMRjiCa3ZwRr2drsYGo3jgbKa7QBpUBz2jTvuHuzaNpJpA5qfjUy5HL4s-eota6-lqcvyg=s1024" alt="booxi interface" width="1024" height="1024" /></li>
<li>Select the URL and copy it to paste it later on Facebook.</li>
</ol>
<p>Then let’s Add your Book Now button on Facebook</p>
<ul>
<li>Open your Business Facebook Page and</li>
<li>Below your cover picture, you should find the option “Add a button”. If you have already added a call-to-action button, you should have access to the option “Edit Button” to replace this button, because you are allowed to have only one call to action at the same time.</li>
<li>Click on Add a Button or Edit Button to configure it.<img class="shadow_medium aligncenter wp-image-181 size-full" src="https://booxi-live-wp-storage.storage.googleapis.com/add-a-button.jpg" alt="Facebook Online booking " width="909" height="829" /></li>
<li>The following pop-up will appear. Select Book Now among the button options.<img class="shadow_medium aligncenter wp-image-183 size-full" src="https://booxi-live-wp-storage.storage.googleapis.com/book-now2-e1472868573768.jpg" alt="Facebook Book Buton" width="752" height="430" /></li>
<li>Paste your booxi URL. At the end of it, you can add ?book=now so the online appointment booking automatically appears.</li>
<li>Click on Create, if it is your first call to action on Facebook or on Save Changes if you just modified it.</li>
</ul>
<h3>And You’re Done!</h3>
<p>Your customers can now book appointment online with you. From that point, you may post once a month an invitation to book appointments online, just to remind your customers that they can do it. This small addition will allow you to save a lot of time , and customers can even book outside your business hours, without leaving voicemail. How wonderful is that?</p>
<hr />
<p>Make it easy for your customers to book with you by addind online booking directly on your Facebook page.</p>
<p style="text-align: center"><a href="https://www.booxi.com/features#online-appointment-booking" class="creativ-shortcode creativ-shortcode-button creativ-shortcode-button-colour-allgreen creativ-shortcode-button-size-medium creativ-shortcode-button-edge-straight" target="_blank">Learn More</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.booxi.com/blog/facebook-online-appointment-booking/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>