<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>booxi &#187; presentation</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.booxi.com/blog/tag/presentation/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.booxi.com/blog</link>
	<description>booxi</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2017 18:59:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
		<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
		<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>http://wordpress.org/?v=3.9.1</generator>
	<item>
		<title>booxi at The Salon de la beauté au CFP des Riverains</title>
		<link>https://www.booxi.com/blog/booxi-at-the-salon-de-la-beaute-au-cfp-des-riverains/</link>
		<comments>https://www.booxi.com/blog/booxi-at-the-salon-de-la-beaute-au-cfp-des-riverains/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2016 16:58:49 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Astrid Bertout]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[affordable solution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Owners]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[presentation]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.booxi.com/blog-dev/?p=73</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Did you know that booxi offers presentations and training? Find out all the details in this article.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The objective of this event was to introduce students and visitors to the latest innovations in the industry. booxi was there in partnership with <a href="http://toncoiffeur.com">toncoiffeur.com</a> to present its smart solution <img class="alignright" src="https://4.bp.blogspot.com/-l9iQMrxLW7k/Vz4vBZJYg3I/AAAAAAAAAYY/UVENGRAkPSkk5IZIwvw8aBIVqyhfyw9RQCLcB/s1600/toncoiffeur.JPG" alt="" />for businesses with multiple employees and self-employed professionals working alone. booxi is a <strong>breakthrough for students who want to start a business</strong>, an a game changer for established businesses.</p>
<p>Students and businesses see booxi as an opportunity to avoid spending between $3,000 to $10,000 to create a website, buy a legacy salon management software and networked computers. <strong>With a small budget</strong>, from $17 to $34 per month ($200 to $400 per year), <strong>they will have all they need</strong> : an automated website, a customers list (CRM), online booking solution, automated confirmation and reminders by text and email, and more. This very easy-to-use solution allows them to be, more efficient than most of their competitors in no time.</p>
<p><img class="alignleft" src="https://4.bp.blogspot.com/-0m5M65eFlEs/Vz4vLFgGVDI/AAAAAAAAAYc/OtjZnhwQaiwkKykA16vluEWHC7s2XDweQCLcB/s1600/formation.JPG" alt="" /></p>
<p>The solution enables them <strong>to get more results with less efforts</strong>, specifically by spending less time on the phone, on administrative tasks and on marketing. So <strong>they can focus on what they really love to do</strong>: spend time with their clients.</p>
<p>In the context of its mission to help professionals be more successful, booxi wishes to inform students of <strong>the importance to have a good online visibility</strong>, and use affordable / free and easy-to-use tools that are available to them to<strong> manage their business more efficiently.</strong></p>
<p>We invite students to talk about booxi to their teachers, and schools to contact us to help them inform their students of the challenges and opportunities that will be presented to them when they graduate, through an <strong>educational presentation provided by booxi</strong>.</p>
<hr />
<p>Do you want to learn more about our school training? Learn about the topics of our presentation and send us your request.</p>
<p style="text-align: left"><a href="https://docs.google.com/a/booxi.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLSfhxM5d9SHJazGz8_7gYLBpl2JBu7608RJoNVY1g1CRRspNjQ/viewform" class="creativ-shortcode creativ-shortcode-button creativ-shortcode-button-colour-allgreen creativ-shortcode-button-size-medium creativ-shortcode-button-edge-straight" target="_blank">Presentation Request</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.booxi.com/blog/booxi-at-the-salon-de-la-beaute-au-cfp-des-riverains/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>