<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>booxi &#187; Stripe Payment</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.booxi.com/blog/tag/stripe-payment/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.booxi.com/blog</link>
	<description>booxi</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2017 18:59:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
		<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
		<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>http://wordpress.org/?v=3.9.1</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Use Stripe to Accept Online Booking &amp; Credit Card Payments</title>
		<link>https://www.booxi.com/blog/stripe/</link>
		<comments>https://www.booxi.com/blog/stripe/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2017 22:00:56 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Astrid Bertout]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Tutorials]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Goup scheduling]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[online payment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stripe Payment]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.booxi.com/blog/?p=1003</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[With Stripe, you can easily accept online payment at the time of booking, thanks to the full integration with booxi.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img class="float_top aligncenter wp-image-1024 size-full" src="https://booxi-live-wp-storage.storage.googleapis.com/stripe.png" alt="Stripe" width="1200" height="418" /><br />
<a href="https://stripe.com/ca" target="_blank">Stripe</a> is a very easy to use payment processor. Fully integrated with booxi, Stripe allows you to easily accept credit card online payments at the time of booking. Whether you need to capture a full payment, deposit, or a booking fee when customers book online with you, booxi made it simple for you and your customer to do so.</p>
<p>You can now choose to request an online payment for any of your services, and for both appointment bookings and group reservations. Requesting a payment can contribute in reducing no-shows, as well as simplify your cancellation fees management. This article shows you how easy it is to do it, by using Stripe.</p>
<p>Features:</p>
<ul>
<li>Request a full or partial payment per service for appointments or reservations.</li>
<li>Accept online payment at booking time, or via email.</li>
<li>See which appointments or reservations have been paid in your calendar.</li>
<li>Review the payment details per appointment or reservation.</li>
<li>Charge, refund and get payment reports using Stripe.</li>
</ul>
<h2 style="text-align: center"><b>Activate Your Stripe Account</b></h2>
<p>booxi supports <a href="https://stripe.com/ca" target="_blank">Stripe</a> which is one of the most trusted online payment processor. In order to start using it with booxi, you will need to create your Stripe account, and activate the Stripe module in booxi. This will enable and show the hidden online payment options in booxi.</p>
<p>Steps:</p>
<ol>
<li>Sign in your booxi account, and click on My Business</li>
<li>Select the Business Module section, and scroll down to the Stripe module.<img class="img_zoom aligncenter size-full wp-image-1004" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/I9lOdfLXaZhoSevcM5QZKFwZ7ZJpmR6OtgL6_X-gkY5Ljb0WVxsUpQp8MDZPM4pYnqdMi5SHFY_ZqKLxjkk3HU4=s0" alt="booxi business Module" /></li>
<li>Turn the module on by clicking on the ON/OFF switch &#8211; a setup dialog will pop up.<img class="shadow_small aligncenter wp-image-1005 size-full" src="https://booxi-live-wp-storage.storage.googleapis.com/stripe-online-payment.png" alt="Stripe Online Payment" width="548" height="273" /></li>
<li>Click on Sign in Stripe, and if you already have a Stripe account, use the Sign in link at the top of the pop up dialog; if you don’t, complete the signup form underneath to create your new Stripe account.</li>
<li>To link (sign in) your existing Stripe account, simply provide your Stripe account email and password when asked, and continue with the following steps, but you must have an existing Stripe account to continue.</li>
<li>The setup dialog will ask you to provide your tax informations so we can correctly calculate taxes for your customer’s online payment. If you only have one tax, leave the second one blank and to 0%.<img class="shadow_medium aligncenter wp-image-1007 size-full" src="https://booxi-live-wp-storage.storage.googleapis.com/complete-tax-rate-configuration1.png" alt="Stripe Set up" width="603" height="848" /></li>
<li>When done click Save and you are done.</li>
</ol>
<h2 style="text-align: center">How to accept online payments with Stripe?</h2>
<p>Now that you have activated your Online Payment Module, you can choose to request a payment for any of your services, simply by adjusting their online payment settings.</p>
<ul>
<li>You will be able to request a full payment of the service, or a fix amount for example as a deposit or reservation fee.</li>
<li>This payment can be requested at the online booking, or by email just after the online booking is completed, leaving more time to pay.</li>
<li>If a customer does not complete the payment at online booking (not by email) within 15 minutes, his reservation will be automatically canceled; without requiring you to do anything.</li>
</ul>
<p>To adjust the online payment settings of a service.</p>
<ol>
<li>Go to your service list and select a service for which you would like to request payment.</li>
<li>From that service profile, click on Details to open the Edit Details form on the right, and scroll down to locate the Online Payment settings (these will only be shown if you have activated your online payment processor module).</li>
<li>Select the option to request payment At Online Booking or By Email, or select Disabled (no payment requested).</li>
<li>Set the Required Payment amount, to the full amount of the service, or a fix amount, for example 10% as a deposit.</li>
<li>Click on Save, and you’re done. When a customer books an appointment online for this service, a payment will be requested.<img class="shadow_medium  aligncenter wp-image-1008 size-full" src="https://booxi-live-wp-storage.storage.googleapis.com/price-per-service.png" alt="Online Payments &amp; Booking" width="576" height="573" /></li>
</ol>
<p>Remember that if you set a required amount equal to the total service price, booxi will assume that you want to charge the service in full, so if the total to be paid varies when booking (for example multiple attendees), the total amount will be requested. Also, if you book multiple services, you can mix services that require a payment in full, partial, or even no payment, and booxi will calculate the amount in respect of each service settings.</p>
<p><i>booxi currently only support online payment for group reservations.<img class="shadow_medium alignright wp-image-1009 size-full" src="https://booxi-live-wp-storage.storage.googleapis.com/online-payment.png" alt="Stripe payment" width="301" height="483" /></i></p>
<h2 style="text-align: center"><b>Your Clients Can Pay Online in Simplicity</b></h2>
<p>When booking online, your client will be informed that a payment is required, just before confirming his booking. Once he has confirmed his booking, he will be requested to pay online using any major credit cards through the secured Stripe online payment system, within the booxi booking process.</p>
<ul>
<li>If the payment is successfully completed, the client will receive an appointment confirmation email from booxi, and a payment confirmation email from Stripe.</li>
<li>If the payment fails, the appointment will be automatically cancelled within 15 minutes, and both you and the client will be informed of that by alert and email.</li>
<li>Since communication is important here, the client must provide an email address at booking when a payment is required.</li>
</ul>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h2 style="text-align: center"><b>You Can Easily Track Who Paid Online</b></h2>
<p>As clients book and complete their online required payments, you can see who paid online and track what is left to be paid.</p>
<ul>
<li>Each reservation will inform you of the current payment status and the associated balance to be paid.</li>
<li>Each appointment will indicate if a payment has been requested and completed.</li>
</ul>
<p>Color status quickly inform you of what to expect in terms of payment.</p>
<ul>
<li>Bleu when a payment has been requested and you await this payment from the client.</li>
<li>Yellow when a balance is left and you need to request that payment.</li>
<li>Green when everything is paid.<img class="shadow_small aligncenter wp-image-1010 size-full" src="https://booxi-live-wp-storage.storage.googleapis.com/requested-payment.png" alt="Stripe enabled" width="291" height="83" /></li>
</ul>
<p><i>booxi currently only tracks online payment information, so you need to continue tracking payment the way you use to, while taking advantage of accepting online payment</i></p>
<h2 style="text-align: center"><b>Capture Payment in Person or Over the Phone</b></h2>
<p>For any reservation or appointment, you can process an online payment, or capture that a manual payment was completed. This means that you can complete an online payment by typing in the client’s credit card information, by send an online payment request to the client by email, or by registering that a payment was completed manually cash, or using physical payment processor terminal. This way you can track all your reservations and appointments payment status.</p>
<p>To capture payment information:</p>
<ol>
<li>Right click on an appointment or a reservation and select Pay to open the payment dialog.</li>
<li>Or open an appointment or reservation and select the top menu and option Pay.</li>
<li>You may also set a required amount for a new appointment or reservation before saving it the first time, and the Payment pop up will automatically open.</li>
</ol>
<p>To capture an online payment for your client, using his credit card information, follow these steps:</p>
<ol>
<li>Set the payment method to Using Stripe</li>
<li>Set the required amount</li>
<li>Click on Pay</li>
<li>The Stripe payment system will appear and complete the payment providing the client email and credit card information.</li>
<li>The payment status will change for Paid.</li>
</ol>
<p>To send a payment request email to your client, follow these steps:</p>
<ol>
<li>Set the payment method to By Email</li>
<li>Set the required amount</li>
<li>Click on Send.</li>
<li>The payment status will change for Awaiting the payment.</li>
</ol>
<p>To register a manual payment cash or using a payment processor terminal, follow these steps:</p>
<ol>
<li>Set the payment method to Manual</li>
<li>Set the required amount</li>
<li>Click on Pay.</li>
<li>The payment status will change for Paid.</li>
</ol>
<p>For each appointment and reservation, you can expand the payment status to review the details of each payment completed (using Stripe, or manual).</p>
<p><i>booxi currently only allows you to capture payment from online booking.</i></p>
<h2 style="text-align: center"><b>You Have a Complete Access to Your Transactions</b></h2>
<h2 style="text-align: center"><b>and Can Do Refund</b></h2>
<p>From your Stripe dashboard, you can easily find a payment transaction, do a refund to a specific customer, and create simple transaction reports.</p>
<p>This means you can use booxi to accept online payment when clients book online; while you continue to track who paid the way you used to, and consolidate all your payments by adding the online payment report provided by Stripe.</p>
<p><img class="img_zoom aligncenter wp-image-1011 size-full" src="https://booxi-live-wp-storage.storage.googleapis.com/stripe-payment-history.png" alt="Stripe Live test" width="1122" height="584" /></p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.booxi.com/blog/stripe/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>