<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>booxi &#187; online visibility</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.booxi.com/blog/tag/visibility/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.booxi.com/blog</link>
	<description>booxi</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2017 18:59:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
		<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
		<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>http://wordpress.org/?v=3.9.1</generator>
	<item>
		<title>How to add book now button directly on your Webself website?</title>
		<link>https://www.booxi.com/blog/how-to-add-book-now-button-directly-on-your-webself-website/</link>
		<comments>https://www.booxi.com/blog/how-to-add-book-now-button-directly-on-your-webself-website/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2017 14:38:43 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Astrid Bertout]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Tutorials]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[online visibility]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[website]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.booxi.com/blog/?p=1537</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Here is the tutorial to learn how to add online appointment booking directly on your Webself website.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img class="float_top aligncenter wp-image-1550 size-full" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/nDarG9RG95oK7v1li6gcErJC3276LsosdNNeFTQ-9-M-o99X1NXWIZPPMroEVoEq33RKtqvZ5pL0iS-HuToUAg=s0" alt="webself-top" width="1200" height="373" /></p>
<ol>
<li>Sign in your Webself editor, and go on the page where you want to add the book now button.</li>
<li>Click on the section ‘’+ ADD’’ and select the option ‘’Script’’ in the Tools Sections.<br />
Click on it, and drop down it on the desired section.<img class="img_zoom aligncenter wp-image-1551 size-full" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/b6KMQT_6vmpRJIhKEUV2pHbCNq2wdRmRvuvfpzQ1R2gw-JpAamebpYjYBgssNbbRVz2enbPvuc7s9w88M8pw=s0" alt="add section" width="290" height="463" /></li>
<li>This pop will appear:<img class="img_zoom aligncenter size-full wp-image-1552" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/5ybr9C0oRvuC2KxAvXhnj8jv4WGLHIbGWq_tgFkpSKFiMAHQd3kLTBmGyOL9yMoBTJmHJzRQWwTwg_KKJq15=s0" alt="script pop up" /></li>
<li>To generate the code that you’ll past on this pop up:</li>
</ol>
<ul>
<li>You’ll need your booxi API Key.<br />
Here’s how to find it:<br />
Go on My Business tab, and then on the section Business Details. Scroll down to the section API Key and copy the code.</li>
<li>Then go <a href="https://www.booxi.com/developers/booknow" target="_blank">to this page</a> and use the Widget Generator to create the script:<img class="img_zoom aligncenter size-full wp-image-1553" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/egv5RSJe8_GV_2o-C5JTG7UMGuvwlBer8u64Bg45ubpTkn44SflEJNAiOvq27eL-QUai9Wv-5MHLqWd6u7O7Yyc=s0" alt="widget generator" /></li>
</ul>
<p>In the section API Key, paste the code you’ve just copied.<br />
Select the language which you want the text to appear on the button, and select the option ‘’External Popup’’. Then you can customize the text of the button if you want to. Finally click on the button ‘’ Generate the code’’ : a code is generated on the right side.</p>
<p>5. Copy the code generated in the section ‘’Widget Code’’.</p>
<p><img class="img_zoom aligncenter size-full wp-image-1554" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/nsUFxl_nzdPF263-IfbGIPAZs2_SdeV8iZf917_RIpAaBhrg9zDRyl11rpGc3iLxu831UZQJtynxOIHdic8Oni4=s0" alt="widget generated" /></p>
<p>6. And go back to the Editor in Webself.</p>
<p>In the pop-up Script, scroll down to the section ‘’Content code between &lt;body&gt; and &lt;/body&gt; tags. Paste the Widget code you’ve just copied.</p>
<p>7. Go back to the booxi code generator and copy the code in the Widget Container section.</p>
<p><img class="img_zoom aligncenter size-full wp-image-1555" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/Z95pOAxVwexShHksu_E8sbEiTn7p2sz1l-pv3PTWPpMt-5ysuWBb8k4jPzzz4LvblJQ71p5rfWmfoJJBtVjDHWo=s0" alt="book now button code" /></p>
<p>8. In the Webself Editor, paste the code in the first section ‘’Code Content’’.<br />
9. Once again go back to your booxi generator, and copy the code in the section ‘’Book Now Button’’. For example, copy the English one.</p>
<p>10. And finally go back to the Webself Editor and paste the code you’ve just copied in the section ‘’Content code between &lt;head&gt; and &lt;/head&gt; tags.</p>
<p>11. Click on the Update buttons, and then on Save and you’re done.</p>
<p>Your customers can now book appointment directly from your Webself website.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.booxi.com/blog/how-to-add-book-now-button-directly-on-your-webself-website/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Small Businesses &#8211; Use the Web at Your Advantage</title>
		<link>https://www.booxi.com/blog/small-businesses-use-the-web-at-your-advantage/</link>
		<comments>https://www.booxi.com/blog/small-businesses-use-the-web-at-your-advantage/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2017 17:00:17 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Astrid Bertout]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Business Tips]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Owners]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[online visibility]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[website]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.booxi.com/blog/?p=1275</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[With hundreds of new businesses created every day, it is important to stand out. You can't simply offer a quality product or service, you also need to make yourself visible on the web! Here are 3 ways to have a web presence. ]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img class="float_top aligncenter wp-image-1294 size-full" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/thwtcJeYvy4UY2z2SFC6rOTr6PxuKL63TDut3BewTUPhKXBLCQfT-6-ix8SbOrH8uRcMq-ArA8DmuMBaGWnHz3o=s0" alt="webself" width="1171" height="527" />With hundreds of new businesses created every day, it is important to stand out.</p>
<p>You can’t simply offer a quality product or service, you also need to make yourself visible on the web! It is very rare that a company, no matter the sector of activity, isn’t on the web somehow.</p>
<p>According to <a href="http://www.chainstoreage.com/article/study-81-research-online-making-big-purchases" target="_blank">Chainstorage.com</a>, it is said that 80% of consumers search online before shopping; it is therefore important that your customers find you!</p>
<p>Luckily for you, there are several ways to have a web presence; through a website, social networks, newsletters, mobile application, etc.  Today, we talk about three ways you can use the web to your advantage!</p>
<h2>1. Get to know your target market</h2>
<p>One of the first steps in getting a business up and running is to determine who will be your target market, who will benefit from your products or services. If you determine your target audience from the beginning, it will be easier to adapt your content, your visuals, to build your website as well as all of your communications (newsletter, text messaging, social networks).</p>
<p>Why is it important to adapt to your target audience?  Because not only do you want to build a good relationship with your customers by offering them a quality experience, but you also want to increase loyalty. By creating a web community with your potential and current customers you increase the chances of recurrence, good reviews, references, etc.</p>
<p>Competitive intelligence is also important before getting starting your own business. Look at similar businesses, those that offer the same services or are located near you. It will give you a good idea for your pricing, services offered and well as the target market. Keep in mind though, this isn’t to copy, but rather to use the information as a guide or for inspiration.</p>
<p>Try to be as creative as possible on the web. Live videos, Facebook contests, daily Instagram posts, ‘Client of the Month’ articles, all of those are great ideas to create an active web community!</p>
<p>Another advantage of the web? Personalized communication!</p>
<p>The personalization of your posts is very interesting and you should definitely explore all of its advantages! For example, on Facebook, you can sponsor posts that will only reach your target market. You can also collect the names of your customers and use it when sending a monthly newsletter. Customizing will make your customers feel that they are important to you; This is a great way to focus on customer loyalty.</p>
<p><img class="shadow_medium  aligncenter wp-image-1280 size-full" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/7blA2CEd0IT6Rn2ZPlQNGY-1KmvvJ8-I41kk0qDRs_MVjlrhajtiqQI02zLpezamj4vosAxqwLpu3Koimpebpg=s0" alt="feedback" width="901" height="480" /></p>
<h2>2. Listen</h2>
<p>Listening to your customers on the web? It is possible and you should definitely do it! In fact, you can gather valuable information that will help you adjust when it’s time to make some changes or modifications in your business.</p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Observe purchasing behaviors:</strong>
<p>Your customers use your services only once and never come back? Do you have a high recurrence rate? Keep records of your customers to evaluate their purchase behaviors, it will be easy to determine if you need to make changes, for example,  there might be something wrong  if the recurrence rate is very low.</li>
<p></p>
<li><strong>Collect comments:<br />
</strong></p>
<p>If you have the time, try to offer a personalized after-sales service.  Send a thank you email asking the customer for their comments on the product, service, or ask them to submit a review about their experience. Facebook offers a &#8216;review&#8217; section to allow customers to give their opinion based on stars (1 to 5)  as well as leave relevant comments. Do not forget to reply to these comments, whether they are positive or negative!</li>
<li><strong>Participate in forums:</strong>
<p>There are several forums or groups on Facebook where you can gather information. For example, about ten thousand professionals joined a Facebook group called &#8216;Dans la tête des entrepreneurs’. It is not unusual to see people ask for design advice about their website or get more information about marketing tactics. it is very interesting because the answers come from professionals who are there to help you! It’s also a great way to make contacts.</li>
<p></p>
<li><strong>Surveys:</strong>
<p>Surveys are also interesting because they allow you to collect answers of questions you may have. You can add a survey section in your newsletter and ask your customers some monthly questions. Want to offer a new service? Create a survey to see if it could possibly interest your customers. There are several tools to help you, for example, <a href="https://fr.surveymonkey.com/" target="_blank">SurveyMonkey</a>.</li>
<p>
</ul>
<h2>3. Adjust</h2>
<p>By collecting information about your customers and their buying habits, you will be able to adjust when the time comes to make changes. Chances are that you have to be flexible when you&#8217;re in business, and that&#8217;s a good thing, because adjusting to please your target market is a good way to retain your customer base and demonstrate how much you care about them.</p>
<p style="text-align: center"><span class="bx_text24">There’s nothing wrong with modifications!</span></p>
<p>Just be sure to notify your customers. Web platforms are a great way to keep your customers informed on news features or updates. Use them to your advantage by encouraging people to react to your publications, leave comments, share or ask questions. Do not forget that adjustments are not a sign of weakness, on the opposite, it shows your customers your flexibility!</p>
<p>You can also use the newsletters, to talk about upcoming news or changes! Newsletters are an excellent way to build loyalty. Have you ever thought about text message marketing? If it works with your target market, why not try it? It is said that 93% of people have a smartphone and 98% of all text messages are open!</p>
<p>You have every advantage to use the web if you are in business! Not only is it an inexpensive (or even free) solution, but the web could propel your business to another level! Customer loyalty, newsletter, animated social platforms; explore the different ways and see what works with your customers, while having fun!</p>
<p style="text-align: center"><span class="bx_text24">Your idea deserves a great site!<br />
Go to <a href="http://www.webself.net" target="_blank">WebSelf.net</a> to create your own free website today!</span></p>
<p>Webself is a free and easy tool to create website. Choose your design, add your texts and pictures and publish your website on the Internet. It has never been easier to create a website! No computer knowledge required, only your imagination ! Start building your own website today.</p>
<p><a href="http://www.webself.net"><img class="shadow_medium aligncenter wp-image-1295 size-full" src="https://booxi-live-wp-storage.storage.googleapis.com/webself-banner.jpg" alt="create your website " width="1440" height="600" /></a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.booxi.com/blog/small-businesses-use-the-web-at-your-advantage/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Create Your Business Instagram Account : a Step by Step Guide</title>
		<link>https://www.booxi.com/blog/how-to-create-your-business-instagram-account-a-step-by-step-guide/</link>
		<comments>https://www.booxi.com/blog/how-to-create-your-business-instagram-account-a-step-by-step-guide/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2017 18:13:50 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Astrid Bertout]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Tutorials]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[online visibility]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.booxi.com/blog/?p=1180</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Follow this step by step tutorial and create your business Instagram account.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img class="float_top aligncenter wp-image-1238 size-full" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/66LaRlqnPOrUmA74vfNFmj0qvHioWlJX3Q54ak-Us6aX4aOocgFCWnysqIMgKTwksOWSbpDk0C7swuPBJ7zfMQ=s0" alt="create your instagram account" width="1280" height="720" /><br />
Learn how to create your Instagram account by following this step by step guide.</p>
<ol>
<li>From your smartphone, go on your Apple Store or on your Google Play, search for the Instagram application and download it. Once it&#8217;s done, open the app and start to create your account.<img class="shadow_small aligncenter wp-image-1239 size-full" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/AyIASjR4UQXN-iLj3x7cdtqSlKiF0Z6mHPW4KRKlV-4ouyxH4I2rPP1J6_J3MKfIw9q1_4uCFDLLsXSIpZlAz3U=s0" alt="download the app" width="674" height="600" /></li>
<li>It&#8217;s easy to sign up: enter your phone number or your email address.<br />
Add your business name, your password, a picture (you can change it later) and click on Next.<br />
Then create a user name and click on Next.<img class="shadow_small aligncenter wp-image-1244 " src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/bR0nTK9oRgc-ybYt_cojkg8xgFw0wysZDBu0NGXv4rVY7QxeDxll8WRZLnGvQm6ENvV7e91_dVIWODBJjV6j=s0" alt="set-up-your-account" width="713" height="423" /></li>
<li>You can now find contacts with the option &#8220;Connect to Facebook&#8221;.</li>
<li>Then Instagram will make some suggestions, based on the most popular accounts.<br />
<img class="shadow_small aligncenter wp-image-1245 " src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/RUt3RjS_Y4XE12BgV8IgvVkFpD-QdQnfGV2ZtCQTv2fMqQZowQvfvxMMYeQwQeKjhbIwiLeZjNH6UmaodR9wcw=s0" alt="find-contact" width="454" height="404" /></li>
<li>Then you can try the professional features, specific for businesses accounts. Use a Professional Profile to add your business phone number, your business address and your business email address.<br />
You have also access to a Statistic section to analyse which post perform better. This is very useful to optimize your account.<br />
Finally the Promotion section allows you to create promotions to get more visibility and more followers.<img class="shadow_small aligncenter wp-image-1243 " style="padding: 35px" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/aUhWMzfefKTgIyMNh3IqEW2arihSWMPTEd1warcEAVMK-haLJmht_Xg3OR38juW2uG81rE85AdS3ueTCy3h1=s0" alt="switch to business profile" width="1221" height="435" /></li>
<li>To activate the professional account on Instagram, link your Instagram account with your business Facebook Page.<br />
To do it, click on &#8220;Log in with Facebook&#8221;, then click on &#8220;Ok&#8221; in the &#8220;Confirm Login&#8221; page.<br />
Then you can select the Facebook page associated with this Instagram account.<img class="shadow_small aligncenter wp-image-1242 " style="padding: 35px" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/r7pt35UamPEl1geppTNsTmSzDxiwnCRDx42p_reTTVAfrNDsZ1tg6XHEkI1D_ifbWDq9NnnGCqoubKKsJzHCpg=s0" alt="link to your facebook page" width="711" height="422" /></li>
<li>You can then set up your business profile by adding useful information. And now you have access to your profile.<br />
Now make sure to publish picture on a regular basis.<br />
No inspiration? Here is a <a href="https://www.booxi.com/blog/12-creative-ways-to-benefit-from-instagram/" target="_blank">guide with 12 ideas</a>.</li>
<li>Once you publish on a regular basis and you have determined you strategy, you can follow your account metrics.</li>
</ol>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.booxi.com/blog/how-to-create-your-business-instagram-account-a-step-by-step-guide/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>12 creative ways to benefit from Instagram</title>
		<link>https://www.booxi.com/blog/12-creative-ways-to-benefit-from-instagram/</link>
		<comments>https://www.booxi.com/blog/12-creative-ways-to-benefit-from-instagram/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2017 15:51:50 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Astrid Bertout]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Business Tips]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Customer Acquisition]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[online visibility]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social network]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.booxi.com/blog/?p=1229</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Help your beauty salon get noticed with 12 great Instagram post ideas. ]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img class="float_top aligncenter wp-image-1230 size-full" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/8JmwZulno89yNK_B_Q5OdUh1moD4l4t79TyLBT0PV_ifXV0rwIqBne0DfYG-CT8NTXFnbIL_74qoPsQdbY7UMA=s0" alt="benefit from instagram" width="1200" height="600" /></p>
<p>According to <a href="https://business.instagram.com/blog/500000-advertisers/">Instagram Advertiser Statistics</a>, 50% of Instagrammers follow a business account. Even more interesting for you, 60% of Instagrammers say they’ve found information about a product or service through the application.<br />
And most importantly, 75% of Instagrammers either visit a website, do research, buy a product/use a service, or talk to a friend after being inspired by a post.</p>
<p>This is a great opportunity to enhance your online visibility, acquire new customers and increase your sales &#8211; especially if you work in an industry where visual presentation is important. Like beauty and wellness, for example.</p>
<p>To begin, don’t use your personal account. Make sure to<a href="https://www.booxi.com/blog/how-to-create-your-business-instagram-account-a-step-by-step-guide/" target="_blank"> create a separate business account </a>instead. This way, you’ll benefit from professional features that will help convert your online visitors into customers. Then, once they become customers,there are other features that will analyze their behaviour.</p>
<ul>
<li>As you know, Instagram is an image-sharing platform, so make sure you only post high-quality photos and videos. This may seem like obvious advice, but you’d be surprised how often sub-standard images are used. Remember, everything you share will affect your business image and reputation, so make sure you choose wisely.</li>
<li>Make sure to add all the relevant information to your profile. This way, your followers will be able to interact easily with your business, or contact you directly if they need to.<img class="shadow_small aligncenter wp-image-1233" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/VEMfBBU6WRe6BeMN-bAaWYKoP8qtQQeqH14OitlX4diQvx_lcEX3AFhpmd3xFGk81mOlBywRAVRqAdCrhtkZbQ=s0" alt="etiket instagram account" width="484" height="861" /><br />
As an example, Etiket’s bio includes a business description, a mention of the industry they work in, a link to their website and three separate calls to action: Call, Email, and Directions. (Just in case you’re not aware, a call to action is a button designed to provoke an immediate response. Ex: Call Now)</li>
<li>Use popular and relevant hashtags that are related to your industry. Why?</li>
</ul>
<p>Because hashtags extend your reach and make it easier for Instagrammers to find your content. In addition, posts with at least one <a href="http://get.simplymeasured.com/rs/simplymeasured2/images/InstagramStudy2014Q3.pdf?mkt_tok=3RkMMJWWfF9wsRolua%252FAZKXonjHpfsX57%252BwtX6a2lMI%252F0ER3fOvrPUfGjI4CTsViI%252BSLDwEYGJlv6SgFQrDEMal41bgNWRM%253D">hashtag generate 12.6% more engagement</a> on average.</p>
<p>How can you think of great hashtags for your posts?</p>
<p>To get inspired, do a hashtag search and see what the most popular hashtags on Instagram are.</p>
<p><img class="shadow_small aligncenter wp-image-1231" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/N4xtaQxQ0sB5SYoPNpTo5CwFUASM9-3F9_ZMszzWs7D2_UenH_5VHOimpwgsV2LtDR8EAPxzKvHMxRIHJPg3epw=s0" alt="hashtag research" width="439" height="781" /></p>
<p>You can also follow other businesses in your industry and see what kind of hashtags they’ve added to their posts. Obviously don’t copy them, but definitely draw inspiration from them.</p>
<p>Finally, you can also use a tool to find the most relevant hashtags for your pictures. Like<a href="https://focalmark.com/">Focalmark</a>, for example. In just a few clicks, you’ll be able to find the most relevant hashtags for the images you’re sharing. And the tool’s algorithm will provide the most popular hashtags for a specific audience.</p>
<p>How many hashtags should you use?</p>
<p>It’s important to add hashtags, but make sure not to go overboard with them.<br />
A study by <a href="https://trackmaven.com/blog/everything-marketers-need-know-instagram-sponsored-content/">TrackMaven</a> shows that posts with 4-5 hashtags generate the most interactions.</p>
<p><img class="shadow_small aligncenter wp-image-1234 size-full" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/prQ55hLSwRBR_LIF3HsS-MMBVL0X42nhkpoM_vkoBOoY9VtMglwvbua-0y347nHTtDc0DIJhk_5MKlg8bpP1=s0" alt="interactions by hashtags" width="805" height="448" /></p>
<p>You can also create a hashtag that uses your business name. So when your followers share pictures about you, they can add a specific hashtag and mention your business name (@businessexample) at the same time.Not only is it a good way to start creating an online community around your business, butit will also make it very easy to know when someone mentions your business on Instagram.</p>
<ul>
<li>Like any other social network, you have to interact with other Instagram users in order to create a community. So make sure to comment on their posts and like their accounts. But that doesn’t mean you should like every account you come across. Instead, find the ones that reflect the values and image you want your business to have and like those.Similarly, you can follow people who’ve subscribed to your account. And if someone mentions your business on their account, take the time to reply. It will show your audience that you’re interested in them and that you’d like to interact with them.</li>
<li>Use Instagram stories to give your followers a peek at your day-to-day business.</li>
</ul>
<p>*What’s a story?<br />
A story is a live video shared on Instagram. It’s temporary, disappearing after 24 hours.</p>
<p>Stories are a good way to create relationships based on direct interaction. A study conducted by Social Bakers shows that <a href="https://www.socialbakers.com/blog/2621-instagram-stories-five-things-marketers-need-to-know">stories have a positive impact on your overall Instagram performance</a>. After watching a story, a follower is more likely to visit your account and interact with it (by liking or commenting on your photos, for example).</p>
<ul>
<li>Use your Instagram account to share useful content with your followers.</li>
</ul>
<p>Are you a hair salon owner? Make a short video tutorial that features an easy do-it-yourself hairstyle.</p>
<p>Are you a beauty salon owner? Post a short video tutorial about makeup that your followers can easily reproduce on their own.</p>
<p>Are you a wellness center owner? Give advice about nutrition, health and well-being, and provide tips your followers can use in their daily lives.</p>
<ul>
<li>Share quotes that inspire and motivate. Learn how to <a href="https://www.booxi.com/blog/how-to-create-shareable-images-that-drive-traffic/">create shareable images that drive traffic </a>by following this guide.  (what guide are you referring to exactly?)<br />
You can also share inspirational lifestyle photos.</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li>You can also post photos that are related to calendar events.For example, during winter,<a href="https://www.instagram.com/sephora/?hl=en">Sephora</a> shared a picture of two products that were placed in snow.<br />
Similarly, <a href="https://www.instagram.com/marcellecosmetics/?hl=en">Marcellecosmetics</a>posted a photo featuring lipsticks and hearts during Valentine’s day.<img class="shadow_small aligncenter wp-image-1235" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-XKS6XONFLlwm5HAYU_4K-SqLDY1QytfJv4rG3haUzUUHF7fffTanlSGmvsiI3EZ43w3fXC4KEU_uaTl9AyQ=s0" alt="promotion ideas based on calendar" width="745" height="683" /></li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li>Post photos of all the members of your team. On Instagram, pictures with people get <a href="http://expandedramblings.com/index.php/important-instagram-stats/13/">38% more likes</a> than those without, and get 32% more comments. It’s a great way to humanize your business.</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li>Also share customer-generated content about your business and products,  and make sure to tag them. Why? Because the content has already been created, and so it’s saved you time. More importantly,<a href="https://zuberance.com/zuberrants/category/top-10-stats-about-online-reviews">88% of people trust online reviews from strangers</a> as much as personal recommendations. Plus, it’s a good way to show your followers that you’re interested in them, which in turn helps you build a closer relationship.</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li>Share some pictures of your products and make them stand out by displaying them in a creative way.<img class="shadow_small aligncenter wp-image-1236" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/Xh2Ki_2W5jv36ZohjR7KRoBc9bFViBR1UXn8RQwIZ-tCzapqobKM-3gsNul6QpzGa_gG7TejyE4Bs2GKaNgkDog=s0" alt="display your products" width="440" height="783" />On the other hand, don’t only post product shots on your account. That’ll bore your followers in a hurry.</li>
<li>Finally, share some stunning Before &amp; After photos. It’s a great way to get people interested in your services.<img class="shadow_small aligncenter wp-image-1237" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/TnCxbc7em6XEPuAZtzbMw4FlzX3x1QCSz7IRibqHv8lfSCemgvOQWgPB0XuAy8S9uDcKWO4rJetOLW0v5mlGJg=s0" alt="before/after picture" width="670" height="430" /></li>
</ul>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.booxi.com/blog/12-creative-ways-to-benefit-from-instagram/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Get more customers by adding online appointment booking to Google My Business</title>
		<link>https://www.booxi.com/blog/get-more-customers-by-adding-booxi-on-google-my-business/</link>
		<comments>https://www.booxi.com/blog/get-more-customers-by-adding-booxi-on-google-my-business/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2017 21:10:44 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Astrid Bertout]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Business Tips]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[customer]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[online visibility]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.booxi.com/blog/?p=1226</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[You can now easily convert online visitors into customers by adding booxi directly to your Google My Business account.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img class="float_top aligncenter wp-image-1217 size-full" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/QSkaIa1KvQ4501-WCLZCBddUzVAomUnvHqhPSI3AZtSkbleD_hy1t72d_dK9W_dxemyghzQ2rufKk0dPh4yD10k=s0" alt="thumbnail" width="1200" height="600" /></p>
<p>Did you know that today 35% of customers would like to schedule appointments during non-business hours and that 25% of millennials (people under 35) will only book appointment online?</p>
<p>Then it&#8217;s obvious that online appointment booking is a competitive advantage and adding it on Internet is a strategic way to attract new customers.</p>
<p>The good news? You can now add online appointment booking directly on your Google My Business profile: a powerful tool to convert online visitors into customers.</p>
<p><strong>How to do it?</strong><br />
The first step is to create your account on Google My Business.<br />
If it’s not already done, here is a <a href="https://www.booxi.com/blog/get-more-visibility-by-registering-with-google-my-business-2/" target="_blank">step by step tutorial</a> to show you how to do it.</p>
<p>It’s easy to do it and free!</p>
<p>Then,</p>
<p><img class="img_zoom size-full wp-image-1219 alignleft" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/VqGEY7CvfXAI3GMrO-Uj4eNE5jJCsZvOrCUoG3y0no5Hgk7tubtd3Ofy2kDI_x-cLfiYTVoNz-RVOda69A7zu1o=s0" alt="unnamed (2)" /><br />
Go to the <a href="https://www.google.com/appserve/mkt/p/aZ4_3ZYNqumnqKN7XzF7PNPc3HF9qzgu-qXrbSYeMzcaGvDeyzN942-z2VHp_51GKjC-S-q93R9pzUON5oqxZ8b64nRcargMbUjtbuk93y9txqtfPkVZuQbS-phwnkEjqaYvDUiE6aARbTeasqwuxwRO48muh8lkSW9s_wbPPhFGIlml7a2G4ROr0ufKSNev63Nfjmvn8Nb_v_Cyxr9uUKIjcnKYdx_IsvJ2t2XtH_uMBJei8Htsr_E=" target="_blank">&#8220;Posts&#8221; tab<br />
</a><a href="https://www.google.com/appserve/mkt/p/aZ4_3ZYNqumnqKN7XzF7PNPc3HF9qzgu-qXrbSYeMzcaGvDeyzN942-z2VHp_51GKjC-S-q93R9pzUON5oqxZ8b64nRcargMbUjtbuk93y9txqtfPkVZuQbS-phwnkEjqaYvDUiE6aARbTeasqwuxwRO48muh8lkSW9s_wbPPhFGIlml7a2G4ROr0ufKSNev63Nfjmvn8Nb_v_Cyxr9uUKIjcnKYdx_IsvJ2t2XtH_uMBJei8Htsr_E=" target="_blank"> <img class="shadow_small aligncenter wp-image-1224 size-full" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/CC59Fn-9uID2cic99kg8LPA-nwEwcATABfQ1aHAPQB8-MogofHpN4cppoF3arvW_I8DLLoNCMlTfH3NB_YzV9Q=s0" alt="posts tab google my business" width="387" height="252" /></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><img class="img_zoom size-full wp-image-1221 alignleft" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/Q8d32nMfhAOc5XJSp6MNvHOz8oB0Ws5E0DDVZldPel9mcnrGIo9mE_jpwX8WjxyO4sGo0C1PP3qWcuN2rTpxDgg=s0" alt="unnamed (3)" /><br />
And click on the section “Write your post”.<br />
Create your message by adding a picture, a short text and the “Reserve” button. On the line <span style="color: #3366ff">example.com</span> add your booxi website link.</p>
<p>To find this link, sign in your booxi account and click on My Business tab, then on Business Details. Copy the link under the section “booxi site”.</p>
<p><img class="shadow_small aligncenter wp-image-1225 size-full" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/3xTJHL2gg-2Gcx-3yQmfy4wHI3hnTg-AE_sbI3yiJSz10CddxrUNsYSzg9upd1UORfOWqfIOt_mcSaowwK6t=s0" alt="book-now-button" width="453" height="930" /></p>
<p><img class="img_zoom size-full wp-image-1223 alignleft" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/xjGS0NwcMTD4Ig7pKGva4FufvodP0E1Ie8K0bYgXRfDlAlUQcmHgZ8qK9b5nA04yhh9Up2TofD75AAfK-39h=s0" alt="unnamed (4)" /><br />
Once it’s done click on Preview and then on Publish. And it’s live on Google, so it’s easy to convert your online visitors into customers!</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p style="text-align: center">You want to add online appointment booking directly on your Google My Business account but you don&#8217;t use booxi yet?<br />
Create your free trial right now!<br />
<a href="https://www.booxi.com/business/signup" class="creativ-shortcode creativ-shortcode-button creativ-shortcode-button-colour-allgreen creativ-shortcode-button-size-medium creativ-shortcode-button-edge-rounded" target="_blank">Get Started</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.booxi.com/blog/get-more-customers-by-adding-booxi-on-google-my-business/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Create Shareable Images That Drive Traffic?</title>
		<link>https://www.booxi.com/blog/how-to-create-shareable-images-that-drive-traffic/</link>
		<comments>https://www.booxi.com/blog/how-to-create-shareable-images-that-drive-traffic/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2017 14:57:27 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Astrid Bertout]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Business Tips]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[online visibility]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social network]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.booxi.com/blog/?p=1049</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Posts that contain photos are 2.3x more engaging than those without photos. In addition inspirational quotes can lead to post interaction, especially shares. Here are a few quick tips to help you create shareable visuals by combining photos and quotes. ]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p style="text-align: left"><a href="http://buzzsumo.com/blog/how-to-massively-boost-your-blog-traffic-with-these-5-awesome-image-stats/"><img class="float_top aligncenter wp-image-1073 size-full" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/lOoGupjaXYu4-yaklSfR1MNdB0zNlmwcdE7Mx7uZSv6Tx6bTmaVDhOffGpYBWrSTOki8Km0SzbVvzc4YVQIDjg=s0" alt="create your own pictures" width="1200" height="600" />Mike Gingerich</a>, writer at Social Media Examiner, says that “people love inspirational quotes that motivate them or elicit a particular emotion, which in turn can lead to post interaction, especially shares”.</p>
<p>This seems to be a winning strategy since it can make more people aware of your business and potentially lead to new customers.</p>
<p>In addition, Facebook posts that contain photos are 2.3x more engaging than those without photos.</p>
<p><img class="wp-image-1050 size-full aligncenter" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/dITfPx5UnGwgv_KA6rECtYN311_Yw_XCtIxEpV_hndjopK1xkqMTQ8EDz5uh-BcqmHKu8dXy4FAndXDZgZ4A=s0" alt="impact of images" width="800" height="556" /></p>
<p>Clearly, then, it’s essential that you add visuals to your posts in order to increase audience interaction as well as your online visibility.</p>
<p>Here are a few quick tips to help you create shareable visuals by combining photos and quotes.</p>
<h3>1. A Picture is Worth a Thousand Words</h3>
<p>The first step is finding photos that fit your business.</p>
<p>You can either use <a href="https://burst.shopify.com/">royalty-free photos from Shopify</a> or choose <a href="https://www.booxi.com/blog/6-outils-pour-avoir-des-photos-splendides-pour-votre-site-web/">one of the following solutions</a>.</p>
<p>Here’s an example that clearly illustrates the creative process.</p>
<p>Imagine that I’m the owner of a hair salon and I want to put a quote on my Facebook page.</p>
<p>The first thing I should do is write a list of keywords that relate to the services I offer.</p>
<p>For example:</p>
<ul>
<li>Hair</li>
<li>Hairdresser</li>
<li>Haircut</li>
</ul>
<p>Then I’ll do a photo search using those words.<br />
Once I find the picture I want, I’ll download it.</p>
<p>Here’s the one I decided to use:</p>
<p><span class="bx_text16"><img class="img_zoom aligncenter size-full wp-image-1051" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/51krfd-CQKddvJqRhBlb5gXp2s_EjtkE36VdXk8-teWg6rxh12iOn7TnXApwesURdh-0zBHKfbfWN-U702Hw6g=s0" alt="image for social network " /></span></p>
<p><span class="bx_text16">*Of course, if you have the time and resources to do it yourself (maybe you own a high quality camera, for example), by all means create your own visuals.</span></p>
<h3>2. Select the Quote</h3>
<p>Next thing you need to do is customize the picture in order to make it shareable. Like we talked about with keywords, you should select a quote that relates to what you do. The good news? It’s usually very easy to find an inspirational quote that’s connected to your field of work.</p>
<p><strong>Here’s a trick:</strong> Use the list of keywords you set up in step # 1 and do a Google search. For example, your search could be &#8220;Quotes + Hair&#8221;. You’ll quickly find a whole bunch of quotes. Now all you have to do is choose the one that suits your needs best.</p>
<p>Going back to my hair salon example, I’ll chose the following quote: &#8220;A woman who cut her hair is about to change her life&#8221; &#8211; Coco Chanel</p>
<h3>3. Customize the Image</h3>
<p>Now that you’ve found the picture and quote you need, all you have to do is to combine them.</p>
<p>To do so, just:</p>
<ul>
<li><a href="https://www.booxi.com/blog/create-your-canva-account-to-produce-your-own-visuals/">Create your Canva account</a>,</li>
<li>Select the type of visual you want to produce.<br />
In my case, I want a picture for my Facebook page, which is why I selected the “Facebook Post” option.<img class="img_zoom aligncenter size-full wp-image-1052" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/CRbKErVXRigar6K5gJH2QYC_IaVAbF4d78TmTo2S92tdVl9ECKAZ4WJa31qi3V48GGh9tn-iD7kVw4NMrIYB=s0" alt="social media type " /></li>
<li>Canva offers a variety of ready-to-use templates. Select the one you prefer.<img class="aligncenter" style="padding-top: 15px:" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/KrLkwIesQUG8rsby-UZWZfkXkOiUacC2Rczr8nxkJEPuR28jV2fjqdEVJC3ZFDQ2uDSji-yPwI1SXjZOfKn-=s0" alt="select-layout" width="508" height="592" /></li>
<li>Upload the picture you find online by clicking on the “Uploads” button, and then click on the “Upload your own images” button.<br />
<img class="img_zoom aligncenter size-full wp-image-1054" style="padding: 5px:" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/7OAVHrx6_FHoIR_17wsb3Qb5HYnOJYGDcavpe_vNqToQ16uNNs3bWFAM5rMBXSctfUbPRhishEOaaZZ2PJChZ40=s0" alt="upload-picture" /></li>
<li>Add the quote you selected earlier by clicking on the “Text” button. Then add the name of your business, but in a discrete fashion.</li>
<li>Save everything by clicking the “Download” button at the top right of the page.</li>
</ul>
<p>The following dropdown menu will appear:</p>
<p><img class="img_zoom aligncenter size-full wp-image-1056" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/DglwwJx2rXbBxd1iUcEV9tPpj4SilTbkmZbXfV-1vR6_ez7whPlIDAS8W20EhkdzwMCRTt8-VPqrbjh7bkyTfQ=s0" alt="format to download " /></p>
<p>Select the format you want when downloading. The .png and .jpeg formats are recommended.</p>
<p>Here’s the result:</p>
<p><img class="img_zoom aligncenter size-full wp-image-1057" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/iOnvhrNLFbMV3-nTNwrTB18EMnf5KjPLBmpaluTusJN_2bLfGZLq-83hIXRlP6ZBFi_SPc5mSWtytnWwJJYF3-w=s0" alt="visual creation" /></p>
<p>You can now post this picture on all your social networks. Analyze the results and repeat these steps any time you want.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.booxi.com/blog/how-to-create-shareable-images-that-drive-traffic/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Create Your Canva Account to Produce Your Own Visuals</title>
		<link>https://www.booxi.com/blog/create-your-canva-account-to-produce-your-own-visuals/</link>
		<comments>https://www.booxi.com/blog/create-your-canva-account-to-produce-your-own-visuals/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2017 14:56:51 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Astrid Bertout]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Tutorials]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[online visibility]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social network]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.booxi.com/blog/?p=1040</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Visual content is 40X more likely to get shared on social media than others types of content. By creating your Canva account, you can easily create images that fits with your business to illustrate your social media's publications.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img class="float_top aligncenter wp-image-1041 size-full" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/Fz91j7ffB9M4LUwUEN-NVnd3AIevnLq5J-vC7WfzDEkQKidT1eW9DIwsGaO6fdHElUWpeJXuw1-YuBZxwh40Qw=s0" alt="create your canva account" width="1280" height="720" />Canva is a solution that allows you to edit images to personalize them and make them fit with your business’ image.<br />
This can be very useful for customizing the images you publish on your social networks, for creating visuals for your Facebook ads, for illustrating your promotions newsletters or for illustrating your blog if you have one.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>#1 &#8211; Go on <a href="http://www.canva.com">Canva website</a>.</p>
<p><img class="img_zoom aligncenter size-full wp-image-1042" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/piHrKQqbyDg74XJ9HRsUslq9Z3xo3XplBMhpbNCpkyzCPEjQCkktQLdy3lMS75MWqapEUiyD3gIf38V3fU5oNMM=s0" alt="sign up with canva" /></p>
<p># 2 &#8211; If you have a Facebook account or a Google Account, click the appropriate button to speed up your account creation.</p>
<p>Otherwise click on &#8220;Sign up with Email&#8221; and follow the steps.</p>
<p># 3 &#8211; In order that Canva offers you the best possible templates according to your needs, select the reason for the creation of your account between the following options:</p>
<p><img class="img_zoom aligncenter size-full wp-image-1043" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/OouW60JHRjuZmf7ZbrP_2bxSVy5Z6trvOttm3KFXk0GZIupAVFh8QNQTIzgvVQLfDYR0yOr2LvoKu0mliDRRfg=s0" alt="Canva sign up completed" /></p>
<p>#4 &#8211; And it’s done.<br />
You can now start to<a href="https://www.booxi.com/blog/how-to-create-shareable-images-that-drive-traffic/"> customize your visuals for your social media publications</a>, for example.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.booxi.com/blog/create-your-canva-account-to-produce-your-own-visuals/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Take Advantage of the Holidays to Boost Your Social Networks!</title>
		<link>https://www.booxi.com/blog/take-advantage-of-the-holidays-to-boost-your-social-networks/</link>
		<comments>https://www.booxi.com/blog/take-advantage-of-the-holidays-to-boost-your-social-networks/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2016 21:57:45 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Astrid Bertout]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Business Tips]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[online visibility]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social network]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.booxi.com/blog/?p=828</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[It’s probably your most busy period of the year however with the right tools to schedule and make your social network publications, you can benefit from the Holidays to regularly publish. ]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img class="float_top aligncenter wp-image-829 size-full" src="https://booxi-live-wp-storage.storage.googleapis.com/social_medias.png" alt="boost your social networks during Holidays" width="1200" height="600" />This is probably your most busy period of the year; however, with the right tools to schedule and make your social network publications, you can benefit from the Holidays to regularly publish and interact on your social networks.</p>
<p style="text-align: center"><b>Virtual Decorations for the Holidays</b></p>
<p>Apply the decoration principle to your social networks by using images that reflect the Holidays spirit in your publications! Avoid waiting time on searching images, and use a website like StockUp that provides you lots of images for free, and is very easy to use.</p>
<p style="text-align: center"><b>Take the Time to Thank Your Customers</b></p>
<p>The Holidays is the right moment to get closer to your customers. So take the time to thank them for their loyalty by adding, for example a picture with all members of your team.</p>
<p style="text-align: center"><b>Inform Your Customers About Your Holidays Schedule</b></p>
<p>Make sure that your customers know about your schedule changes and that they can easily book appointments with you. Publish a post to remind your customers that they can book their appointment online. And<a href="https://www.booxi.com/blog/add-online-booking-to-facebook/"> add the Book Now call to action to your Facebook page</a> if it’s not done already.</p>
<p style="text-align: center"><b>Share Trends in Your Field</b></p>
<p>If you are for example, in the beauty, make up or hairstyle industry, spot styles and hairstyles that have been the most shared on Pinterest and Instagram and publish them on your social networks. Your audience will be pleased  to see that your are an expert and that you know the trends: an efficient and simple strategy to invite them to book an appointment online with you.</p>
<p style="text-align: center"><b>The Perfect Moment for Gifts</b></p>
<p>You can organize a contest to offer gifts to your audience on your social networks. It’s a very simple way to get more visibility and to reward people who like your page. Make it simple: for example it could be a sort!</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.booxi.com/blog/take-advantage-of-the-holidays-to-boost-your-social-networks/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Benefits of Online Reviews and Ratings</title>
		<link>https://www.booxi.com/blog/online-reviews/</link>
		<comments>https://www.booxi.com/blog/online-reviews/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2016 22:23:12 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Astrid Bertout]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Business Tips]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[online visibility]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[user experience]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.booxi.com/blog/?p=740</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[92% of consumers read online reviews before buying or booking. One good reason among others to allow your customers to share their experience with your business.
Let’s see why and how to do it. ]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.brightlocal.com/learn/local-consumer-review-survey/">91% of consumers read online reviews before buying or booking.</a> Indeed statistics show that the feedback from other customers are extremely important and trustworthy to them as they rely on reviews and ratings published online to make a purchase decision.</p>
<p>However many professionals and business owners don’t benefit from consumer feedback as their website and Facebook page do not offer any way to leave a feedback.</p>
<p>The main reason is because many of them express fear about it : the fear that an unsatisfied customer publishes a negative comment, or the fear that they don’t have enough time to properly manage and review comments.</p>
<p>As mentioned above, statistics show that consumers do consult online reviews to build their opinion on your business. Which is why, it is crucial that they easily find comments and reviews about your business and your services; if they can’t find any, they will most likely find another business with reviews.</p>
<p><img class="aligncenter wp-image-759 size-full" src="https://booxi-live-wp-storage.storage.googleapis.com/Untitled-7.png" alt="online rating and reviews" width="1200" height="600" /></p>
<h2 style="text-align: center"><span style="font-weight: 400">There is Much to Win, Nothing to Lose</span></h2>
<p>There are more positive than negative points in letting your customers give their feedback on your business:</p>
<ul>
<li>Testimonials help future customers to take a decision.</li>
<li>If an unsatisfied customer has the opportunity to express himself, and that you create a dialogue, chances are that you won’t lose that customer. In contrast, an unsatisfied customer who couldn’t express himself will probably never come back.</li>
<li>If you take a moment and answer to a negative review, you show to your futures customers how professional and caring about your customers you are.</li>
<li>Finally it is much better to have few negative comments online and to be aware of a problem in your business than it is to find out too late. For you it’s an opportunity to fix something before it becomes a costly problem.</li>
</ul>
<h2 style="text-align: center"><span style="font-weight: 400">Easy to Do and Simple to Managed</span></h2>
<p>Adding reviews and rating to your online presence is not that difficult of a task, and those reviews can be managed with little time investment.</p>
<p><b>How to activate it on your Facebook page?</b></p>
<ol>
<li>Go on<a href="https://www.booxi.com/blog/get-more-visibility-by-creating-your-facebook-page-for-your-local-business/"> your Facebook page</a>,</li>
<li>Then click on Settings,</li>
<li>Then click on General on the left,</li>
<li>In the section Reviews, click on Edit.<img class="shadow_medium aligncenter wp-image-755 size-full" src="https://booxi-live-wp-storage.storage.googleapis.com/activate-reviews.png" alt="turn on review on Facebook" width="932" height="198" /></li>
<li>Then choose the option Allow visitors to review this Page</li>
<li>Finally click on Save Changes.</li>
</ol>
<p><strong>Ask your current customers to leave a review on your Google My Business profile</strong><br />
After creating your <a href="https://www.booxi.com/blog/get-more-visibility-by-registering-with-google-my-business-2/">Google My Business profile</a>, to get the most out of your search results, ask your most loyal customers to <a href="https://support.google.com/maps/answer/6230175?visit_id=1-636312521334535531-1954460559&amp;rd=1&amp;hl=en">leave a review on your profile</a>. This is a really effective strategy to convert online visitors into real customers. Indeed <a href="http://searchengineland.com/88-consumers-trust-online-reviews-much-personal-recommendations-195803">88% of consumers</a> believe online reviews as much as a friend&#8217;s recommendation.</p>
<p><b>What do I do with it?</b></p>
<ul>
<li>Now all you have to do is to inform your customers they can leave a feedback online about your business and your services. Remember to ask all your happy customers to do it.</li>
<li>Schedule about 4 sessions of 15 minutes each during the week to review comments and answer them.</li>
<li>You can also ask to your customers to let their reviews on others platforms such as Tripadvisor for example.</li>
</ul>
<p>You are a booxi user and you want to give your review on our solution ?</p>
<p><a href="https://www.facebook.com/booxicom/reviews/?utm_source=article&amp;utm_campaign=the-benefits-of-online-reviews-and-ratings&amp;utm_medium=cta">Click here.</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.booxi.com/blog/online-reviews/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Get Online Visibility in 8 Simple Steps With a Tiny Budget</title>
		<link>https://www.booxi.com/blog/get-online-visibility-in-8-simple-steps-with-tiny-budget/</link>
		<comments>https://www.booxi.com/blog/get-online-visibility-in-8-simple-steps-with-tiny-budget/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2016 21:45:49 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Astrid Bertout]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Business Tips]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[online visibility]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.booxi.com/blog/?p=711</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Today your online visibility is crucial, but we know that you have very limited time to work on it. That's why we created this guide for you. It's easy to apply and you can follow the steps in any order. ]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img class="float_top aligncenter wp-image-783 size-full" src="https://booxi-live-wp-storage.storage.googleapis.com/guide_en.png" alt="online visibility guide" width="1200" height="600" /></p>
<p>In this article, we have put together a few tips you can easily apply to get online visibility. Go step by step, according to your needs and the time you have.</p>
<p>The first thing you can do is to create a file with a description of your business, the main information, few pictures, and your address for example. Then all you have to do is to copy/paste when you create your different profiles. A lot of saved time!<br />
<a href="https://www.booxi.com/blog/get-more-visibility-by-registering-with-google-my-business-2/?utm_source=blog&amp;utm_campaign=get-online-visibility-in-8-simply-steps-with-a-tiny-budget&amp;utm_medium=article"><img class="alignright" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/TUjuAbRn2VeGaIx0Rl1khqlAs6McRpoh9f082bWqloiXa-kRiZoS5D6sSXCfNbyaeyn8jBt4_TuYSwaDQAGp8A=s0" alt="Register On Google My Business" width="150" height="150" /></a></p>
<ul>
<li><strong><strong><a href="https://www.booxi.com/blog/get-more-visibility-by-registering-with-google-my-business-2/?utm_source=blog&amp;utm_campaign=get-online-visibility-in-8-simply-steps-with-a-tiny-budget&amp;utm_medium=article">Register on Google My Business<br />
</a></strong></strong></li>
</ul>
<p>Easy and free, this first step will allow you to come out with a better exposure on the Google search results when people enter your business name.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.booxi.com/blog/get-more-visibility-by-creating-your-facebook-page-for-your-local-business/?utm_source=blog&amp;utm_campaign=get-online-visibility-in-8-simply-steps-with-a-tiny-budget&amp;utm_medium=article"><img class="alignright wp-image-717 size-thumbnail" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/4orVo83rkJv9ch7iR4GUIq2Kitj9dXLQSvGqXtW2QKtjo1X1A_leaQeQ1xyA9FfghmX7Q_JlEpHjdW0Ug5eh=s150-c" alt="Create your Facebook Page" width="150" height="150" /></a></p>
<ul>
<li><strong><strong><a href="https://www.booxi.com/blog/get-more-visibility-by-creating-your-facebook-page-for-your-local-business/?utm_source=blog&amp;utm_campaign=get-online-visibility-in-8-simply-steps-with-a-tiny-budget&amp;utm_medium=article">Create your Business Page on Facebook</a></strong></strong></li>
</ul>
<p>85% of customers have a Facebook account. This means you absolutely have to be present on this social network. Once you have your Facebook page, make sure to <a href="https://www.booxi.com/blog/post-on-your-social-networks-in-just-15-minutes-a-week/?utm_source=blog&amp;utm_campaign=get-online-visibility-in-8-simply-steps-with-a-tiny-budget&amp;utm_medium=article">regularly publish relevant content on it</a>.</p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Create your website</strong></li>
</ul>
<p>Today there are many ways you can easily get a website, even with a small budget. For example, as soon as you create an account with booxi, you get an automated website on which your customers can find all the information they are looking for, such as your service offer, prices, business hours and your address.<br />
To go even further and help you create your own website with more content, booxi made partnerships with <a href="http://www.appyourself.com/fr-ca" target="_blank">appyourself</a> and <a href="http://en.webself.net/" target="_blank">Webself</a>.<br />
<a href="https://www.booxi.com/blog/add-online-booking-to-facebook/?utm_source=blog&amp;utm_campaign=get-online-visibility-in-8-simply-steps-with-a-tiny-budget&amp;utm_medium=article"><img class="alignright wp-image-724" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/bJ2nyoYaaBiXucNJig14-OGZkBQigE8PyRUlMfok22IpUOpGfP_kUZM9u4M1ZeIoEmz6jYNfUS4Zb6ACE1Ce=s0" alt="Add book now to Facebook " width="245" height="150" /></a></p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Add a call-to-action</strong></li>
</ul>
<p>It is good to be visible and to have online traffic, but it is even better when you can convert those visitors into customers. That’s why you have to add a call-to-action. With booxi you can easily <a href="https://www.booxi.com/developers?utm_source=blog&amp;utm_campaign=get-online-visibility-in-8-simply-steps-with-a-tiny-budget&amp;utm_medium=article">add a Book Now button directly on your website</a> or activate the feature <a href="https://www.booxi.com/blog/add-online-booking-to-facebook/?utm_source=blog&amp;utm_campaign=get-online-visibility-in-8-simply-steps-with-a-tiny-budget&amp;utm_medium=article">Book Now on your Facebook page</a>.</p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Register to online professional directories in your industry</strong></li>
</ul>
<p>You can easily find online specialized directories for each industry using specific keywords. For example, you can try on Google : Association + your industry, group + your industry or even directory + your industry + your region.<br />
Once you found interesting ones, all you need to do is to register to their free online profile.</p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Join groups of interest on Facebook and take part of the conversation</strong></li>
</ul>
<p>On Facebook, search for groups with people that would be interested by your services and participate to the conversations. Answer questions, stand as an expert for your industry, and use this opportunity to subtly promote your business and your services. However make sure to respect the policies of each groups, to avoid any risk of being blocked.<strong><br />
</strong><a href="https://www.booxi.com/blog/3-simple-ways-to-gain-visibility-with-facebook-ads/?utm_source=blog&amp;utm_campaign=get-online-visibility-in-8-simply-steps-with-a-tiny-budget&amp;utm_medium=article"><img class="alignright wp-image-721 size-full" src="https://booxi-live-wp-storage.storage.googleapis.com/Untitled-2.png" alt="Promote your business with Facebook ads" width="150" height="150" /></a></p>
<ul>
<li><a href="https://www.booxi.com/blog/3-simple-ways-to-gain-visibility-with-facebook-ads/?utm_source=blog&amp;utm_campaign=get-online-visibility-in-8-simply-steps-with-a-tiny-budget&amp;utm_medium=article"><strong>Promote your business with Facebook ads</strong></a></li>
</ul>
<p>Now that you have created the foundations of your online visibility, you can go further by promoting your business online. Indeed even small budgets can benefit from Facebook Ads. We have selected the most relevant types of ads for you. <strong><br />
</strong></p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Participate to forums by answering questions in your field of expertise</strong></li>
</ul>
<p>Websites like Quora can bring new visitors if you give relevant advice on subjects related to your industry. Don’t forget to add a link towards your website to drive traffic.</p>
<p>You now have everything you need to start building your online visibility. It is not that difficult, you can do it!</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.booxi.com/blog/get-online-visibility-in-8-simple-steps-with-tiny-budget/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>