<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>booxi &#187; Customer Acquisition</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.booxi.com/blog/tag/customer-acquisition/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.booxi.com/blog</link>
	<description>booxi</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2017 18:59:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
		<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
		<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>http://wordpress.org/?v=3.9.1</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Create an effective satisfaction survey in 7 simple steps</title>
		<link>https://www.booxi.com/blog/create-an-effective-satisfaction-survey-in-7-simple-steps/</link>
		<comments>https://www.booxi.com/blog/create-an-effective-satisfaction-survey-in-7-simple-steps/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2017 16:02:02 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Astrid Bertout]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Business Tips]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Customer Acquisition]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[customer retention]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.booxi.com/blog/?p=1299</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Keeping customers happy is crucial to ensuring customer retention. It also helps greatly with new customer acquisition. Find out our best practice guide to create a relevant satisfaction survey and get a very accurate feedback. ]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img class="float_top aligncenter wp-image-1357 size-full" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/aCpigFxVn3sqZEIeHsUWzWrd-U-qYaikKK5ZLwtM5o-w85KBznS6MQtPf9kLuTDEp2Yc0OX7eLDangMr3CTS=s0" alt="create your own survey" width="1200" height="600" />Did you know that <a href="http://www.trackur.com/96-of-unhappy-customers-wont-complain-to-you-but-will-tell-15-friends-infographic" target="_blank">96% of unhappy customers</a> won’t complain and 91% of them will simply never return?</p>
<p>Given this, it’s easy to understand that you need to:</p>
<p>1- Ensure that your customers are happy with the services you offer as well as the overall customer experience you provide.</p>
<p>2- Send a survey on a regular basis to measure their satisfaction and see if there’s anything you need to improve upon.</p>
<p>Customer satisfaction is the key to your success: not only does it ensure customer loyalty, but it also helps attract new customers thanks to positive word-of-mouth.</p>
<p>Getting customer feedback regarding all the steps of your customer journey is therefore essential.</p>
<p style="text-align: center">In this guide, you’ll learn how to create a satisfaction survey with ease.</p>
<p><img class="img_zoom aligncenter wp-image-1300 size-full" src="https://booxi-live-wp-storage.storage.googleapis.com/form-animation.gif" alt="create your form" width="360" height="363" />Source : <a href="https://gsuite.google.com/learning-center/products/forms/get-started/" target="_blank">Google Inc</a></p>
<p>1. Determine all the steps throughout your customer journey, from initial contact to rebooking.<br />
Here’s an example of a customer journey:</p>
<p><strong>→ Before the appointment</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Find all the necessary information about the business quickly and easily</li>
<li>Contact the business quickly and easily.</li>
<li>Book an appointment quickly and easily.</li>
<li>Receive an appointment reminder.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>→ During the appointment</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Receive a warm welcome.</li>
<li>Receive excellent service.</li>
<li>Be listened to and receive assistance</li>
<li>Have a positive experience during payment.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong> → After the appointment</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Be able to book the next appointment quickly and easily.</li>
<li>Have incentive to return. For example, through a loyalty program.</li>
<li>Enjoy a personalized customer experience.</li>
</ul>
<p>2. For each of the steps you identify, make sure to ask your customers relevant questions.</p>
<p>Here’s an example for the first step in the “Before the appointment” section:</p>
<p><em>- How did you hear about our business?</em><br />
<em> Through Facebook</em><br />
<em> Through a friend</em><br />
<em> Through Instagram</em><br />
<em> By doing online research</em><br />
<em> While passing by</em></p>
<p><strong>Tip: </strong>After the questions,make sure to leave some space so customers can give their opinions, feedback and recommendations. They might bring up a point you didn’t think about.</p>
<p>3. Creating the survey</p>
<p>Once you’ve determined all your questions, you can start to build the survey. There are</p>
<p>many platforms that’ll help you do it for free. For example, you can use Google Forms.</p>
<p>*Here’s <a href="https://gsuite.google.com/learning-center/products/forms/get-started/" target="_blank">all the information you’ll need</a> to create your Google Forms account. From there, you’ll quickly learn how to create your first survey.<br />
<br />
<strong>Tip #1</strong> &#8211; At the end of the survey, make sure to add a section to thank your customers for taking the time to answer your questions.<br />
<br />
<strong>Tip #2</strong> &#8211; Estimate the time needed to complete the form and make sure to mark it clearly. This way, your clients will see their progress as they answer the questions. In general, try to be as concise as possible, and avoid creating a form that takes more than 5 minutes to complete.</p>
<p>You can even add a progress bar to encourage them.</p>
<p><a href="https://gsuite.google.com/learning-center/products/forms/get-started/"><img class="shadow_medium aligncenter wp-image-1301 size-full" src="https://booxi-live-wp-storage.storage.googleapis.com/progress-bar.jpg" alt="progress bar" width="324" height="73" /></a></p>
<p>4. Send out your survey</p>
<p>Once your survey is ready, send it out to get as many answers as possible, in order to get as much useful information as possible.</p>
<p>Send it out on all your communication channels:</p>
<ul>
<li>Create a post on your Facebook page, and on every other social network that you use for business. Don’t forget to mention how long it’ll take to complete the survey.</li>
<li>If you have a client list, send the survey by email. They’ll be able to fill it out when they have some time.
<p><strong>Tip #1</strong> – Personalize the email subject header in order to increase the chances that your customers willopen it and complete the survey. It’s an effective strategy to increase your open rate.<em>Here’s an example:<br />
</em><em>[Fname], your opinion matters to me!</em></p>
<p><strong>Tip #2 </strong>– Don’t forget to explain why they’re receiving the email.For example, it can be: “Thanks for visiting us. In order to offer you the best experience possible, we would like to ask you some questions.”</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li>You can even send them the link by text message at the end of their appointment. Between 92 and 98% of all texts are read, making it the media with the highest open rate. In comparison, emails are only read 22% of the time.</li>
</ul>
<p>5. Analyze the answers</p>
<p>Once you start to receive answers, take time to analyze them. Determine your strengths as well as the steps during the customer journey that need to be improved.</p>
<p>Don’t forget to take into account all the additional suggestions and comments made by your customers.</p>
<p>It’s also important to identify how many times the same point is brought up by different customers. This will let you know what to focus on first.</p>
<p>6. Build for the future:</p>
<p>Based on the answers you receive and your analysis of them, prioritize future actions in order to improve your customer experience.</p>
<p><em>For example:</em></p>
<p>If the main issue raised by your customers is that it’s hard to find your business online, focus your efforts on promoting your business and building an online visibility strategy.</p>
<p>If their main frustration is that it takes a lot of time to book an appointment, why not offer online appointment booking to your customers?</p>
<p>And so on.</p>
<p>Then, for all the changes you need to make in order to improve customer satisfaction, establish deadlines and respect them.</p>
<p>7. Finally, send out your satisfaction survey regularly.</p>
<ul>
<li>This will help you monitor your improvements and see if they’ve had a positive impact on customer satisfaction.</li>
<li>Because customers’ expectations can quickly change, you need to make sure you meet them all the time.</li>
</ul>
<p>You now have all the information you need to create an effective satisfaction survey, and to implement changes that will help you offer a standout customer experience.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.booxi.com/blog/create-an-effective-satisfaction-survey-in-7-simple-steps/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>12 creative ways to benefit from Instagram</title>
		<link>https://www.booxi.com/blog/12-creative-ways-to-benefit-from-instagram/</link>
		<comments>https://www.booxi.com/blog/12-creative-ways-to-benefit-from-instagram/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2017 15:51:50 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Astrid Bertout]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Business Tips]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Customer Acquisition]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[online visibility]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social network]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.booxi.com/blog/?p=1229</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Help your beauty salon get noticed with 12 great Instagram post ideas. ]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img class="float_top aligncenter wp-image-1230 size-full" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/8JmwZulno89yNK_B_Q5OdUh1moD4l4t79TyLBT0PV_ifXV0rwIqBne0DfYG-CT8NTXFnbIL_74qoPsQdbY7UMA=s0" alt="benefit from instagram" width="1200" height="600" /></p>
<p>According to <a href="https://business.instagram.com/blog/500000-advertisers/">Instagram Advertiser Statistics</a>, 50% of Instagrammers follow a business account. Even more interesting for you, 60% of Instagrammers say they’ve found information about a product or service through the application.<br />
And most importantly, 75% of Instagrammers either visit a website, do research, buy a product/use a service, or talk to a friend after being inspired by a post.</p>
<p>This is a great opportunity to enhance your online visibility, acquire new customers and increase your sales &#8211; especially if you work in an industry where visual presentation is important. Like beauty and wellness, for example.</p>
<p>To begin, don’t use your personal account. Make sure to<a href="https://www.booxi.com/blog/how-to-create-your-business-instagram-account-a-step-by-step-guide/" target="_blank"> create a separate business account </a>instead. This way, you’ll benefit from professional features that will help convert your online visitors into customers. Then, once they become customers,there are other features that will analyze their behaviour.</p>
<ul>
<li>As you know, Instagram is an image-sharing platform, so make sure you only post high-quality photos and videos. This may seem like obvious advice, but you’d be surprised how often sub-standard images are used. Remember, everything you share will affect your business image and reputation, so make sure you choose wisely.</li>
<li>Make sure to add all the relevant information to your profile. This way, your followers will be able to interact easily with your business, or contact you directly if they need to.<img class="shadow_small aligncenter wp-image-1233" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/VEMfBBU6WRe6BeMN-bAaWYKoP8qtQQeqH14OitlX4diQvx_lcEX3AFhpmd3xFGk81mOlBywRAVRqAdCrhtkZbQ=s0" alt="etiket instagram account" width="484" height="861" /><br />
As an example, Etiket’s bio includes a business description, a mention of the industry they work in, a link to their website and three separate calls to action: Call, Email, and Directions. (Just in case you’re not aware, a call to action is a button designed to provoke an immediate response. Ex: Call Now)</li>
<li>Use popular and relevant hashtags that are related to your industry. Why?</li>
</ul>
<p>Because hashtags extend your reach and make it easier for Instagrammers to find your content. In addition, posts with at least one <a href="http://get.simplymeasured.com/rs/simplymeasured2/images/InstagramStudy2014Q3.pdf?mkt_tok=3RkMMJWWfF9wsRolua%252FAZKXonjHpfsX57%252BwtX6a2lMI%252F0ER3fOvrPUfGjI4CTsViI%252BSLDwEYGJlv6SgFQrDEMal41bgNWRM%253D">hashtag generate 12.6% more engagement</a> on average.</p>
<p>How can you think of great hashtags for your posts?</p>
<p>To get inspired, do a hashtag search and see what the most popular hashtags on Instagram are.</p>
<p><img class="shadow_small aligncenter wp-image-1231" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/N4xtaQxQ0sB5SYoPNpTo5CwFUASM9-3F9_ZMszzWs7D2_UenH_5VHOimpwgsV2LtDR8EAPxzKvHMxRIHJPg3epw=s0" alt="hashtag research" width="439" height="781" /></p>
<p>You can also follow other businesses in your industry and see what kind of hashtags they’ve added to their posts. Obviously don’t copy them, but definitely draw inspiration from them.</p>
<p>Finally, you can also use a tool to find the most relevant hashtags for your pictures. Like<a href="https://focalmark.com/">Focalmark</a>, for example. In just a few clicks, you’ll be able to find the most relevant hashtags for the images you’re sharing. And the tool’s algorithm will provide the most popular hashtags for a specific audience.</p>
<p>How many hashtags should you use?</p>
<p>It’s important to add hashtags, but make sure not to go overboard with them.<br />
A study by <a href="https://trackmaven.com/blog/everything-marketers-need-know-instagram-sponsored-content/">TrackMaven</a> shows that posts with 4-5 hashtags generate the most interactions.</p>
<p><img class="shadow_small aligncenter wp-image-1234 size-full" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/prQ55hLSwRBR_LIF3HsS-MMBVL0X42nhkpoM_vkoBOoY9VtMglwvbua-0y347nHTtDc0DIJhk_5MKlg8bpP1=s0" alt="interactions by hashtags" width="805" height="448" /></p>
<p>You can also create a hashtag that uses your business name. So when your followers share pictures about you, they can add a specific hashtag and mention your business name (@businessexample) at the same time.Not only is it a good way to start creating an online community around your business, butit will also make it very easy to know when someone mentions your business on Instagram.</p>
<ul>
<li>Like any other social network, you have to interact with other Instagram users in order to create a community. So make sure to comment on their posts and like their accounts. But that doesn’t mean you should like every account you come across. Instead, find the ones that reflect the values and image you want your business to have and like those.Similarly, you can follow people who’ve subscribed to your account. And if someone mentions your business on their account, take the time to reply. It will show your audience that you’re interested in them and that you’d like to interact with them.</li>
<li>Use Instagram stories to give your followers a peek at your day-to-day business.</li>
</ul>
<p>*What’s a story?<br />
A story is a live video shared on Instagram. It’s temporary, disappearing after 24 hours.</p>
<p>Stories are a good way to create relationships based on direct interaction. A study conducted by Social Bakers shows that <a href="https://www.socialbakers.com/blog/2621-instagram-stories-five-things-marketers-need-to-know">stories have a positive impact on your overall Instagram performance</a>. After watching a story, a follower is more likely to visit your account and interact with it (by liking or commenting on your photos, for example).</p>
<ul>
<li>Use your Instagram account to share useful content with your followers.</li>
</ul>
<p>Are you a hair salon owner? Make a short video tutorial that features an easy do-it-yourself hairstyle.</p>
<p>Are you a beauty salon owner? Post a short video tutorial about makeup that your followers can easily reproduce on their own.</p>
<p>Are you a wellness center owner? Give advice about nutrition, health and well-being, and provide tips your followers can use in their daily lives.</p>
<ul>
<li>Share quotes that inspire and motivate. Learn how to <a href="https://www.booxi.com/blog/how-to-create-shareable-images-that-drive-traffic/">create shareable images that drive traffic </a>by following this guide.  (what guide are you referring to exactly?)<br />
You can also share inspirational lifestyle photos.</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li>You can also post photos that are related to calendar events.For example, during winter,<a href="https://www.instagram.com/sephora/?hl=en">Sephora</a> shared a picture of two products that were placed in snow.<br />
Similarly, <a href="https://www.instagram.com/marcellecosmetics/?hl=en">Marcellecosmetics</a>posted a photo featuring lipsticks and hearts during Valentine’s day.<img class="shadow_small aligncenter wp-image-1235" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-XKS6XONFLlwm5HAYU_4K-SqLDY1QytfJv4rG3haUzUUHF7fffTanlSGmvsiI3EZ43w3fXC4KEU_uaTl9AyQ=s0" alt="promotion ideas based on calendar" width="745" height="683" /></li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li>Post photos of all the members of your team. On Instagram, pictures with people get <a href="http://expandedramblings.com/index.php/important-instagram-stats/13/">38% more likes</a> than those without, and get 32% more comments. It’s a great way to humanize your business.</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li>Also share customer-generated content about your business and products,  and make sure to tag them. Why? Because the content has already been created, and so it’s saved you time. More importantly,<a href="https://zuberance.com/zuberrants/category/top-10-stats-about-online-reviews">88% of people trust online reviews from strangers</a> as much as personal recommendations. Plus, it’s a good way to show your followers that you’re interested in them, which in turn helps you build a closer relationship.</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li>Share some pictures of your products and make them stand out by displaying them in a creative way.<img class="shadow_small aligncenter wp-image-1236" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/Xh2Ki_2W5jv36ZohjR7KRoBc9bFViBR1UXn8RQwIZ-tCzapqobKM-3gsNul6QpzGa_gG7TejyE4Bs2GKaNgkDog=s0" alt="display your products" width="440" height="783" />On the other hand, don’t only post product shots on your account. That’ll bore your followers in a hurry.</li>
<li>Finally, share some stunning Before &amp; After photos. It’s a great way to get people interested in your services.<img class="shadow_small aligncenter wp-image-1237" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/TnCxbc7em6XEPuAZtzbMw4FlzX3x1QCSz7IRibqHv8lfSCemgvOQWgPB0XuAy8S9uDcKWO4rJetOLW0v5mlGJg=s0" alt="before/after picture" width="670" height="430" /></li>
</ul>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.booxi.com/blog/12-creative-ways-to-benefit-from-instagram/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to get new customers with Local Awareness Ads: A guide for Small Businesses</title>
		<link>https://www.booxi.com/blog/get-new-customers-with-local-awareness-ads/</link>
		<comments>https://www.booxi.com/blog/get-new-customers-with-local-awareness-ads/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2017 18:12:30 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Astrid Bertout]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Business Tips]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Customer Acquisition]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Facebook ads]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Local Business]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.booxi.com/blog/?p=1080</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Learn how to use Facebook Ads to promote your business locally and attract new customers. ]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img class="float_top aligncenter wp-image-1079 size-full" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/wsptTct0Hi9pf30znqaA3t8e3o_5P5U6T3wv40G0yOoGbCMmDq-YRXndBBIhFh2cOV5OP3Mcj3lUVasUxRGF=s0" alt="local awareness ads" width="1200" height="600" />A study performed by Google showed that 4 out of 5 consumers want <a href="https://think.storage.googleapis.com/docs/how-advertisers-can-extend-their-relevance-with-search_research-studies.pdf%20">personalized ads</a> based on their city, postal code or immediate environment. This represents a great business opportunity for small business owners.</p>
<p>You can take advantage of these findings by using local awareness ads from Facebook to target potential customers that live close to your business. Facebook ads are simple to use and allow you to manage your budget with ease (for example, you can set a limit of $5/day). In order to increase the chances of driving targeted people to your salon, give them a good reason to click on your ads and interact with your business. One thing you can do is offer them a promotion on one of your services or products.</p>
<p>Let&#8217;s show you how to create and set up your first local awareness ads.<br />
Before you create a promotion to attract new customers, you need to make sure you exclude your current customers from the targeted audience.</p>
<p>This video explains how to <a href="https://www.facebook.com/business/help/170456843145568?__mref=message_bubble">create a customized audience</a>. We’ll then show how you to make sure your current customers don’t receive your Facebook ads.</p>
<p>Once it’s finished, let’s start creating your ad:</p>
<ol>
<li>Access the <a href="https://www.facebook.com/login.php?next=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.facebook.com%2Fads%2Fmanage%2Fpowereditor%2F%3Furl%3Dhttps%253A%252F%252Fwww.facebook.com%252Fads%252Fmanage%252Fpowereditor%252F%26campaign_id%3D163681540489385%26placement%3D%252Fbusiness%252Fhelp%252F162528860609436%26creative%3Dcta_button" target="_blank">Power Editor</a>.</li>
<li>Next, choose your marketing objective by selecting the “Reach” option. Then give your campaign a name.
<p><img class="shadow_small aligncenter wp-image-1096 size-full" src="https://booxi-live-wp-storage.storage.googleapis.com/marketing-goal.png" alt="marketing-goal" width="932" height="935" /><br />
If it’s not already done, set up your account and click “Continue”.</p>
<p><img class="shadow_small aligncenter wp-image-1097 size-full" src="https://booxi-live-wp-storage.storage.googleapis.com/account-settings1.jpg" alt="account settings" width="958" height="559" /></li>
<li>In this section, you’ll be able to exclude your current customers from targeting.<br />
Just click on the “Exclude” link and select the audience you decided on at the beginning of this guide.</p>
<p><img class="shadow_small aligncenter wp-image-1098 size-full" src="https://booxi-live-wp-storage.storage.googleapis.com/exclude-current-client-listr.png" alt="exclude-current-client-list" width="944" height="710" /><br />
Then, to promote your business at the local level, check the box that says &#8220;Use the location of your Facebook page to reach people near your business&#8221;.<br />
You can also determine your advertising radius, and even include or exclude specific neighborhoods.</p>
<p><img class="shadow_small aligncenter wp-image-1099 size-full" src="https://booxi-live-wp-storage.storage.googleapis.com/geographic-radius.png" alt="local awareness " width="937" height="624" /><br />
At this stage you can also determine if you want to target the people who live in the area, the people who were recently in the area, the people traveling through the area or everyone in this area.</p>
<p><img class="shadow_small aligncenter wp-image-1100 size-full" src="https://booxi-live-wp-storage.storage.googleapis.com/targeted-people.png" alt="targeted-people" width="737" height="628" /><br />
You can then refine the audience you want to reach by adding specific criteria. For example, you can target by:<br />
- Age<br />
- Gender<br />
- Language<br />
- You can even target people based on interests, behaviours or the type of connection with your business (for example you can decide to include or exclude your fans).You can save the target audience you just created for future use.</p>
<p><img class="shadow_small aligncenter wp-image-1101 size-full" src="https://booxi-live-wp-storage.storage.googleapis.com/more-detailled-target.png" alt="more-detailled-target" width="656" height="434" /></li>
<li>You can request automatic placements by Facebook or make your own settings. All you need to do is determine where you want to show your ads.<br />
<img class="shadow_small aligncenter wp-image-1102 size-full" src="https://booxi-live-wp-storage.storage.googleapis.com/placement.png" alt="placement" width="661" height="652" /></li>
<li>Finally, determine the budget for your ad and when it’ll run.
<p><img class="shadow_small aligncenter wp-image-1103 size-full" src="https://booxi-live-wp-storage.storage.googleapis.com/budget-and-schedules.png" alt="budget-and-schedules" width="942" height="782" /><br />
Once you’ve set all the criteria, click “Continue”.</li>
<li>You can now create the visual for your ad.Be sure to make your offer precise. It must be easy to understand and easy to apply.<br />
For example, you could offer a 25% discount on a service or advertise a giveaway.</p>
<p>Once you’ve determined your offer, create an image for your ad.</p>
<p>It could be really simple. An image that illustrates your service(s) is often enough.</p>
<p><img class="shadow_small aligncenter wp-image-1104 size-full" src="https://booxi-live-wp-storage.storage.googleapis.com/image-format.png" alt="image-format" width="939" height="796" /><br />
Depending on your ad, choose the appropriate format (carousel, single image, single video or slideshow).<br />
Here’s an example:</p>
<p><img class="img_zoom aligncenter size-full wp-image-1105" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/yNVMPa--9bw3DDHFG6JjgJjjwvGjYnvgAw0puOYsLQiNy-NxN1hH64-Yfji8DPOwTEtAFXFuajCoThMlsJEjjA=s0" alt="ads example" />It’s really important that you add a call to action, which is simply a button that encourages people to interact with your ad.<br />
For example, if you offer online appointment booking, make sure to direct the targeted audience to the link that lets them book online.<br />
In addition, by using an appointment tool you’ll be able to review appointment history &#8211; and then you’ll be able to verify if a person is actually a new customer.</p>
<p><strong>To go even further:</strong></p>
<p>Some appointment tools let you ask your customers how they heard about your business while they’re booking online.<br />
It’s a good way to track how many new customers you’ve attracted thanks to your ad. In turn, you’ll be able to measure your return on investment.</p>
<p><img class="shadow_small aligncenter wp-image-1106 size-full" src="https://booxi-live-wp-storage.storage.googleapis.com/call-to-action.png" alt="call-to-action" width="400" height="529" /></li>
<li>Once everything’s done, click on the &#8220;Place Order&#8221; button.
<p><img class="shadow_small aligncenter wp-image-1107 size-full" src="https://booxi-live-wp-storage.storage.googleapis.com/place-order.png" alt="place-order" width="246" height="39" /></li>
<li>Then add your credit card information:
<p><img class="shadow_small aligncenter wp-image-1108 size-full" src="https://booxi-live-wp-storage.storage.googleapis.com/credit-card-ingo.png" alt="credit-card-info" width="439" height="526" /></li>
<li>Click on “Continue” and you’re done.</li>
</ol>
<p>There &#8211; you’ve just created your first local awareness ad to attract new clients.</p>
<p>You can let it run for a week for two (or however long your test period is) and then analyze your return on investment at the end of it. Depending on how many new customers you attracted, you can adjust your Facebook ad as needed and keep testing.</p>
<p><img class="shadow_small aligncenter wp-image-1109 size-full" src="https://booxi-live-wp-storage.storage.googleapis.com/complete-ads-example.jpg" alt="complete ads example" width="521" height="529" /></p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.booxi.com/blog/get-new-customers-with-local-awareness-ads/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>