<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>booxi &#187; website</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.booxi.com/blog/tag/website/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.booxi.com/blog</link>
	<description>booxi</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2017 18:59:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
		<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
		<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>http://wordpress.org/?v=3.9.1</generator>
	<item>
		<title>4 marketing tips to promote your website</title>
		<link>https://www.booxi.com/blog/4-marketing-tips-to-promote-your-website/</link>
		<comments>https://www.booxi.com/blog/4-marketing-tips-to-promote-your-website/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2017 20:06:35 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Astrid Bertout]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Business Tips]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[website]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.booxi.com/blog/?p=1591</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[In a fast-changing digital world, you need to constantly keep up-to-date with new trends to properly promote your business. ]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img class="float_top aligncenter wp-image-1593 size-full" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/mI2GV7mp_t4SMTwvqeifVMod0PXyqvSqLcK8o3uHpUIHOeHQFrYA-BStPzCQcwbfF-q6FNY3pZ2HjUuNxNtLaA=s0" alt="website promotion" width="1200" height="600" /><br />
In a fast-changing digital world, you need to constantly keep up-to-date with new trends to ensure that our business evolves along with the technology. Luckily for you, there are tons of tools available to help you deepen your web knowledge.</p>
<p>Today, WebSelf, one of booxi’s partners gives you 4 marketing tips to promote your website.</p>
<p><b>First, get to know your customers</b></p>
<p>The first step is to determine your target market and get to know your clientele.</p>
<p>This is essential since you will have to take them into account in almost all of your marketing actions, to retain them or simply to win new customers.</p>
<p><i>Your offers, products and services, who are they for?</i></p>
<p>The answer to this question is very important because it will give you an idea of ​​what type of audience you will be dealing with.</p>
<p>When you’ve somewhat determined your target market, you need to learn as much about them as you can. Their buying habits, their gender, their age, etc. The more information you have, the easier it will be to personalize your marketing efforts in order to maximize them.</p>
<p><b>1. Spread the good news</b></p>
<p>Someone once said that a website is a direct reflection of a business. That’s why your online presence, whether it’s through a website, social networks, online directories, etc. must be impeccable. at all times.</p>
<p>When you’re proud of the final result, it’s time to spread the good news and share your website everywhere! Ask for your entourage’s opinion and share a link on your personal social media to get the word out. It will also increase your visibility online and will allow you to win a few customers!</p>
<p><b>2. Use social platforms</b></p>
<p>Do we really need to tell you about the importance of creating business accounts on social networks? Be sure to choose wisely which platform you wish to appear on, and then properly use them. Do not forget that many will use it as a support for their technical questions. Answer all questions and suggestions from your customers and communicate with original and interesting content.<br />
<img class="img_zoom aligncenter size-full wp-image-1594" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/OTIZOfG-rBOquVjwa8ikWXrOgBLr5M3aGOsCOsxpwBz25PY2E4ANFKdrgaX9SvFRw94CXn7LkZDSpHHckAmPcw=s0" alt="social" /></p>
<p><b>3. Increase customer loyalty with a newsletter</b></p>
<p>A great way to retain your current customer base is to send them a newsletter. This is advantageous especially when we know that it is 5x easier and less expensive to retain our current customer base than to find new customers.</p>
<p>Send a newsletter to inform your customers of new things coming up, share your blog articles or simply to remind them that you still exist! WebSelf offers an email collector tool, in the editor, where you can collect your visitors’ e-mail addresses use them to send out a newsletter, for example.</p>
<p><b>4. Set up a reward system</b></p>
<p>Your satisfied customers will be your best brand ambassadors, and you must reward loyalty! There are several kinds of reward systems, whether it&#8217;s sponsorship, ex, offer a discount whenever a client refers you to another, or you offer your customers discounts or gifts after X numbers of purchases. Be careful: Offer only gifts / discounts that are proportional to expenses. You want to retain your customers but you do not want to lose too much money in the process.</p>
<p><a href="http://en.webself.net/">Try creating your free website NOW</a></p>
<p><a href="http://en.webself.net/">Webself</a> is a free and easy tool to create website. Choose your design, add your texts and pictures and publish your website on the Internet. It has never been easier to create a website! No computer knowledge required, only your imagination ! Start building your own website today.</p>
<p><img class="aligncenter wp-image-1596 size-full" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/F6KJa79JK3XNjpj_Vf6w7IzCLewlOCummGNpZNHrx6JNEPg8C9yB4Xlw1K822r9Pk9tNAo0RlsYIMxh7MZzeBdA=s0" alt="webself website creator " width="1440" height="600" /></p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.booxi.com/blog/4-marketing-tips-to-promote-your-website/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to add book now button directly on your Webself website?</title>
		<link>https://www.booxi.com/blog/how-to-add-book-now-button-directly-on-your-webself-website/</link>
		<comments>https://www.booxi.com/blog/how-to-add-book-now-button-directly-on-your-webself-website/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2017 14:38:43 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Astrid Bertout]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Tutorials]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[online visibility]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[website]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.booxi.com/blog/?p=1537</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Here is the tutorial to learn how to add online appointment booking directly on your Webself website.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img class="float_top aligncenter wp-image-1550 size-full" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/nDarG9RG95oK7v1li6gcErJC3276LsosdNNeFTQ-9-M-o99X1NXWIZPPMroEVoEq33RKtqvZ5pL0iS-HuToUAg=s0" alt="webself-top" width="1200" height="373" /></p>
<ol>
<li>Sign in your Webself editor, and go on the page where you want to add the book now button.</li>
<li>Click on the section ‘’+ ADD’’ and select the option ‘’Script’’ in the Tools Sections.<br />
Click on it, and drop down it on the desired section.<img class="img_zoom aligncenter wp-image-1551 size-full" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/b6KMQT_6vmpRJIhKEUV2pHbCNq2wdRmRvuvfpzQ1R2gw-JpAamebpYjYBgssNbbRVz2enbPvuc7s9w88M8pw=s0" alt="add section" width="290" height="463" /></li>
<li>This pop will appear:<img class="img_zoom aligncenter size-full wp-image-1552" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/5ybr9C0oRvuC2KxAvXhnj8jv4WGLHIbGWq_tgFkpSKFiMAHQd3kLTBmGyOL9yMoBTJmHJzRQWwTwg_KKJq15=s0" alt="script pop up" /></li>
<li>To generate the code that you’ll past on this pop up:</li>
</ol>
<ul>
<li>You’ll need your booxi API Key.<br />
Here’s how to find it:<br />
Go on My Business tab, and then on the section Business Details. Scroll down to the section API Key and copy the code.</li>
<li>Then go <a href="https://www.booxi.com/developers/booknow" target="_blank">to this page</a> and use the Widget Generator to create the script:<img class="img_zoom aligncenter size-full wp-image-1553" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/egv5RSJe8_GV_2o-C5JTG7UMGuvwlBer8u64Bg45ubpTkn44SflEJNAiOvq27eL-QUai9Wv-5MHLqWd6u7O7Yyc=s0" alt="widget generator" /></li>
</ul>
<p>In the section API Key, paste the code you’ve just copied.<br />
Select the language which you want the text to appear on the button, and select the option ‘’External Popup’’. Then you can customize the text of the button if you want to. Finally click on the button ‘’ Generate the code’’ : a code is generated on the right side.</p>
<p>5. Copy the code generated in the section ‘’Widget Code’’.</p>
<p><img class="img_zoom aligncenter size-full wp-image-1554" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/nsUFxl_nzdPF263-IfbGIPAZs2_SdeV8iZf917_RIpAaBhrg9zDRyl11rpGc3iLxu831UZQJtynxOIHdic8Oni4=s0" alt="widget generated" /></p>
<p>6. And go back to the Editor in Webself.</p>
<p>In the pop-up Script, scroll down to the section ‘’Content code between &lt;body&gt; and &lt;/body&gt; tags. Paste the Widget code you’ve just copied.</p>
<p>7. Go back to the booxi code generator and copy the code in the Widget Container section.</p>
<p><img class="img_zoom aligncenter size-full wp-image-1555" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/Z95pOAxVwexShHksu_E8sbEiTn7p2sz1l-pv3PTWPpMt-5ysuWBb8k4jPzzz4LvblJQ71p5rfWmfoJJBtVjDHWo=s0" alt="book now button code" /></p>
<p>8. In the Webself Editor, paste the code in the first section ‘’Code Content’’.<br />
9. Once again go back to your booxi generator, and copy the code in the section ‘’Book Now Button’’. For example, copy the English one.</p>
<p>10. And finally go back to the Webself Editor and paste the code you’ve just copied in the section ‘’Content code between &lt;head&gt; and &lt;/head&gt; tags.</p>
<p>11. Click on the Update buttons, and then on Save and you’re done.</p>
<p>Your customers can now book appointment directly from your Webself website.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.booxi.com/blog/how-to-add-book-now-button-directly-on-your-webself-website/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Small Businesses &#8211; Use the Web at Your Advantage</title>
		<link>https://www.booxi.com/blog/small-businesses-use-the-web-at-your-advantage/</link>
		<comments>https://www.booxi.com/blog/small-businesses-use-the-web-at-your-advantage/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2017 17:00:17 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Astrid Bertout]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Business Tips]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Owners]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[online visibility]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[website]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.booxi.com/blog/?p=1275</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[With hundreds of new businesses created every day, it is important to stand out. You can't simply offer a quality product or service, you also need to make yourself visible on the web! Here are 3 ways to have a web presence. ]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img class="float_top aligncenter wp-image-1294 size-full" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/thwtcJeYvy4UY2z2SFC6rOTr6PxuKL63TDut3BewTUPhKXBLCQfT-6-ix8SbOrH8uRcMq-ArA8DmuMBaGWnHz3o=s0" alt="webself" width="1171" height="527" />With hundreds of new businesses created every day, it is important to stand out.</p>
<p>You can’t simply offer a quality product or service, you also need to make yourself visible on the web! It is very rare that a company, no matter the sector of activity, isn’t on the web somehow.</p>
<p>According to <a href="http://www.chainstoreage.com/article/study-81-research-online-making-big-purchases" target="_blank">Chainstorage.com</a>, it is said that 80% of consumers search online before shopping; it is therefore important that your customers find you!</p>
<p>Luckily for you, there are several ways to have a web presence; through a website, social networks, newsletters, mobile application, etc.  Today, we talk about three ways you can use the web to your advantage!</p>
<h2>1. Get to know your target market</h2>
<p>One of the first steps in getting a business up and running is to determine who will be your target market, who will benefit from your products or services. If you determine your target audience from the beginning, it will be easier to adapt your content, your visuals, to build your website as well as all of your communications (newsletter, text messaging, social networks).</p>
<p>Why is it important to adapt to your target audience?  Because not only do you want to build a good relationship with your customers by offering them a quality experience, but you also want to increase loyalty. By creating a web community with your potential and current customers you increase the chances of recurrence, good reviews, references, etc.</p>
<p>Competitive intelligence is also important before getting starting your own business. Look at similar businesses, those that offer the same services or are located near you. It will give you a good idea for your pricing, services offered and well as the target market. Keep in mind though, this isn’t to copy, but rather to use the information as a guide or for inspiration.</p>
<p>Try to be as creative as possible on the web. Live videos, Facebook contests, daily Instagram posts, ‘Client of the Month’ articles, all of those are great ideas to create an active web community!</p>
<p>Another advantage of the web? Personalized communication!</p>
<p>The personalization of your posts is very interesting and you should definitely explore all of its advantages! For example, on Facebook, you can sponsor posts that will only reach your target market. You can also collect the names of your customers and use it when sending a monthly newsletter. Customizing will make your customers feel that they are important to you; This is a great way to focus on customer loyalty.</p>
<p><img class="shadow_medium  aligncenter wp-image-1280 size-full" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/7blA2CEd0IT6Rn2ZPlQNGY-1KmvvJ8-I41kk0qDRs_MVjlrhajtiqQI02zLpezamj4vosAxqwLpu3Koimpebpg=s0" alt="feedback" width="901" height="480" /></p>
<h2>2. Listen</h2>
<p>Listening to your customers on the web? It is possible and you should definitely do it! In fact, you can gather valuable information that will help you adjust when it’s time to make some changes or modifications in your business.</p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Observe purchasing behaviors:</strong>
<p>Your customers use your services only once and never come back? Do you have a high recurrence rate? Keep records of your customers to evaluate their purchase behaviors, it will be easy to determine if you need to make changes, for example,  there might be something wrong  if the recurrence rate is very low.</li>
<p></p>
<li><strong>Collect comments:<br />
</strong></p>
<p>If you have the time, try to offer a personalized after-sales service.  Send a thank you email asking the customer for their comments on the product, service, or ask them to submit a review about their experience. Facebook offers a &#8216;review&#8217; section to allow customers to give their opinion based on stars (1 to 5)  as well as leave relevant comments. Do not forget to reply to these comments, whether they are positive or negative!</li>
<li><strong>Participate in forums:</strong>
<p>There are several forums or groups on Facebook where you can gather information. For example, about ten thousand professionals joined a Facebook group called &#8216;Dans la tête des entrepreneurs’. It is not unusual to see people ask for design advice about their website or get more information about marketing tactics. it is very interesting because the answers come from professionals who are there to help you! It’s also a great way to make contacts.</li>
<p></p>
<li><strong>Surveys:</strong>
<p>Surveys are also interesting because they allow you to collect answers of questions you may have. You can add a survey section in your newsletter and ask your customers some monthly questions. Want to offer a new service? Create a survey to see if it could possibly interest your customers. There are several tools to help you, for example, <a href="https://fr.surveymonkey.com/" target="_blank">SurveyMonkey</a>.</li>
<p>
</ul>
<h2>3. Adjust</h2>
<p>By collecting information about your customers and their buying habits, you will be able to adjust when the time comes to make changes. Chances are that you have to be flexible when you&#8217;re in business, and that&#8217;s a good thing, because adjusting to please your target market is a good way to retain your customer base and demonstrate how much you care about them.</p>
<p style="text-align: center"><span class="bx_text24">There’s nothing wrong with modifications!</span></p>
<p>Just be sure to notify your customers. Web platforms are a great way to keep your customers informed on news features or updates. Use them to your advantage by encouraging people to react to your publications, leave comments, share or ask questions. Do not forget that adjustments are not a sign of weakness, on the opposite, it shows your customers your flexibility!</p>
<p>You can also use the newsletters, to talk about upcoming news or changes! Newsletters are an excellent way to build loyalty. Have you ever thought about text message marketing? If it works with your target market, why not try it? It is said that 93% of people have a smartphone and 98% of all text messages are open!</p>
<p>You have every advantage to use the web if you are in business! Not only is it an inexpensive (or even free) solution, but the web could propel your business to another level! Customer loyalty, newsletter, animated social platforms; explore the different ways and see what works with your customers, while having fun!</p>
<p style="text-align: center"><span class="bx_text24">Your idea deserves a great site!<br />
Go to <a href="http://www.webself.net" target="_blank">WebSelf.net</a> to create your own free website today!</span></p>
<p>Webself is a free and easy tool to create website. Choose your design, add your texts and pictures and publish your website on the Internet. It has never been easier to create a website! No computer knowledge required, only your imagination ! Start building your own website today.</p>
<p><a href="http://www.webself.net"><img class="shadow_medium aligncenter wp-image-1295 size-full" src="https://booxi-live-wp-storage.storage.googleapis.com/webself-banner.jpg" alt="create your website " width="1440" height="600" /></a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.booxi.com/blog/small-businesses-use-the-web-at-your-advantage/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Integrate the Book Now Button in Your Website</title>
		<link>https://www.booxi.com/blog/how-to-integrate-the-book-now-button-in-your-website/</link>
		<comments>https://www.booxi.com/blog/how-to-integrate-the-book-now-button-in-your-website/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2017 16:28:43 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Astrid Bertout]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Tutorials]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[online booking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[website]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.booxi.com/blog/?p=988</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Find out how easy it is to add online booking to your website, with a step by step tutorial and a series of useful links to generate the code you need and fully customize your Book Now button.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img class="float_top aligncenter wp-image-993 size-full" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/rDDBCz4_k3m23CDIt3cUWYF9wSX2MFZPnfGFoVAQMR4UTyzKtNx9pulGbdnX0G-wsCpeVVvScWrvY9uzzO3OLw=s0" alt="Integrate book now button in your website" width="1280" height="720" />This article guides you through simple steps to easily add online booking to your website. It also provides you with useful links to generate the Javascript code that best suites the website creation tool you are using.</p>
<p>Book Now works prety much for any kind of website, no matter if it is custom made or if it was created using a website creator/builder/designer tool. Book Now is also responsive and will work just fine with most mobile devices.</p>
<h3 style="text-align: center">Use One of Our Tutorials and Code Generators</h3>
<p>If you know what tool was used to create your website, you can use one of the links below, and simply follow the tutorial steps.<img class="img_zoom wp-image-991 alignright" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/580NOjvWld1z9yA2h46zHCJfeIqXBmOYgsrZCBD1SIybeAsXMYMCSgX2Pfyh6yhSQpnKQwtpuB0BYggo5eOswQ=s0" alt="wordpress logo" width="318" height="187" /></p>
<ul>
<li><a href="https://www.booxi.com/developers/wordpress" target="_blank">WordPress websites</a></li>
<li><a href="https://www.booxi.com/developers/wix" target="_blank">Wix websites</a></li>
<li><a href="https://www.booxi.com/developers/lightspeed" target="_blank">Lightspeed eCom websites</a></li>
<li><a href="https://www.booxi.com/blog/how-to-use-the-booxi-book-now-widget-with-votresite-ca/" target="_blank">Votresite.ca websites</a></li>
</ul>
<p>If you have no idea what tool was used to create your website, or if it is not covered by the links listed before, use the generic tutorial below.</p>
<ul>
<li><a href="https://www.booxi.com/developers/booknow" target="_blank">Any other website tool or custom websites</a></li>
</ul>
<h3 style="text-align: center">You Can Fully Customize Your Book Now Button</h3>
<p>booxi allows you to fully customize your button, so it matches perfectly your brand. If you are familiar with Javascript and CSS, use this <a href="https://www.booxi.com/blog/how-to-fully-customize-your-book-now-button/" target="_blank">article to find out how to customize it.</a></p>
<h3 style="text-align: center">Have Someone Else Do It For You</h3>
<p>We thought you might simplify things even more by sending an email to your web developer with all the required information. So we added a small Share button next to your API key, which will ask you for an email address and send an automated email with your API key and a link to this article. You will find this Share button in My Business, Business Details and scrolling down to your API Key.</p>
<p><img class="img_zoom aligncenter size-full wp-image-990" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/OAJDKH099iYPISquQuCvctZIU5rdbaXRAghSDOLkij9Up1gb3oToqIbcrptLhTqo1Sg3tcrcsrZzetZDuyBDwQ=s0" alt="send my API key pop up" /></p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.booxi.com/blog/how-to-integrate-the-book-now-button-in-your-website/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Importance of a Website</title>
		<link>https://www.booxi.com/blog/the-importance-of-a-website/</link>
		<comments>https://www.booxi.com/blog/the-importance-of-a-website/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2016 20:53:56 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Astrid Bertout]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Business Tips]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[online visibility]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[website]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.booxi.com/blog/?p=624</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Often, entrepreneurs think a website is an unnecessary expense, especially when they already have a Facebook page. Here are some benefits of having a website and why it is important for small businesses to have a digital presence today.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img class="float_top aligncenter wp-image-627 size-full" src="https://booxi-live-wp-storage.storage.googleapis.com/website_en.png" alt="customizable website" width="1200" height="600" /></p>
<p>booxi offers you an automated web site. To go even further, we introduce you our partner Webself, to create your own web site, complete, fully customizable and on which you will be able to add more content.</p>
<p>You’ve created a business, you’ve designed a powerful logo and you have defined your target market? Now is time to build a solid customer base! Did you know that 46% of small businesses still don’t have a website?</p>
<p>Often, entrepreneurs think a website is an unnecessary expense, especially when they already have a Facebook page. Instead, they must view it as an investment. Here are some benefits of having a website and why it is important for small businesses to have a digital presence today.</p>
<h2>1. Available 24/7, everywhere.</h2>
<p>Unlike a physical store, a website is accessible 24/7. With an FAQ page, your website can even answer your customer&#8217;s questions independently. In addition to being available at all hours of the day, your customers can view your website from all over the world, and on multiple devices like computers, tablets and mobile phones (if your website is optimized for mobile use).</p>
<h2>2. An inexpensive solution</h2>
<p>When you are self-employed, time is money. A website will help you decrease your expenses, including printing costs, technical support and more visibility will result in an increase in sales. On a short and medium-term basis, your investment will turn into profit gains. Also, when you have an online store, you can sell your products online even if your business is closed!</p>
<h2>3. Building an online community</h2>
<p>Another advantage of having a website is to build a community with your customers. Not only will your website be an important source of information about your products and services, but you can also find creative ways to stay in touch with your customers. Why not create a blog? A blog offers several advantages such as boosting your marketing strategies, allowing you to write about topics that you like while improving your visibility, forming partnerships, as well as increasing your income!</p>
<h2>WebSelf</h2>
<p>Ready to get started in creating a website? Here is the solution: WebSelf!</p>
<p><a href="http://en.webself.net/?utm_source=booxi&amp;utm_medium=article&amp;utm_campaign=partenariat">WebSelf.net</a> is a website builder for entrepreneurs, small businesses, artisans and associations to create a professional-looking website for free. WebSelf believes that the Internet should be accessible to everyone and here&#8217;s why they offer an an easy-to-use editor where no technical knowledge is required. Once you have created your free account, you only have to select a design, add your content, text, images, videos, etc. and publish your website on the web! In addition, you get free and unlimited support.</p>
<p>Whether you are a musician, entrepreneur, owner of a restaurant, WebSelf provides all the necessary tools and feature to create a beautiful website.</p>
<p><a href="http://en.webself.net/?utm_source=booxi&amp;utm_medium=article&amp;utm_campaign=partenariat">Start creating your website today</a></p>
<p><img class="aligncenter wp-image-289 size-full" src="https://booxi-live-wp-storage.storage.googleapis.com/2016-08-26.jpg" alt="Webself banner" width="1440" height="600" /></p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.booxi.com/blog/the-importance-of-a-website/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>6 tools for stunning photos for your website by Webself.net</title>
		<link>https://www.booxi.com/blog/6-tools-for-stunning-photos-for-your-website/</link>
		<comments>https://www.booxi.com/blog/6-tools-for-stunning-photos-for-your-website/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2016 19:48:50 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Astrid Bertout]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Business Tips]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[online visibility]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[optimization]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[website]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.booxi.com/blog-dev/?p=279</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Images make everything more attractive and trustworthy. Here are 6 tools to improve your website images. ]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img class="float_top shadow_large aligncenter wp-image-299 size-full" src="http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/dR_UN-iIbZmAwL_RmOGjuuZweSDb0hd7YjQXUlrGbcG3l4rZqoTBV19xgu5iz5PtcRaxXJ8iLIWIDscn0Nn2xqw=s0" alt="website example" width="836" height="474" /></p>
<p>In our latest newsletter, we asked you what you thought <a href="http://en.webself.net/blog/2016/07/13/7-tips-to-improve-the-design-of-your-website">made an interesting website</a>. You responded majoritarily that it is the quality images that catch your eye and make you visit and stay on a website. Obviously, the images play a big role in the visual of a website, but are often difficult to manage.</p>
<p>Today, we will talk about 6 tools to have the most perfect images: 3 image banks and 3 of our favorite picture editors!</p>
<hr />
<h2 style="text-align: center">Image Banks</h2>
<hr class="dash" />
<h3 style="text-align: center">Pexels</h3>
<p><img class="shadow_medium aligncenter wp-image-281" src="http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/_uWevGd8YvpumLOeORToMI3GMmHlRHfa4-pJfvWdAVnS9QIKfUf_DhxlfEVpXAdlxx0rPxANBTNP_PS28H0TAw=s0" alt="pexels website" width="850" height="474" /></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Pexels offers more than 10 000 free and royalty free pictures that you can use for just about anything! This means that you can use them for your website, publish them on your social networks, or even modify them to better suit your needs.</p>
<p style="text-align: center"><a href="https://www.pexels.com/" class="creativ-shortcode creativ-shortcode-button creativ-shortcode-button-colour-white creativ-shortcode-button-size-medium creativ-shortcode-button-edge-straight" target="_self">Visit Website</a></p>
<hr class="dash" />
<h3 style="text-align: center">Unsplash</h3>
<p><img class="shadow_medium aligncenter wp-image-282 size-full" src="https://booxi-live-wp-storage.storage.googleapis.com/unsplash-blog-e1472502412211.png" alt="site web Unsplash" width="1000" height="557" /></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Unsplash is a website offering thousands of high resolution photos. Again, these photos are completely free and can be used in any context. Also, Unsplash uploads ten new photos every ten days, so be sure to visit this website often!</p>
<p style="text-align: center"><a href="https://unsplash.com/" class="creativ-shortcode creativ-shortcode-button creativ-shortcode-button-colour-white creativ-shortcode-button-size-medium creativ-shortcode-button-edge-straight" target="_self">Visit Website</a></p>
<hr class="dash" />
<h3 style="text-align: center">Fotolia</h3>
<p><img class="shadow_medium aligncenter wp-image-283" src="http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/r6MyqS5RTRFCbD18kxOuyXYW2ObVpXEs9CjmN6lmRRSHJIT8P8AQp1k1-BQCP7ogdC51r3AY3N4nbNPxOSefEw=s0" alt="site web fotolia" width="850" height="474" /></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p style="text-align: left">Still can’t find what you are looking for? Try Fotolia, one of the largest global image databases. With 60 million media (photos, videos, illustrations), you will surely find a photo suitable for your website. In addition, they offer several ways to buy pictures on their website, either by credit or monthly/annual subscription.</p>
<p style="text-align: center"><a href="https://us.fotolia.com/" class="creativ-shortcode creativ-shortcode-button creativ-shortcode-button-colour-white creativ-shortcode-button-size-medium creativ-shortcode-button-edge-straight" target="_self">Visit Website</a></p>
<hr />
<h2 style="text-align: center">Photo Editors</h2>
<hr class="dash" />
<h3 style="text-align: center">Canva</h3>
<p><img class="shadow_medium aligncenter wp-image-284" src="http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/wgs3oABsnwVH00Aa72CkQtv49f2WtJA7MY00DE-C5P1JxzHDEank2Qtmu_rWcWuFsxRGRCeB55hfkEypQjuhAg=s0" alt="site web canva" width="850" height="472" /></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Canva is a platform that allows you to become a pro in graphic design within minutes! You can edit your own photos, or select a picture directly from their selection of over one million royalty-free images. You can modify, add filters, or text on your images. Also, Canva allows you to easily create visual for your social networks or even for an advertising flyer.</p>
<p style="text-align: center"><a href="https://www.canva.com/" class="creativ-shortcode creativ-shortcode-button creativ-shortcode-button-colour-white creativ-shortcode-button-size-medium creativ-shortcode-button-edge-straight" target="_self">Visit Website</a></p>
<hr class="dash" />
<h3 style="text-align: center">Pixlr</h3>
<p><img class="shadow_medium aligncenter wp-image-285" src="http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/jSR8amLcQygB0DKp6gGJ2c81BpB-MQ2G6_tKO9ZJCdETTuRTrC0n8QTjYxCcsEa_UwKso_Y753EPmZOMHf8eNw=s0" alt="site web pixlr" width="850" height="575" /></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>You have a little more knowledge in photo editing? With its French interface, Pixlr offers a multitude of features to enhance the quality of your images. Brightness to cropping, through photo editing, Pixlr offers similar functionality as the professional photo editors, but for free!</p>
<p style="text-align: center"><a href="https://pixlr.com/" class="creativ-shortcode creativ-shortcode-button creativ-shortcode-button-colour-white creativ-shortcode-button-size-medium creativ-shortcode-button-edge-straight" target="_self">Visit Website</a></p>
<hr class="dash" />
<h3 style="text-align: center">PicMonkey</h3>
<p><img class="shadow_medium aligncenter wp-image-286 size-full" src="https://booxi-live-wp-storage.storage.googleapis.com/picmonkey-blog.png" alt="site web picmonkey" width="1000" height="552" /></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p style="text-align: center"><a href="https://www.picmonkey.com/" class="creativ-shortcode creativ-shortcode-button creativ-shortcode-button-colour-white creativ-shortcode-button-size-medium creativ-shortcode-button-edge-straight" target="_self">Visit Website</a></p>
<hr />
<p>Webself is a free and easy tool to create website. Choose your design, add your texts and pictures and publish your website on the Internet. It has never been easier to create a website! No computer knowledge required, only your imagination ! Start building your own website today.</p>
<p><a href="http://www.webself.net"><br />
<img class="aligncenter wp-image-289 size-full" src="http://booxi-live-wp-storage.storage.googleapis.com/2016-08-26.jpg" alt="2016-08-26" width="1440" height="600" /></a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.booxi.com/blog/6-tools-for-stunning-photos-for-your-website/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>booxi in partnership with appyourself</title>
		<link>https://www.booxi.com/blog/booxi-in-partnership-with-appyourself/</link>
		<comments>https://www.booxi.com/blog/booxi-in-partnership-with-appyourself/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 Aug 2016 20:28:49 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Astrid Bertout]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[online visibility]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[website]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.booxi.com/blog-dev/?p=173</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[booxi combined with appyourself provides you all you need to be visible online and to convert, easily and at a very affordable bugdet, visitors to customers. ]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img class="float_top aligncenter wp-image-225 size-full" src="https://booxi-live-wp-storage.storage.googleapis.com/Appyourself-booxi2.png" alt="partnership appyourself + booxi" width="1200" height="628" />Creating Your Own Website and Mobile Application Has Never Been Easier 85% of internet users go online with their computer, tablet or smartphone to shop around before they buy. Will they find you? Is your service offer well presented and up-to-date? Do you succeed to convert visitors into customers ? Aware that you have to be visible on the Internet and social media, that you may not be an expert at it, and that you may not have the time and bugdet for it ; appyourself has developed a solution to help you manage all of your Internet communication channels from a single interface! booxi combined with appyourself provides you all you need to easily achieve your goals at very affordable budget.</p>
<h3>Web-Mobile-Facebook: One Platform for All.</h3>
<div id="attachment_174" style="width: 1034px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img class="wp-image-174 size-large" src="http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/TV8znA3v_SW1B7no9ghlVWbUcVFA_wvmsIBtLNTptb0DFQonrk0IwXh5EN7LLkhSsAi1usThtfAeUeokUqp3vF0=s1024" alt="appyourself interface on multiple devices" width="1024" height="1024" /><p class="wp-caption-text">appyourself interface on multiple devices</p></div>
<p>appyourself allows you to easily get a “custom-made” responsive website (it will fit all the screen : computer, tablet or smartphone). You can also complete your offer by creating your own applications for iPhone and Android, to build your customer loyalty. Facebook application is a mini-website integrated to your page which will allow you to increase your direct booking. The appyourself toolbox gives you the freedom to customize your online image (by creating as many pages as you want for your website, customizing the colors and the layout of the different sections, adding your own images, and more) without even coding a single line of HTML, and without technical knowledge. From this point, you will be able to make changes by yourself, when you want them, and your website will always be up-to-date.</p>
<blockquote>
<p style="text-align: center">A single interface to manage your Internet communication channels.</p>
</blockquote>
<h3>Convert Your Online Visitors into Customers</h3>
<p>It is good to be visible and to have online traffic, but it is even better when you can convert those visitors into customers. It is crucial to provide a call-to-action on your website, to engage your visitors. That’s why appyourself partnered with booxi, to integrate online appointment booking directly in your website. With this easy and efficient appointment management solution, you can convert more visitors into customers. This means more appointments and more revenues for you.</p>
<h3>Build Customer Loyalty</h3>
<p>With the integrated booxi and appyourself CRMs, you have a better knowledge of your customer’s habits and needs, as well as a way to maintain contact with them. To keep in touch with your customers and your leads, you can use templates made available to you to prepare marketing campaigns like newsletters or promotions as examples.</p>
<hr />
<p style="text-align: center">appyourself also allows you to manage your online reputation following your customers feedback from the solution.</p>
<p style="text-align: center"><strong>Develop and retain your customers on Internet.<br />
</strong> <strong>To see appyourself in action</strong></p>
<p style="text-align: center"><a href="http://ressources.appyourself.com/en-demonstration?utm_source=booxi&amp;utm_medium=newsletter&amp;utm_campaign=qc-juillet-2016" class="creativ-shortcode creativ-shortcode-button creativ-shortcode-button-colour-allgreen creativ-shortcode-button-size-medium creativ-shortcode-button-edge-straight" target="_blank">Request a demo </a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.booxi.com/blog/booxi-in-partnership-with-appyourself/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Get More Customers Through Internet ?</title>
		<link>https://www.booxi.com/blog/get-more-customers-through-internet/</link>
		<comments>https://www.booxi.com/blog/get-more-customers-through-internet/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2016 16:29:34 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[booxi-admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Business Tips]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[online visibility]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[user experience]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[website]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.booxi.com/blog-dev/?p=60</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Today 86% of customers use Internet. Then it is a great opportunity for you to get more clients. Here are some tips to optimize your chances to convert your online traffic into real customers.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img class="float_top shadow_large aligncenter wp-image-391 size-full" src="https://booxi-live-wp-storage.storage.googleapis.com/photo_1460954037_temp.jpg" alt="Use Internet to get more customers" width="1050" height="700" /><br />
<div class="creativ-shortcode creativ-shortcode-cols  creativ-shortcode-cols-half-half "><div class="creativ-shortcode creativ-shortcode-col creativ-shortcode-col-a"><div class="creativ-shortcode-col-inner"><p>Whether you have just started your business or you are already well settled, you invest time to develop new customers. To be sure to invest your efforts in a good way, here are some guidelines to get more customers through Internet</p>
</div></div></p>
<div class="creativ-shortcode creativ-shortcode-col creativ-shortcode-col-b"><div class="creativ-shortcode-col-inner"></div></div>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<ul>
<li>Increase your visibility</li>
<li>Enhance the user experience</li>
<li>Involve Your Current Customers To Attract New Ones</div></li>
</ul>
<hr />
<h3>Increase Your Visibility</h3>
<p>The first step is to be easily and professionaly available online. You don’t need to be a technology expert, there is a lot of solutions to create a website in a few clics, even for limited budgets. For example, 85 % of the consumers have a Facebook account. That’s why create a business Facebook page is a good start. Later an automated website from booxi, or from <a href="http://www.appyourself.com/fr-ca">appyourself</a>, or <a href="http://en.webself.net/">Webself</a> for example, will provide you a website on a little budget. Then increase the visibility of your website by sharing useful content regularly on your social networks. You can, for example, inform them about your news, your promotions, a change in your open hours or give them advice. You don’t need to be on all the social networks. The most efficient communication is the one that use the tool that your customers actually use. For example :</p>
<ul>
<li>Twitter to announce a slot last minute with a discount</li>
<li><span style="line-height: 21.6px">Facebook, to share information about your promotions or to post articles</span></li>
<li><span style="line-height: 21.6px">Instagram or Pinterest, greatly facilitate sharing photos and pictures, if your business plays in the beauty, visual and creativity industries.</span></li>
<li><span style="line-height: 21.6px">Finally keep in mind that it is usual to publish the same message on different platforms, as long as the format is adapted.</span></li>
</ul>
<h3>Enhance The User Experience</h3>
<p>Once your customers find you online, be sure that it is very simple for them to book an appointment with you. First, you have to be easily reachable by adding the information of all the means to contact you. Clearly indicate your details on your website and maybe add the online appointment booking. Your customers can make an appointment at the time that suit them best, even out of your open hours and without having to leave a voice message. You would be surprised to see how much people prefer to avoid the phone. When they have the opportunity to do it, around 20% of customers will book online. If your customers have to make an additional effort to reach you, they won’t do it.</p>
<h3>Involve Your Current Customers To Attract New Ones</h3>
<p>Finally your current customers are your best ambassadors. You can encourage them to testimony, by sharing their reviews on you social networks. And the more they will comment, like and share your publications, the more your visibility will increase.</p>
<ul>
<li>Likes and shares increase the visibility of your publication on news feed</li>
<li><span style="line-height: 21.6px">Comments will be display on their friends news feed</span></li>
<li><span style="line-height: 21.6px">People rely heavily on advice from their friends</span></li>
<li><span style="line-height: 21.6px">Finally, the more interactions you have on your page, the more your page will appear and reach people.</span></li>
</ul>
<p>To conclude, online presence is imperative, the use of social networks will bring new customers to discover your business and to make online appointment with you.</p>
<hr />
<p style="text-align: center">booxi can help you to easily complete those steps. Try it for free during 30 days &#8211; no credit card required.</p>
<p style="text-align: center"><a href="https://www.booxi.com/en" class="creativ-shortcode creativ-shortcode-button creativ-shortcode-button-colour-allgreen creativ-shortcode-button-size-medium creativ-shortcode-button-edge-straight" target="_blank">Read More ?</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.booxi.com/blog/get-more-customers-through-internet/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to make my website look amazing?</title>
		<link>https://www.booxi.com/blog/how-to-make-my-website-look-amazing/</link>
		<comments>https://www.booxi.com/blog/how-to-make-my-website-look-amazing/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2016 19:06:09 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Astrid Bertout]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Business Tips]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[customer]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[online visibility]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[website]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.booxi.com/blog-dev/?p=23</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Some tips to have an great website that will catch the attention of your customers and increase your online visibility. ]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img class="float_top aligncenter wp-image-815 size-full" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/u7KXnAvXf20hlJD2vDrDlXrgjs-rA5Wm-8pq8g1j9gUxqx2nOowJjSV1V_zLIs4_jPAcFqKf--Vwy2pOBqak=s0" alt="website for your business" width="1200" height="600" /><div class="creativ-shortcode creativ-shortcode-cols  creativ-shortcode-cols-half-half "><div class="creativ-shortcode creativ-shortcode-col creativ-shortcode-col-a"><div class="creativ-shortcode-col-inner"><p>You have a great online visibility tool, your booxi website, so lets make sure it looks awesome by following the tips provided in this article.</p>
</div></div></p>
<div class="creativ-shortcode creativ-shortcode-col creativ-shortcode-col-b"><div class="creativ-shortcode-col-inner"></div></div>
<ul>
<li>Business description that sells</li>
<li>A good service offer</li>
<li>A team they can trust</li>
<li>Delightful pictures</li>
<li>More links, more visibility</li>
<li>Share it</div></li>
</ul>
<hr />
<p>It won&#8217;t take much time and efforts, but it will provide great results as every little detail is important and for customers to find what they are looking for.</p>
<h3>Business description that sells</h3>
<p>It&#8217;s important to write a description that sells your business. Try to be catchy; use short sentences and a friendly vocabulary so customers quickly get what your business is all about. Identify your competitive advantage; what makes you different from your competitors and write them down. Consider adding the following:</p>
<ul>
<li>How long you have been in business (if more than 3 years)</li>
<li>Your expertise</li>
<li>Accreditation</li>
</ul>
<p>The most important thing to remember here is to be concise and sell your business.</p>
<h3>A good service offer</h3>
<p>If you offer many services, list them all, even if you do not wish to offer online booking for all of them (you can disable online booking for specific services). If you don&#8217;t list some services, customers will assume you don&#8217;t offer them at all. You can organize your service in categories to make it easier to understand. Show the prices, the duration and add a full description that sells the service. The more details you give, the better. It is important to be concise and clear in all your descriptions.</p>
<p><img style="font-weight: normal;color: #000000" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/dTTdbd1h53HI9mDe_IogJVNqdMFXxCqeKfaZ4__40Sj2aVQbOfPckcaclVoXAuPlM_1yFjFNCJ5iHv8tSEnXV_mfM_HLzBx4pNuJMSl3l9uPWiEb3baOCqgfq9HJ216pv-dNyLE" alt="" />Add a new service</p>
<p><img style="font-weight: normal;color: #000000" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/vX5jPqrhHrZfRxafVASmplWlJi5Syax8bQIwmWG0OJiYBgnXD_BK3w-PUtILeZyvrMrySgeQUKkHXDClAdslrPv9_dlzUqGUEpKmPMWMGO-kXlhT0ZEeScbMtaKt_3KXsMKaz_o" alt="" />Add a category of service<br />
<img class="shadow_medium aligncenter wp-image-112 size-full" src="http://booxi-live-wp-storage.storage.googleapis.com/promotion.jpg" alt="service offer" width="914" height="843" /></p>
<h3>A team they can trust</h3>
<p>Customers have to trust you, and it has been proven that when they see a face, it becomes easier for them to trust. Which is why we strongly recommend that you list your personnel with pictures. Provide a position, so customers know who is who, and a short bio that should sell the merits of this skilled professional. Consider adding the following:</p>
<ul>
<li>Years of experience</li>
<li>Particular skills or diplomas</li>
<li>Name of the association the person is a member of</li>
</ul>
<p>You may ask your personnel to fill their profile on their own. Make sure to update the list of services they offer, so customers understand what they do.</p>
<p><img class="shadow_medium aligncenter wp-image-113 size-full" src="http://booxi-live-wp-storage.storage.googleapis.com/promomotion.jpg" alt="listpersonnel" width="308" height="368" /></p>
<h3>Delightful Pictures</h3>
<p>Consumers love to visualize before buying and statistics show that websites and posts that have pictures are more viewed by consumers. Images make everything more attractive, trustworthy and thanks to them it is easier for customers to understand what the services are about. Add photos of your business (cover and logo), your personnel, and your services. A page with pictures is eye catching and shows that your are a professional in your field.</p>
<p>You can upload pictures using your desktop computer, a tablet or use your smartphone with our mobile app to take and associate pictures to your services and personnel.</p>
<p><img class="shadow_medium aligncenter wp-image-114 size-full" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/MFMoNja0qu534-UDqUXL6gTn3GDMl6fmluAF0PkK6AcVrH198M5TEC4Dhq0MOBpL3sxFiJwkasdkv7ql3isN=s0" alt="picture website" width="1601" height="531" /><br />
If you do not have a logo like most self-employed professionals, simply use your profile picture as a logo. If you don&#8217;t have pictures, here are <a href="https://www.booxi.com/blog/6-tools-for-stunning-photos-for-your-website/" target="_blank">6 tools for stunning photos</a>.</p>
<h3>More links, more visibility</h3>
<p>If you have another website, add a link to it on your booxi page (Business details section &#8211; website). It will give you more visibility and help Google search results.</p>
<h3>Share it</h3>
<p>Now that you have an attractive booxi website, share it and make sure it is visible everywhere you are. Add it to your Facebook page, Linkedin, Google plus, Twitter and Pinterest. The more links you create, the more people will find you and take appointments with you. Add links to your booxi website also improves your SEO, meaning that it increases your chances to <a href="https://www.booxi.com/blog/get-more-visibility-by-registering-with-google-my-business-2/" target="_blank">come up first in Google search</a>.</p>
<h3></h3>
<p>Now that your have your website, make sure it <a href="https://www.booxi.com/blog/get-online-visibility-in-8-simple-steps-with-tiny-budget/" target="_blank">drives traffic</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.booxi.com/blog/how-to-make-my-website-look-amazing/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>How can I use my booxi URL?</title>
		<link>https://www.booxi.com/blog/how-can-i-use-my-booxi-url/</link>
		<comments>https://www.booxi.com/blog/how-can-i-use-my-booxi-url/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2016 18:59:51 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Astrid Bertout]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Tutorials]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[online visibility]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[website]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.booxi.com/blog-dev/?p=19</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Get more visibility by maximizing your booxi URL use. ]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><div class="creativ-shortcode creativ-shortcode-cols  creativ-shortcode-cols-half-half "><div class="creativ-shortcode creativ-shortcode-col creativ-shortcode-col-a"><div class="creativ-shortcode-col-inner"><p>
Now that you are the lucky owner of a booxi website, you can take full advantage of it by making good use of your URL, meaning the unique web address that was reserved for you.</p>
</div></div><br />
<div class="creativ-shortcode creativ-shortcode-col creativ-shortcode-col-b"><div class="creativ-shortcode-col-inner"></div></div></p>
<ul>
<li>Your unique and personalised URL</li>
<li>Where to find your URL ?</li>
<li>Where to use it ?</div></li>
</ul>
<hr />
<h3>Your unique and personalized URL</h3>
<p>booxi has reserved for you, a unique URL that you can share everywhere, as if it was a domain name like mybusiness.com. booxi created a simple and short URL that matches your business name and looks like that: www.booxi.com/YourBusinessName.</p>
<p>You can use this URL as the address for your main website, and put it on your business card, post it on social networks, or include it in your emails. If you have another website, and it does not yet have the Book Now button, you may want to use your booxi website as much as possible so your clients can book appointments.</p>
<h3>Where to find your URL?</h3>
<p>You can find your booxi URL within your Business Details, or in your booxi website using the following steps.</p>
<ol>
<li>Go to your booxi website using FIND A BUSINESS.</li>
<li>Click on Share this page</li>
<li>Copy-Paste the URL (Copy this link) or click on <img style="color: #000000" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/8jxzhr1Fitp4BDOor22l34R2L5WTRm6Eyh5PTt3yGIJzO_m4sLNbcjqWG-rQkmIpieiHPoGUHx_kTZO6PdRVoMISAgYsJjqaLKMGNCgu3vwMHFolNDE81fGL0nf5vyuxinz4aJA" alt="" width="42" height="27" /></li>
<li>You can now paste the link wherever you want.<img class="shadow_medium aligncenter" src="https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/GeALATKPDaVyyKzsCzDV67ioYyIx26UbwPFe4qL7LkYPTFTNt5nTyc8etUwpCr0kFT5P2ax1utrTf75Acx5Q8F-0vnZi74rFtK7kFDmnGPdNbEI3Qp00AfQaTgTfDRRrbzSUEjg" alt="" width="1422" height="546" /></li>
</ol>
<h3>Where to use it?</h3>
<p>The objective is to increase your visibility, and get more people to book appointment with you. Paste your URL in all the posts you do on your facebook or google plus pages; add it to your classified ads; and add it to profiles you create in any online directory. You should also make sure to add it to your email template or email signature, so it is in every email you send.</p>
<p>This way clients will have an easy access to your website, and an easy access to book every time you communicate with them.</p>
<h3>Things to remember:</h3>
<ul>
<li>Your unique URL can be used as your own domain name.</li>
<li>Use it everywhere so people can easily find you and book appointments with you.</li>
</ul>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.booxi.com/blog/how-can-i-use-my-booxi-url/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>