<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>booxi &#187; integration</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.booxi.com/blog/tag/integration/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.booxi.com/blog</link>
	<description>booxi</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2017 18:59:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
		<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
		<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>http://wordpress.org/?v=3.9.1</generator>
	<item>
		<title>How to use booxi with Lightspeed?</title>
		<link>https://www.booxi.com/blog/tutorial-use-lightspeed-with-booxi/</link>
		<comments>https://www.booxi.com/blog/tutorial-use-lightspeed-with-booxi/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2016 19:08:34 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Astrid Bertout]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Tutorials]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[integration]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Lightspeed]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[point of sales]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.booxi.com/blog-dev/?p=25</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[In this article we show you how to use Lightspeed, POS system, with booxi, to save even more time. ]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="float_top creativ-shortcode creativ-shortcode-video-embed"><iframe class="post_vid_iframe" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/pAHoHQcJ-nk" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div>
<p><div class="creativ-shortcode creativ-shortcode-cols  creativ-shortcode-cols-half-half "><div class="creativ-shortcode creativ-shortcode-col creativ-shortcode-col-a"><div class="creativ-shortcode-col-inner"><p>In this step by step tutorial, we will demonstrate you how to setup your Lightspeed module in booxi, and how to create sales in Lightspeed from booxi appointments.</p>
<p>This tutorial covers the following topics:</p>
</div></div><br />
<div class="creativ-shortcode creativ-shortcode-col creativ-shortcode-col-b"><div class="creativ-shortcode-col-inner"></div></div></p>
<ul>
<li>How to setup the Lightspeed module</li>
<li>How to link services to Lightspeed sale items</li>
<li>How to link personnel to Lightspeed employees</li>
<li>How to create a sale in Lightspeed from a booxi appointment</div></li>
</ul>
<hr />
<p>We assume in this tutorial that you already know how to use both Lightspeed and booxi, as well as you have already completed the review of your booxi business profile, including your service offer and your personnel. If not, please start with the following tutorial to get familiar with booxi.</p>
<p><a href="http://www.booxi.com/blog-dev/tutorial-review-your-business-profile/">Tutorial &#8211; Review your business profile</a></p>
<p>You must first be signed in your booxi account to complete the following steps.</p>
<h3>Step 1 &#8211; Setup your Lightspeed module</h3>
<p>In order to use booxi with Lightspeed POS, you must setup the Lightspeed module in booxi, using your Lightspeed credentials (email and password).</p>
<ol>
<li>Sign in your booxi if it is not already done.</li>
<li>From the main menu located on the left side of the page, click on My Business.</li>
<li>Click on Modules at the bottom of the section list.<img class="shadow_medium aligncenter wp-image-304" src="http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/KU411_EvRK2yEGzd-CO1ZCTKwKWKH8ABAdYbtUc-jSspz-yugjcyNnbHIonnAn1t_f4v-pLJDvuQgL7x9DMEEw=s1024" alt="Business Modules in booxi" width="850" height="717" /></li>
<li>Locate the Lightspeed module in the list and click the switch to turn it on.<img class="shadow_medium aligncenter wp-image-305 size-full" src="https://booxi-live-wp-storage.storage.googleapis.com/lightspeed-eng.jpg" alt="activate Lightspeed" width="558" height="249" /><img class="shadow_medium aligncenter wp-image-307 size-full" src="https://booxi-live-wp-storage.storage.googleapis.com/enable-lightspeed-module.jpg" alt="Sign in to Lightspeed" width="608" height="484" /></li>
<li>Click on Sign-in to Lightspeed.</li>
<li>A pop up will ask for your Lightspeed credentials (email and password) used to Login your Lightspeed account. If valid, booxi will display your account number and a choice of shops and registers. If not valid, and error message will be displayed.<img class="shadow_medium aligncenter wp-image-309" src="http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/c0lbbwxtp6AqfhX_5WT1h66c8T7x5sHiwgozZloS-MLMiuusFex7YNnA2pIJTdqportAlud44xC30ZYAHS9Q9v4=s0" alt="link booxi with lightspeed" width="650" height="700" /></li>
<li>Select the Associated Shop for which you want to manage appointments.</li>
<li>Select the Preferred Register for this computer, with which the sales will be created.</li>
<li>Now select the Tax Category and Default Tax Class that best define your labor sales tax.</li>
<li>Click Save and you are done.<br />
<img class="shadow_medium aligncenter wp-image-310 size-full" src="http://booxi-live-wp-storage.storage.googleapis.com/save.png" alt="save" width="257" height="61" /></li>
</ol>
<h3>Step 2 &#8211; Associate a service to a Lightspeed sale item</h3>
<p>booxi let you and your clients book appointments for services. When it is time to create a sale for a given appointment, booxi must know which Lightspeed sale item corresponds to which service. You may associate a Lightspeed non inventory sale item for each booxi service using the following steps.</p>
<ol>
<li>From the main menu located on the left side of the page, click on Services.</li>
<li>Select one of your services from the list.</li>
<li>Click on Service Details.<img class="shadow_medium aligncenter wp-image-311" src="http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/s5QNqLTH31KUYk-7VOFpuhgSREseLrNb0YRufgJEUDlxY0Q5yf9wGe-gaYJU9NX5lUp-RDQ_czEl9joTMfWHEQ=s1024" alt="services details" width="850" height="539" /></li>
<li>At the top of the Service Details form, you should see a selection of sale items (Link with Lightspeed). Choose the associated item that should appear in a sale when this service is given.<img class="shadow_medium aligncenter wp-image-312" src="http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/Gn9TppCeEAhsP8co2Tg2GiVqzriLDa651tRUEZAStLYorxjaxH5fRxfWsJ4JRqqm68FxvNkLsHgBM8mbZ_ca=s1024" alt="services details lightspeed" width="650" height="674" /></li>
<li>Click on Save to keep your changes or Undo to cancel.<br />
<img class="shadow_medium aligncenter wp-image-310 size-full" src="http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/CGGj2lc-odtNiN-qC_qUCNyZ8jocQPSdXLYazTiOW9191KEr0AhlV1kQZMhCyv5EpLDJ5D0eI8vNNth8wVZriw=s0" alt="save" width="257" height="61" /></li>
<li>Repeat those steps to link all your services to different sale items. If you do not see a selection of non inventory sale items, it is because your Lightspeed module has not been activated.</li>
</ol>
<h3>Step 3 &#8211; Associate Personnel to Lightspeed Employees</h3>
<p>booxi let you manage appointments for all members of your personnel. When it is time to create a sale for a given appointment, booxi must know which Lightspeed employee has provided the service. You may associate a Lightspeed employee for each booxi personnel using the following steps.</p>
<ol>
<li>From the main menu located on the left side of the page, click on Personnel.</li>
<li>Select one member of your personnel from the list.</li>
<li>Click on Personnel Details.<img class="shadow_medium aligncenter wp-image-313" src="http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/va-ac1BEOYi0TpCZ0rqciYHNf0lZ_29f6Wv967W8yuqA1t5xyNmi8Ss-99sb4dTXGWqK52Ncr7DmJXhOtntwAQ=s1024" alt="personnel" width="850" height="498" /></li>
<li>At the top of the Personnel Details form, you should see a selection of employees (Link with Lightspeed). Choose the associated employee that should appear in a sale when this member of your personnel provides a service.<img class="shadow_medium aligncenter wp-image-314 size-full" src="http://booxi-live-wp-storage.storage.googleapis.com/personnel-details-lightspeed.jpg" alt="personnel details lightspeed" width="557" height="468" /></li>
<li>Click on Save to keep your changes or Undo to cancel.<img class="shadow_medium aligncenter wp-image-310 size-full" src="http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/CGGj2lc-odtNiN-qC_qUCNyZ8jocQPSdXLYazTiOW9191KEr0AhlV1kQZMhCyv5EpLDJ5D0eI8vNNth8wVZriw=s0" alt="save" width="257" height="61" /></li>
<li>Repeat those steps to link all members of your personnel to different employees. If you do not see a selection of employees, it is because your Lightspeed module has not been activated.</li>
</ol>
<h3>Step 4 &#8211; Create a Lightspeed sale from a booxi appointment</h3>
<p>Now that you have setup booxi to work with Lightspeed, you can create a sale for each appointment.</p>
<ol>
<li>From the main menu located on the left side of the page, click on Calendar.</li>
<li>Select an appointment.</li>
<li>Right click on the appointment for which you want to make a sale and select the option New Lightspeed Sale.<img class="shadow_medium aligncenter wp-image-315 size-full" src="http://booxi-live-wp-storage.storage.googleapis.com/menu.jpg" alt="menu" width="495" height="552" /><img class="shadow_medium aligncenter wp-image-316 size-full" src="http://booxi-live-wp-storage.storage.googleapis.com/lightspeed-sale.png" alt="lightspeed sale" width="607" height="797" /></li>
<li>The member of your Personnel providing the service will be set with the appointment details by default, you may change it.</li>
<li>The Service is also set with the appointment details value if the service was linked to a sale item, if not, you may select a non inventory item and link them.</li>
<li>The Client information will be set to the appointment’s client details. If booxi could not find a client match in your Lightspeed customers, you will be able to tell booxi to add this client to your Lightspeed customers.<br />
<img class="shadow_medium aligncenter wp-image-320 size-full" src="http://booxi-live-wp-storage.storage.googleapis.com/add-customer.png" alt="add customer" width="518" height="84" /></li>
<li>You may change the default Register in which the sale will be created.</li>
<li>By default, the employee creating the sale is the current booxi user, you may change the employee selection (Sold by).</li>
<li>Click on Create Sale to create the sale in Lightspeed and change browser window to complete the sale using Lightspeed.</li>
</ol>
<h3>Step 5 &#8211; Create a work order in Lightspeed from a booxi appointment</h3>
<p>Unlike the sales, Lightspeed do not provide APIs to create work orders, so we simply save you time by opening Lightspeed with the right customer, and ready to create the work order yourself. So even though this option is called create work order, it actualy does not create it for you, but instead, save you time on the creating process.</p>
<ol>
<li>From the main menu located on the left side of the page, click on Calendar.</li>
<li>Select an appointment.</li>
<li>Right click on the appointment for which you want to create a work order and select the option New Lightspeed Work Order.<img class="shadow_medium aligncenter wp-image-318 size-full" src="http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/vliJRIPdWTe0o7UreeYVEopVs79H57Vxr5bSsz17iihYNb4Gj3bpubWOyTAjQ9MktvcvaywY2UboX-CWCaVtOg=s0" alt="work order" width="495" height="552" /><br />
<img class="shadow_medium aligncenter wp-image-319 size-full" src="http://booxi-live-wp-storage.storage.googleapis.com/lightsdpeed1.png" alt="lightsdpeed" width="607" height="492" /></li>
<li>The following pop-up appears.<br />
If the customer is already link between Lightspeed and booxi all you have to do is to click on New Work Order.<br />
<span style="line-height: 21.6px">If the customer doesn’t exist in Lightspeed, the option Add a new customer in Lightspeed appears. Click on New Work Order.<br />
<img class="shadow_medium aligncenter wp-image-317 size-full" style="color: #000000" src="http://booxi-live-wp-storage.storage.googleapis.com/add-a-new-customer-in-lightspeed.png" alt="add a new customer in lightspeed" width="536" height="86" /><br />
</span></li>
<li>Complete the Work Order like you usually do in Lightspeed.</li>
</ol>
<h3>Step 6 &#8211; Import Your Lightspeed Customers in booxi</h3>
<p>Even though booxi allows you to match a booxi client with a Lightspeed customer every time you make a sale or you create a work order, you may want to import all your Lightspeed customer in booxi at once, and do the matching in advance to save time on the long run.</p>
<ol>
<li>From the main menu located on the left side of the page, click on the tab Client.</li>
<li>Then click on the Options Icon</li>
<li>And select Import from Lightspeed.<img class="shadow_medium aligncenter wp-image-321" src="http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/pZ921idbGyZClo4UbkTxEBvwp2HzTTeAQK2sYFo7m4mhv47SoYEI7gPoXCqOtGIiziWXlQJt78PcUJxZAfmIzg=s0" alt="import Lightspeed" width="750" height="421" /></li>
<li>This pop-up will appear. Click on the button Import Customers, and the import will be instantly done.<img class="shadow_medium aligncenter wp-image-322" src="http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/HNK4Y_bKaLXkypWB51uWifXxvC_W72sDylqanI8jIxb2q8EbbLw8VQT6afTld2yltsQWXNKxzNzZ18YWCRuH=s0" alt="import" width="650" height="456" /></li>
<li>And you’re done.</li>
</ol>
<h3>Things to remember</h3>
<p>Activate and setup your Lightspeed module in booxi.<br />
Associate (link) your booxi services to Lightspeed non inventory items.<br />
Associate (link) your booxi personnel to Lightspeed employees.<br />
Create a sales in Lightspeed from a booxi appointment.<br />
Create a work order in Lightspeed from a booxi appointment.<br />
Add new clients to your Lightspeed customers when you create sales or work order from booxi.<br />
Use Lightspeed in one browser window and booxi in another one, so you can easily navigate between Lightspeed for sales and booxi for appointments.</p>
<p>To know more about Lightspeed, <a title="Lightspeed" href="https://www.lightspeedhq.com/%20">click here.</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.booxi.com/blog/tutorial-use-lightspeed-with-booxi/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>