<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>booxi &#187; social network</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.booxi.com/blog/tag/social-network/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.booxi.com/blog</link>
	<description>booxi</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2017 18:59:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
		<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
		<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>http://wordpress.org/?v=3.9.1</generator>
	<item>
		<title>12 creative ways to benefit from Instagram</title>
		<link>https://www.booxi.com/blog/12-creative-ways-to-benefit-from-instagram/</link>
		<comments>https://www.booxi.com/blog/12-creative-ways-to-benefit-from-instagram/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2017 15:51:50 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Astrid Bertout]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Business Tips]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Customer Acquisition]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[online visibility]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social network]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.booxi.com/blog/?p=1229</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Help your beauty salon get noticed with 12 great Instagram post ideas. ]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img class="float_top aligncenter wp-image-1230 size-full" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/8JmwZulno89yNK_B_Q5OdUh1moD4l4t79TyLBT0PV_ifXV0rwIqBne0DfYG-CT8NTXFnbIL_74qoPsQdbY7UMA=s0" alt="benefit from instagram" width="1200" height="600" /></p>
<p>According to <a href="https://business.instagram.com/blog/500000-advertisers/">Instagram Advertiser Statistics</a>, 50% of Instagrammers follow a business account. Even more interesting for you, 60% of Instagrammers say they’ve found information about a product or service through the application.<br />
And most importantly, 75% of Instagrammers either visit a website, do research, buy a product/use a service, or talk to a friend after being inspired by a post.</p>
<p>This is a great opportunity to enhance your online visibility, acquire new customers and increase your sales &#8211; especially if you work in an industry where visual presentation is important. Like beauty and wellness, for example.</p>
<p>To begin, don’t use your personal account. Make sure to<a href="https://www.booxi.com/blog/how-to-create-your-business-instagram-account-a-step-by-step-guide/" target="_blank"> create a separate business account </a>instead. This way, you’ll benefit from professional features that will help convert your online visitors into customers. Then, once they become customers,there are other features that will analyze their behaviour.</p>
<ul>
<li>As you know, Instagram is an image-sharing platform, so make sure you only post high-quality photos and videos. This may seem like obvious advice, but you’d be surprised how often sub-standard images are used. Remember, everything you share will affect your business image and reputation, so make sure you choose wisely.</li>
<li>Make sure to add all the relevant information to your profile. This way, your followers will be able to interact easily with your business, or contact you directly if they need to.<img class="shadow_small aligncenter wp-image-1233" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/VEMfBBU6WRe6BeMN-bAaWYKoP8qtQQeqH14OitlX4diQvx_lcEX3AFhpmd3xFGk81mOlBywRAVRqAdCrhtkZbQ=s0" alt="etiket instagram account" width="484" height="861" /><br />
As an example, Etiket’s bio includes a business description, a mention of the industry they work in, a link to their website and three separate calls to action: Call, Email, and Directions. (Just in case you’re not aware, a call to action is a button designed to provoke an immediate response. Ex: Call Now)</li>
<li>Use popular and relevant hashtags that are related to your industry. Why?</li>
</ul>
<p>Because hashtags extend your reach and make it easier for Instagrammers to find your content. In addition, posts with at least one <a href="http://get.simplymeasured.com/rs/simplymeasured2/images/InstagramStudy2014Q3.pdf?mkt_tok=3RkMMJWWfF9wsRolua%252FAZKXonjHpfsX57%252BwtX6a2lMI%252F0ER3fOvrPUfGjI4CTsViI%252BSLDwEYGJlv6SgFQrDEMal41bgNWRM%253D">hashtag generate 12.6% more engagement</a> on average.</p>
<p>How can you think of great hashtags for your posts?</p>
<p>To get inspired, do a hashtag search and see what the most popular hashtags on Instagram are.</p>
<p><img class="shadow_small aligncenter wp-image-1231" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/N4xtaQxQ0sB5SYoPNpTo5CwFUASM9-3F9_ZMszzWs7D2_UenH_5VHOimpwgsV2LtDR8EAPxzKvHMxRIHJPg3epw=s0" alt="hashtag research" width="439" height="781" /></p>
<p>You can also follow other businesses in your industry and see what kind of hashtags they’ve added to their posts. Obviously don’t copy them, but definitely draw inspiration from them.</p>
<p>Finally, you can also use a tool to find the most relevant hashtags for your pictures. Like<a href="https://focalmark.com/">Focalmark</a>, for example. In just a few clicks, you’ll be able to find the most relevant hashtags for the images you’re sharing. And the tool’s algorithm will provide the most popular hashtags for a specific audience.</p>
<p>How many hashtags should you use?</p>
<p>It’s important to add hashtags, but make sure not to go overboard with them.<br />
A study by <a href="https://trackmaven.com/blog/everything-marketers-need-know-instagram-sponsored-content/">TrackMaven</a> shows that posts with 4-5 hashtags generate the most interactions.</p>
<p><img class="shadow_small aligncenter wp-image-1234 size-full" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/prQ55hLSwRBR_LIF3HsS-MMBVL0X42nhkpoM_vkoBOoY9VtMglwvbua-0y347nHTtDc0DIJhk_5MKlg8bpP1=s0" alt="interactions by hashtags" width="805" height="448" /></p>
<p>You can also create a hashtag that uses your business name. So when your followers share pictures about you, they can add a specific hashtag and mention your business name (@businessexample) at the same time.Not only is it a good way to start creating an online community around your business, butit will also make it very easy to know when someone mentions your business on Instagram.</p>
<ul>
<li>Like any other social network, you have to interact with other Instagram users in order to create a community. So make sure to comment on their posts and like their accounts. But that doesn’t mean you should like every account you come across. Instead, find the ones that reflect the values and image you want your business to have and like those.Similarly, you can follow people who’ve subscribed to your account. And if someone mentions your business on their account, take the time to reply. It will show your audience that you’re interested in them and that you’d like to interact with them.</li>
<li>Use Instagram stories to give your followers a peek at your day-to-day business.</li>
</ul>
<p>*What’s a story?<br />
A story is a live video shared on Instagram. It’s temporary, disappearing after 24 hours.</p>
<p>Stories are a good way to create relationships based on direct interaction. A study conducted by Social Bakers shows that <a href="https://www.socialbakers.com/blog/2621-instagram-stories-five-things-marketers-need-to-know">stories have a positive impact on your overall Instagram performance</a>. After watching a story, a follower is more likely to visit your account and interact with it (by liking or commenting on your photos, for example).</p>
<ul>
<li>Use your Instagram account to share useful content with your followers.</li>
</ul>
<p>Are you a hair salon owner? Make a short video tutorial that features an easy do-it-yourself hairstyle.</p>
<p>Are you a beauty salon owner? Post a short video tutorial about makeup that your followers can easily reproduce on their own.</p>
<p>Are you a wellness center owner? Give advice about nutrition, health and well-being, and provide tips your followers can use in their daily lives.</p>
<ul>
<li>Share quotes that inspire and motivate. Learn how to <a href="https://www.booxi.com/blog/how-to-create-shareable-images-that-drive-traffic/">create shareable images that drive traffic </a>by following this guide.  (what guide are you referring to exactly?)<br />
You can also share inspirational lifestyle photos.</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li>You can also post photos that are related to calendar events.For example, during winter,<a href="https://www.instagram.com/sephora/?hl=en">Sephora</a> shared a picture of two products that were placed in snow.<br />
Similarly, <a href="https://www.instagram.com/marcellecosmetics/?hl=en">Marcellecosmetics</a>posted a photo featuring lipsticks and hearts during Valentine’s day.<img class="shadow_small aligncenter wp-image-1235" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-XKS6XONFLlwm5HAYU_4K-SqLDY1QytfJv4rG3haUzUUHF7fffTanlSGmvsiI3EZ43w3fXC4KEU_uaTl9AyQ=s0" alt="promotion ideas based on calendar" width="745" height="683" /></li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li>Post photos of all the members of your team. On Instagram, pictures with people get <a href="http://expandedramblings.com/index.php/important-instagram-stats/13/">38% more likes</a> than those without, and get 32% more comments. It’s a great way to humanize your business.</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li>Also share customer-generated content about your business and products,  and make sure to tag them. Why? Because the content has already been created, and so it’s saved you time. More importantly,<a href="https://zuberance.com/zuberrants/category/top-10-stats-about-online-reviews">88% of people trust online reviews from strangers</a> as much as personal recommendations. Plus, it’s a good way to show your followers that you’re interested in them, which in turn helps you build a closer relationship.</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li>Share some pictures of your products and make them stand out by displaying them in a creative way.<img class="shadow_small aligncenter wp-image-1236" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/Xh2Ki_2W5jv36ZohjR7KRoBc9bFViBR1UXn8RQwIZ-tCzapqobKM-3gsNul6QpzGa_gG7TejyE4Bs2GKaNgkDog=s0" alt="display your products" width="440" height="783" />On the other hand, don’t only post product shots on your account. That’ll bore your followers in a hurry.</li>
<li>Finally, share some stunning Before &amp; After photos. It’s a great way to get people interested in your services.<img class="shadow_small aligncenter wp-image-1237" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/TnCxbc7em6XEPuAZtzbMw4FlzX3x1QCSz7IRibqHv8lfSCemgvOQWgPB0XuAy8S9uDcKWO4rJetOLW0v5mlGJg=s0" alt="before/after picture" width="670" height="430" /></li>
</ul>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.booxi.com/blog/12-creative-ways-to-benefit-from-instagram/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Create Shareable Images That Drive Traffic?</title>
		<link>https://www.booxi.com/blog/how-to-create-shareable-images-that-drive-traffic/</link>
		<comments>https://www.booxi.com/blog/how-to-create-shareable-images-that-drive-traffic/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2017 14:57:27 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Astrid Bertout]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Business Tips]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[online visibility]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social network]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.booxi.com/blog/?p=1049</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Posts that contain photos are 2.3x more engaging than those without photos. In addition inspirational quotes can lead to post interaction, especially shares. Here are a few quick tips to help you create shareable visuals by combining photos and quotes. ]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p style="text-align: left"><a href="http://buzzsumo.com/blog/how-to-massively-boost-your-blog-traffic-with-these-5-awesome-image-stats/"><img class="float_top aligncenter wp-image-1073 size-full" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/lOoGupjaXYu4-yaklSfR1MNdB0zNlmwcdE7Mx7uZSv6Tx6bTmaVDhOffGpYBWrSTOki8Km0SzbVvzc4YVQIDjg=s0" alt="create your own pictures" width="1200" height="600" />Mike Gingerich</a>, writer at Social Media Examiner, says that “people love inspirational quotes that motivate them or elicit a particular emotion, which in turn can lead to post interaction, especially shares”.</p>
<p>This seems to be a winning strategy since it can make more people aware of your business and potentially lead to new customers.</p>
<p>In addition, Facebook posts that contain photos are 2.3x more engaging than those without photos.</p>
<p><img class="wp-image-1050 size-full aligncenter" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/dITfPx5UnGwgv_KA6rECtYN311_Yw_XCtIxEpV_hndjopK1xkqMTQ8EDz5uh-BcqmHKu8dXy4FAndXDZgZ4A=s0" alt="impact of images" width="800" height="556" /></p>
<p>Clearly, then, it’s essential that you add visuals to your posts in order to increase audience interaction as well as your online visibility.</p>
<p>Here are a few quick tips to help you create shareable visuals by combining photos and quotes.</p>
<h3>1. A Picture is Worth a Thousand Words</h3>
<p>The first step is finding photos that fit your business.</p>
<p>You can either use <a href="https://burst.shopify.com/">royalty-free photos from Shopify</a> or choose <a href="https://www.booxi.com/blog/6-outils-pour-avoir-des-photos-splendides-pour-votre-site-web/">one of the following solutions</a>.</p>
<p>Here’s an example that clearly illustrates the creative process.</p>
<p>Imagine that I’m the owner of a hair salon and I want to put a quote on my Facebook page.</p>
<p>The first thing I should do is write a list of keywords that relate to the services I offer.</p>
<p>For example:</p>
<ul>
<li>Hair</li>
<li>Hairdresser</li>
<li>Haircut</li>
</ul>
<p>Then I’ll do a photo search using those words.<br />
Once I find the picture I want, I’ll download it.</p>
<p>Here’s the one I decided to use:</p>
<p><span class="bx_text16"><img class="img_zoom aligncenter size-full wp-image-1051" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/51krfd-CQKddvJqRhBlb5gXp2s_EjtkE36VdXk8-teWg6rxh12iOn7TnXApwesURdh-0zBHKfbfWN-U702Hw6g=s0" alt="image for social network " /></span></p>
<p><span class="bx_text16">*Of course, if you have the time and resources to do it yourself (maybe you own a high quality camera, for example), by all means create your own visuals.</span></p>
<h3>2. Select the Quote</h3>
<p>Next thing you need to do is customize the picture in order to make it shareable. Like we talked about with keywords, you should select a quote that relates to what you do. The good news? It’s usually very easy to find an inspirational quote that’s connected to your field of work.</p>
<p><strong>Here’s a trick:</strong> Use the list of keywords you set up in step # 1 and do a Google search. For example, your search could be &#8220;Quotes + Hair&#8221;. You’ll quickly find a whole bunch of quotes. Now all you have to do is choose the one that suits your needs best.</p>
<p>Going back to my hair salon example, I’ll chose the following quote: &#8220;A woman who cut her hair is about to change her life&#8221; &#8211; Coco Chanel</p>
<h3>3. Customize the Image</h3>
<p>Now that you’ve found the picture and quote you need, all you have to do is to combine them.</p>
<p>To do so, just:</p>
<ul>
<li><a href="https://www.booxi.com/blog/create-your-canva-account-to-produce-your-own-visuals/">Create your Canva account</a>,</li>
<li>Select the type of visual you want to produce.<br />
In my case, I want a picture for my Facebook page, which is why I selected the “Facebook Post” option.<img class="img_zoom aligncenter size-full wp-image-1052" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/CRbKErVXRigar6K5gJH2QYC_IaVAbF4d78TmTo2S92tdVl9ECKAZ4WJa31qi3V48GGh9tn-iD7kVw4NMrIYB=s0" alt="social media type " /></li>
<li>Canva offers a variety of ready-to-use templates. Select the one you prefer.<img class="aligncenter" style="padding-top: 15px:" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/KrLkwIesQUG8rsby-UZWZfkXkOiUacC2Rczr8nxkJEPuR28jV2fjqdEVJC3ZFDQ2uDSji-yPwI1SXjZOfKn-=s0" alt="select-layout" width="508" height="592" /></li>
<li>Upload the picture you find online by clicking on the “Uploads” button, and then click on the “Upload your own images” button.<br />
<img class="img_zoom aligncenter size-full wp-image-1054" style="padding: 5px:" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/7OAVHrx6_FHoIR_17wsb3Qb5HYnOJYGDcavpe_vNqToQ16uNNs3bWFAM5rMBXSctfUbPRhishEOaaZZ2PJChZ40=s0" alt="upload-picture" /></li>
<li>Add the quote you selected earlier by clicking on the “Text” button. Then add the name of your business, but in a discrete fashion.</li>
<li>Save everything by clicking the “Download” button at the top right of the page.</li>
</ul>
<p>The following dropdown menu will appear:</p>
<p><img class="img_zoom aligncenter size-full wp-image-1056" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/DglwwJx2rXbBxd1iUcEV9tPpj4SilTbkmZbXfV-1vR6_ez7whPlIDAS8W20EhkdzwMCRTt8-VPqrbjh7bkyTfQ=s0" alt="format to download " /></p>
<p>Select the format you want when downloading. The .png and .jpeg formats are recommended.</p>
<p>Here’s the result:</p>
<p><img class="img_zoom aligncenter size-full wp-image-1057" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/iOnvhrNLFbMV3-nTNwrTB18EMnf5KjPLBmpaluTusJN_2bLfGZLq-83hIXRlP6ZBFi_SPc5mSWtytnWwJJYF3-w=s0" alt="visual creation" /></p>
<p>You can now post this picture on all your social networks. Analyze the results and repeat these steps any time you want.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.booxi.com/blog/how-to-create-shareable-images-that-drive-traffic/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Create Your Canva Account to Produce Your Own Visuals</title>
		<link>https://www.booxi.com/blog/create-your-canva-account-to-produce-your-own-visuals/</link>
		<comments>https://www.booxi.com/blog/create-your-canva-account-to-produce-your-own-visuals/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2017 14:56:51 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Astrid Bertout]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Tutorials]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[online visibility]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social network]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.booxi.com/blog/?p=1040</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Visual content is 40X more likely to get shared on social media than others types of content. By creating your Canva account, you can easily create images that fits with your business to illustrate your social media's publications.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img class="float_top aligncenter wp-image-1041 size-full" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/Fz91j7ffB9M4LUwUEN-NVnd3AIevnLq5J-vC7WfzDEkQKidT1eW9DIwsGaO6fdHElUWpeJXuw1-YuBZxwh40Qw=s0" alt="create your canva account" width="1280" height="720" />Canva is a solution that allows you to edit images to personalize them and make them fit with your business’ image.<br />
This can be very useful for customizing the images you publish on your social networks, for creating visuals for your Facebook ads, for illustrating your promotions newsletters or for illustrating your blog if you have one.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>#1 &#8211; Go on <a href="http://www.canva.com">Canva website</a>.</p>
<p><img class="img_zoom aligncenter size-full wp-image-1042" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/piHrKQqbyDg74XJ9HRsUslq9Z3xo3XplBMhpbNCpkyzCPEjQCkktQLdy3lMS75MWqapEUiyD3gIf38V3fU5oNMM=s0" alt="sign up with canva" /></p>
<p># 2 &#8211; If you have a Facebook account or a Google Account, click the appropriate button to speed up your account creation.</p>
<p>Otherwise click on &#8220;Sign up with Email&#8221; and follow the steps.</p>
<p># 3 &#8211; In order that Canva offers you the best possible templates according to your needs, select the reason for the creation of your account between the following options:</p>
<p><img class="img_zoom aligncenter size-full wp-image-1043" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/OouW60JHRjuZmf7ZbrP_2bxSVy5Z6trvOttm3KFXk0GZIupAVFh8QNQTIzgvVQLfDYR0yOr2LvoKu0mliDRRfg=s0" alt="Canva sign up completed" /></p>
<p>#4 &#8211; And it’s done.<br />
You can now start to<a href="https://www.booxi.com/blog/how-to-create-shareable-images-that-drive-traffic/"> customize your visuals for your social media publications</a>, for example.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.booxi.com/blog/create-your-canva-account-to-produce-your-own-visuals/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>7 Marketing Ideas to Get the Most Out of Valentine&#8217;s Day</title>
		<link>https://www.booxi.com/blog/7-marketing-ideas-to-get-the-most-out-of-valentines-day/</link>
		<comments>https://www.booxi.com/blog/7-marketing-ideas-to-get-the-most-out-of-valentines-day/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2017 21:22:33 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Astrid Bertout]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Business Tips]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[customer retention]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social network]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.booxi.com/blog/?p=908</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Seasonal events are good opportunities to establish strategies that will allow you to build your customer loyalty, get more customers, and increase sales. As Valentine's Day approaches, here are 7 promotion ideas to get the most out of this day.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img class="float_top aligncenter wp-image-911 size-full" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/dyb43YUGuykueGPLzASV4auOsouV37Nt3XVtHPizm4Z1FhFI3QnLlKEvBOvfxL-P66Yt0Csyz7vSVemG2A2Eqw=s0" alt="heart for Valentine Day" width="1200" height="600" /></p>
<p>Seasonal events are good opportunities to establish strategies that will allow you to build your customer loyalty, get more customers, and increase sales. As Valentine&#8217;s Day approaches, here are 7 promotion ideas to get the most out of this day.</p>
<ol>
<li>
<h2>Spread the Love</h2>
<p><a href="https://www.booxi.com/blog/get-the-most-out-of-your-client-list/" target="_blank">Easily export your customer list to import it into your free mailing solution</a>, such as <a href="https://mailchimp.com/" target="_blank">Mailchimp</a>, and surprise your customers.</p>
<p>♥ For example, you can send gift suggestions “For Him” or “For Her”, with products and services that you offer.<br />
♥ You can also send a coupon for a limited period of time (until february 14th), and with specific conditions to encourage your customers to use it during less busy hours.<br />
♥ Take advantage of this to remind your customers that Valentine’s week is very busy, so that they can book an appointment online to be sure to reserve their place.</li>
<li>
<h2>Get More Customers</h2>
<p>Invite your customers to refer their friends using invitation cards. For example the referred friend will enjoy a discount on his first appointment booked, while the customer who made that reference will receive a product or a sample as a reward. It’s a great time to create new businesses opportunities.</li>
<li>
<h2>Create Promotions to Increase Your Product&#8217;s Sales</h2>
<p>Since margins on products are higher than on services, you should take advantage of Valentine’s day to offer product combinations and increase your sales.</p>
<p>♥ For example you can offer a package with two products of the same line for a special price.<br />
♥ On the purchase of selected products, you can offer a second one at half-price.<br />
♥ If your customers can buy your products online, offer a free shipping or give them a specific promocode for Valentine’s Day.</p>
<p><img class="img_zoom aligncenter size-full wp-image-913" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/uegIf-OvJEsW7fMpPnyGgFMju_4FG2sOCmx6rpqO_5ZD1ccdAdlF4pPBXcLAiEsa3po5tiQzjqKZdO3-r16q1IU=s0" alt="Promotion for Valentine Day" /></li>
<li>
<h2>Highlight One of Your Partner</h2>
<p>You can take advantage of this day to establish joint strategies with one of your partner; a good way to take advantage of each other&#8217;s notoriety.<br />
It can be a product combination with your partner, or a promotion on a service offered by your partner for each visit to your shop during Valentine’s Day week and vice versa.<br />
You don’t have any partner yet? Create one! You could as example contact one of the local flower shops and offer a partnership for this occasion!</li>
<li>
<h2>Make Promotion on Your Social Networks</h2>
<p>Make the most out of Valentine’s Day by regularly publishing on your social networks and creating interaction on your pages.</p>
<p>♥ Share gift suggestions using products and services you offer.<br />
♥ Start a contest with little effort and in a few minutes. For example, you can ask your customers to comment on your publication with the name of a person with whom they would like to enjoy one of your services. Then make a draw where both names drawn will win a free appointment.</p>
<p><img class="img_zoom aligncenter size-full wp-image-912" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/AX9CYO5kC2DuLh2L5tHtCKm7K1b93sQopcOX9Eu0s31SGGjO02P4a56mINcy8tLDC84-cESt5ZZGQNWSpfVx=s0" alt="promotion for couple" /></p>
<p>♥ Make sure to share your current promotions on your social networks to optimize their impact.<br />
♥ You can also announce that there will be some surprise in your store on February 14th, or even for the entire week.</li>
<li>
<h2>Rewards Your Best Customers</h2>
<p>Valentine&#8217;s Day can be an opportunity to increase customer loyalty. If you have a small budget for this specific day you can spoil your customers during their visit on February 14th:</p>
<p>♥ Offer them chocolates, samples or discounts on their next appointment (make sure to keep a note not forget it).Use a tool that allows you to track appointments history and keep notes per customer.<br />
♥ Want to go even further? Send flowers to your three best customers! The positive word of mouth that this will generate is well worth it!</li>
<li>
<h2>Create an atmosphere in your store</h2>
<p>Make a romantic playlist using <a href="https://www.youtube.com/?hl=en&amp;gl=CA" target="_blank">Youtube</a> or <a href="http://8tracks.com/" target="_blank">8Tracks</a> for example and search words like “Love”. Add candles and chocolates on your counter, and at the end of an appointment offer a few samples… There are a lot of special attentions that you can offer during this day! It&#8217;s up to you to find the ones that suit you best.</li>
</ol>
<p>In most of our tips the visual you add to your message is crucial. Take a look at these 6 tools to find the perfect images.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.booxi.com/blog/7-marketing-ideas-to-get-the-most-out-of-valentines-day/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Take Advantage of the Holidays to Boost Your Social Networks!</title>
		<link>https://www.booxi.com/blog/take-advantage-of-the-holidays-to-boost-your-social-networks/</link>
		<comments>https://www.booxi.com/blog/take-advantage-of-the-holidays-to-boost-your-social-networks/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2016 21:57:45 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Astrid Bertout]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Business Tips]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[online visibility]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social network]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.booxi.com/blog/?p=828</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[It’s probably your most busy period of the year however with the right tools to schedule and make your social network publications, you can benefit from the Holidays to regularly publish. ]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img class="float_top aligncenter wp-image-829 size-full" src="https://booxi-live-wp-storage.storage.googleapis.com/social_medias.png" alt="boost your social networks during Holidays" width="1200" height="600" />This is probably your most busy period of the year; however, with the right tools to schedule and make your social network publications, you can benefit from the Holidays to regularly publish and interact on your social networks.</p>
<p style="text-align: center"><b>Virtual Decorations for the Holidays</b></p>
<p>Apply the decoration principle to your social networks by using images that reflect the Holidays spirit in your publications! Avoid waiting time on searching images, and use a website like StockUp that provides you lots of images for free, and is very easy to use.</p>
<p style="text-align: center"><b>Take the Time to Thank Your Customers</b></p>
<p>The Holidays is the right moment to get closer to your customers. So take the time to thank them for their loyalty by adding, for example a picture with all members of your team.</p>
<p style="text-align: center"><b>Inform Your Customers About Your Holidays Schedule</b></p>
<p>Make sure that your customers know about your schedule changes and that they can easily book appointments with you. Publish a post to remind your customers that they can book their appointment online. And<a href="https://www.booxi.com/blog/add-online-booking-to-facebook/"> add the Book Now call to action to your Facebook page</a> if it’s not done already.</p>
<p style="text-align: center"><b>Share Trends in Your Field</b></p>
<p>If you are for example, in the beauty, make up or hairstyle industry, spot styles and hairstyles that have been the most shared on Pinterest and Instagram and publish them on your social networks. Your audience will be pleased  to see that your are an expert and that you know the trends: an efficient and simple strategy to invite them to book an appointment online with you.</p>
<p style="text-align: center"><b>The Perfect Moment for Gifts</b></p>
<p>You can organize a contest to offer gifts to your audience on your social networks. It’s a very simple way to get more visibility and to reward people who like your page. Make it simple: for example it could be a sort!</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.booxi.com/blog/take-advantage-of-the-holidays-to-boost-your-social-networks/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>